<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<source><jobs><job><location>Austin, TX, US / Remote (US)</location><title>Technical Product Marketing Lead — Legion Health (Y Combinator startup)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>67775</job_reference><company>Legion Health</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/be7d0a2d4fa476f01e0a78557413302dbee2819e.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/legion-health</company_website><company_description>Pioneering psychiatry with AI</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/67775</url><description>About Legion Health
Legion Health is a pioneering telepsychiatry company dedicated to transforming patient care through advanced technology. We leverage cutting-edge language models and robust data analytics to enhance our patient-provider interactions, improve access to mental health services, and streamline our clinical operations.
Our mission is to integrate innovative AI solutions into every facet of psychiatric care, ensuring providers and patients benefit from the most effective and efficient treatment strategies.
About the role
Skills: Growth design, Marketing design, Data Modeling, Data Analytics
About Legion Health
Legion Health is a pioneering telepsychiatry startup dedicated to transforming patient care through advanced technology. We leverage cutting-edge language models and robust data analytics to enhance our patient-provider interactions, improve access to mental health services covered by insurance, and streamline our clinical operations. Our mission is to integrate innovative AI solutions into every facet of psychiatric care, ensuring providers and patients benefit from the most effective and efficient treatment strategies.
Legion Health is backed by Y Combinator; top-tier VCs including Soma Capital, UpHonest Capital, and Alumni Ventures; and unicorn angel investors including Erica Johnson (Co-Founder at Modern Health), Wei Deng (Founder at Clipboard Health), and Jarrett Streebin (Founder at EasyPost). Y Combinator is the world’s top startup accelerator and has backed companies like Airbnb, DoorDash, Instacart, and Coinbase.
About the Role
We are seeking a highly skilled and driven Technical Product Marketing Lead to join our dynamic team. This role is critical in driving our patient acquisition and clinician hiring funnels, product improvements, and top-of-funnel growth. You will be a key player in setting up modern analytics software like PostHog to drive user feedback, working with engineering and design to create an exceptional patient experience, and leading growth experiments.
This is a full-time position at a fast-growing, high-impact startup. It is not a typical 9-5 job. We seek passionate individuals dedicated to transforming mental health care and serving millions of patients lacking access. Candidates must be ready to work hard and make a significant impact. While this is primarily a product marketing role, you will be expected to contribute as a generalist across various functions and be ready to jump in wherever needed to support the team and company objectives.
Responsibilities
Analytics and Measurement: Measure analytics for patient acquisition and clinician hiring funnels.
Product Improvements: Enhance leads, conversion, and retention through product improvements.
Modern Analytics Setup: Implement and manage analytics software like PostHog for user feedback.
Cross-functional Collaboration: Partner with engineering and design teams to create a superior patient experience.
Growth Experiments: Design and execute growth experiments to boost top-of-funnel performance.
Website Enhancements: Improve website to increase traffic and user engagement.
Strategic Growth Thinking: Strategize top-of-funnel growth and support related efforts.
Technical Generalist: Apply technical skills across product, design, and engineering to develop top-notch products.
Data-driven Decisions: Use data to shape marketing strategies and product development.
Market Research: Identify growth opportunities through market research.
Customer Insights: Analyze customer insights to guide product and marketing decisions.
Campaign Management: Plan, execute, and optimize multi-channel marketing campaigns.
Content Development: Create and oversee marketing content to drive engagement and conversions.
Skills and Qualifications
Technical Expertise: Strong technical skills and ability to work across product, design, and engineering.
Analytics Proficiency: Experience with modern analytics tools like PostHog.
Product Marketing Experience: Proven success in product marketing and growth experiments.
Cross-functional Collaboration: Excellent at working with engineering, design, and other teams.
Strategic Thinking: Strong strategic thinking and problem-solving skills.
Market and Customer Insight: Ability to analyze market and customer data to drive decisions.
Campaign Management: Experienced in planning and executing marketing campaigns.
Content Development: Skilled in creating engaging, conversion-driven content.
Early-stage Startup Experience: Experience in a pre-Series A startup is a plus but not required.
About the Interview Process
Phone Interview: Initial call with co-founder and CTO.
Technical Interview/Workshop: Deep dive into technical skills and problem-solving capabilities.
Case Study: Tackle a real-world problem related to our current technical challenges.
Interview with Co-founders: Discuss vision, motivation, and fit.
Interview with Technical Advisor: Additional insights and assessments.
Reference Checks: Confirm past achievements and qualifications.
Compensation
Salary: $80,000 to $160,000
Equity: 0.20% - 1.00%
Location
Austin, TX, US / Remote (US; MX; AR; BR)
Remote: Yes
Join us at Legion Health and be a part of revolutionizing mental health care through advanced technology and innovative AI solutions.
Technology
Technology at Legion
We are revolutionizing telepsychiatry through a core AI infrastructure that enables a vastly improved patient experience and quality of mental health care. We are actively improving our services in ingesting, chunking, embedding, caching, and searching to achieve this goal. Our technical goals include:
Enhanced processing: Implement robust data structures and caching mechanisms to handle increasing volumes of language data spanning every facet of patients’ care while minimizing latency and maximizing system responsiveness.
System scalability: Ensure our systems can scale effectively to support growth from one million to hundreds of millions of data points.
Securing sensitive data: Uphold the highest standards of data security and privacy in compliance with HIPAA guidelines.
##Stack TypeScript, Node.js, PostgreSQL, Redis, Supabase, Azure, Google Cloud, AWS, LangChain, PostHog, Retool
Interview Process
Phone Interview: Initial call with co-founder and CTO.
Technical Interview/Workshop: Deep dive into technical skills and problem-solving capabilities.
Case Study: Tackle a real-world problem related to our current technical challenges.
Interview with Co-founders: Discuss vision, motivation, and fit.
Interview with Technical Advisor: Additional insights and assessments.
Reference Checks: Confirm past achievements and qualifications.</description><min_compensation>$80K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$160K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>New York, NY, US</location><title>Full Stack iOS Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>67758</job_reference><company>Alinea</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/309f21a43676330a7d4946870c8eaef1865fe8b0.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/alinea</company_website><company_description>Automated investing for the next generation 💸</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/67758</url><description>About Alinea
Alinea is an investing app for GenZs. We’re a Y Combinator backed start-up and have raised $5.5M from top investors including Goodwater Capital, F7 Ventures, and GFR.
We are looking to build out a team of passionate and driven individuals who want to make an impact. Come join us!
About the role
We're looking for strong applied full stack iOS engineering candidates to join Alinea. If your aspirations are to become VP Engineering one day, we'd like to help you get there. If you'd rather be heads-down building product for the foreseeable future, great. But either way, the latter will be your focus in the near term.
Alinea is an investing app for GenZs. We’re a Y Combinator backed start-up and have raised over $5.5M for our seed round from top investors including Goodwater Capital, F7 Ventures, GFR and Worklife Ventures. Alinea is looking for a talented engineer to lead the design and development of the Alinea iOS app and work directly with the founding team. We are looking for an ambitious, fast-moving, and creative individual who will address customer needs to build the best investing experience for the next generation. This may not be the right role for you if you are uncomfortable with any of the following:
1. Trying to predict the customer's needs yourself
2. Working on different parts of the stack
3. A role that will push you to learn new skill sets constantly
Responsibilities
Work directly with the founders and lead designer to define the product roadmap and report directly to the Co-CEOs and CTO
Help guide and implement our overall product roadmap
Qualifications
3+ years Software Engineering experience (or 1+ years Full Stack Development)
Excellent communication skills are critical
Grounding in CS fundamentals—you've got the broad-based knowledge needed to build a collaborative, client-server application end to end. You may need to pick up some new platforms &amp; skills along the way but you're good at that and it's fun for you.
You enjoy delivering delightful, polished front ends. You needn't be a designer—but you enjoy working with them and appreciate the work that goes into achieving that polish and delight.
An interest in product strategy, a desire to collaborate, resonance with our values, and a sense of humor. A willingness to step on others' toes respectfully and kindly, and to have the same done to you.
Experience working at small startups (not required but preferred)
Our Tech Stack
iOS Swift
Next.js + Typescript 4 + Node.js(Express) + Firebase + Socket.io + Redux         
MongoDB + AWS(EB, EC2, CloudWatch, CodeDeploy)                      
Swift 5 + Programmatic UI + MVVM-C Architecture
Technology
iOS Swift
Next.js + Typescript 4 + Node.js(Express) + Firebase + Socket.io + Redux
MongoDB + AWS(EB, EC2, CloudWatch, CodeDeploy)
Swift 5 + Programmatic UI + MVVM-C Architecture</description><min_compensation>$120K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$175K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US / Remote</location><title>Machine Learning PhD Scientist</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>67668</job_reference><company>Ten Lives</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/e831961d555ac79ac4d50f463f10bdbd3cfc71ad.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/ten-lives</company_website><company_description>Decarbonizing food proteins with AI.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/67668</url><description>About Ten Lives
Ten Lives (YC S22) is pioneering research in AI and biology to feed the world, sustainably. Our flagship brand decarbonizes the pet food industry by reducing the fifth of the world’s meat consumed by pets.
About the role
Ten Lives is tackling the climate emergency by optimizing microbial factories with AI. With backing from YC / Collab Fund and NSF grants, we’re decoding the microbial genome to produce food proteins at the lowest cost and environmental impact.
Ten Lives is seeking a motivated Machine Learning Scientist to tackle the problem of DNA sequence design. This position offers an opportunity to work at the forefront of AI research, applying advances from natural language processing to the language of life - DNA. As an early employee, you will have the opportunity to lead research initiatives and collaborate with our interdisciplinary team of computational and experimental scientists.
What we offer at Ten Lives
Real impact. Ten Lives can directly reduce global emissions by 1% by 2040.
Supportive environment to explore, innovate, and drive research direction.
We encourage publishing and presenting scientific findings.
Competitive salary, comprehensive health insurance, PTO, and 401(k) matching.
Hybrid / remote-friendly.
Responsibilities:
Implement, optimize, and deploy state-of-the-art machine learning models for DNA sequence design.
Develop efficient, robust code and data pipelines, ensuring high-quality results.
Analyze and interpret computational approaches, presenting findings to colleagues in regular update meetings.
Establish automated processes to continually evaluate and enhance our design methodology.
Collaborate with diverse teams across biology and machine learning, contributing to the scientific and strategic vision of the company.
Qualifications:
PhD degree in Machine Learning, Mathematics, Computational Biology, Statistics, Physics, or related disciplines.
Demonstrated ability to implement and analyze state-of-the-art models for sequential data (text / genomic / time series) and/or expertise in explainability methods.
Proficiency in writing clean and efficient code and deploying services on cloud computing platforms like GCP, AWS, or Azure.
Interest in climate solutions and likes cats.</description><min_compensation>$150K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$225K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US / South San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Sr Robotics Software Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>67466</job_reference><company>Andromeda Surgical</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/ad29152e507992c17de56b3d0a62d1fd6769fd3b.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/andromeda-surgical</company_website><company_description>Autonomous surgical robots</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/67466</url><description>About Andromeda Surgical
We are building autonomous surgical robots to drastically shorten the learning curve for surgeons.
About the role
Skills: C++, Python
The ideal candidate is self-motivated and multi-tasker. You will be part of a small team with high level of expertize in different areas so team dynamics and communication will be key. You should excel in working with high performance and real time systems.
Responsibilities
Writing clean, high-quality, high-performance, maintainable code
Taking charge of the Localization, Planning, and Controls of the robot arm
Support test and deployment of new products and features
Architect robust software systems
Participate in code reviews
Qualifications
Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science (or related field)
3+ years of relevant work experience
Expertise in C++ and/or python
Experience working with Linux based systems
Experience with ROS/ROS2 (Robot Operating System) is a plus
Experience with cloud technologies
Experience with Agile or Scrum software development methodologies
Experience with Medical/Healthcare technologies is a plus
Technology
We are using off the shelf robot hardware and building controls, planning, ML algorithms to take high level guidance from surgeons and execute surgical steps faster and with more precision than the surgeon themselves. This requires low latency and high accuracy planning and controls, computer vision for anatomical landmark detection, building intuitive user interface for the surgeons to issues commands from.</description><min_compensation>$150K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$250K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US / Remote</location><title>Full Stack Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>67363</job_reference><company>Infisical</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/621cb43ec50d1aae545391abcc114014c84d295f.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/infisical</company_website><company_description>Open-source secrets manager for developers</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/67363</url><description>About Infisical
Infisical is the #1 open source secret management platform – used by tens of thousands of developers.
We raised $3M from Y Combinator, Gradient Ventures (Google's VC fund), and awesome angel investors like Elad Gil, Arash Ferdowsi (founder/ex-CTO of Dropbox), Paul Copplestone (founder/CEO of Supabase), James Hawkins (founder/CEO of PostHog), Andrew Miklas (founder/ex-CTO of PagerDuty), Diana Hu (GP at Y Combinator), and more.
We are default alive, and have signed many customers ranging from fastest growing startups to post-IPO enterprises.
About the role
Skills: Go, Kubernetes, TypeScript, Docker, Amazon Web Services (AWS)
About Infisical
Infisical is the #1 open source secret management platform for developers. In other words, we help organizations manage API-keys, DB access tokens, certificates, and other credentials across all parts of their infra! In fact, we process over 2B of such secrets per month.
Our customers already include some of the largest public enterprises and some of the fastest-growing startups. Developers love us and every day our community is growing stronger! Join us on a mission to make security easier for all developers – starting from secret management.
About this role
Infisical is looking for a full stack engineer to help us build, optimize, and create the foundations of the product. You will be working closely with our CTO and the rest of the engineering team on:
making Infisical usable across a wide range of tech stacks;
maintaining our infrastructure;
ensuring our customers have a great experience;
implementing and advancing functionality like automatic secret rotation;
experimenting with new approaches for secret management in the AI world.
Overall, you’re going to be one of the defining pieces of our team as we scale to thousands of customers over the next 18 months.
About you
This job will require you to be a Swiss army knife of an engineer. Overall, this role demands the following pivotal skills:
Proven expertise in infrastructure management, tooling, and optimization.
Experience with Docker and/or Kubernetes.
Understanding of cloud-native architecture (AWS preferred) and Infrastructure as Code (Terraform)
Proficiency in TypeScript and/or Go.
On any given day, you may be:
developing new features that will be used by tens of thousands of developers.
working on resiliency and stability of the Infisical platform.
improving security and cryptography practices.
squashing bugs as well as talking to our community and enterprise customers.
hyper-polishing Infisical's UI/UX/DX.
presenting your work (e.g., new features/learnings) through blogs or videos to our community. or all of the above!
How you will grow?
With this role, you play the defining role in building out Infisical, choosing the right technologies, setting up all the necessary processes from the start, solving scalability issues, as well as making sure that our community and customer base keeps growing.
As our team grows and you get more experience on the team, you'll also have the opportunity to fully own particular parts of the platform end-to-end.
Team, Values &amp; Benefits
Our team has worked across transformative tech companies, from Figma to AWS to Red Hat.
We have an office in San Francisco, but we are mostly a remote team. We try to get together as often as possible – whether it's for an off-site, conferences, or just get-togethers. This is a full-time role open to anyone in North/South American and European time zones.
At Infisical, we will treat you well with a competitive salary and equity offer. Depending on your risk tolerance, we would love to talk more with you about the range of options available between the two. For some other benefits (including lunch stipend, work setup budget, etc), please check out our careers page: https://infisical.com/careers.</description><min_compensation>$50K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$150K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Burlington, MA, US</location><title>Silicon Photonics Engineer / Associate Silicon Photonics Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>67284</job_reference><company>SiPhox Health</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/fdae89b0d904fabc52fea58355efccbccf5d0bfd.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/siphox-health</company_website><company_description>Wearable and At-Home protein monitoring with silicon photonic chips</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/67284</url><description>About SiPhox Health
Wearable and At-Home protein monitoring with silicon photonic chips
About the role
Skills: MATLAB, Python
SiPhox Health is developing a revolutionary home testing platform for biomarkers linked with inflammation, hormones, and metabolic/cardiovascular health. 6 out of 10 Americans have a chronic disease, and our mission is to enable new direct-to-consumer health and wellness paradigms to address this crisis. Our chip-based solution combines biochemistry with state-of-the-art integrated photonics, electronics, and microfluidics.
We are looking for a skilled and motivated Silicon Photonics Engineer to join our team as we scale up and advance the photonics capabilities that power our system.
Key responsibilities:
Design and verification of novel photonic devices and circuits
Build and refine experimental setups for effectively coupling light into optical chips
Conduct detailed optical measurements and functional biosensing experiments to characterize the performance of photonic devices
Analyze data from wafer and chip characterization to assess and improve device performance
Document results and clearly present findings and insights to the team
Qualifications and Skills:
M.S. or Ph.D. in integrated photonics (Electrical Engineering, Applied Physics, Optics, or related field)
Experience participating in or leading design/layout/characterization cycles of photonic devices with commercial foundries
Demonstrated track record of creative multidisciplinary design and hands-on problem solving to bring those designs to fruition
Expert with photonic characterization tools such as lasers, photodetectors, and data acquisition systems
Experience in photonics simulation software such as Tidy3D, Lumerical, or COMSOL Multiphysics
Experience in photonics layout software such as Luceda IPKISS, KLayout, gdsfactory, Cadence, or Synopsys
Proficient in Python or MATLAB
Familiarity with one or more is a plus: biosensors, microfluidics, optical chip packaging
Technology
We are developing a new paradigm for consumer health tech wearables by replacing a 100lb optical instrument with an area of silicon smaller than a postage stamp.</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US / Remote (US)</location><title>Founding Full-Stack Software Engineer (React / React Native / Node.js / NestJS)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>67195</job_reference><company>Carma</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/995749b249373d88528eca173b29dc4d2d8e77da.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/carma</company_website><company_description>Same-Day Auto Repair for Commercial Fleets.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/67195</url><description>About Carma
Same-Day Auto Repair for Commercial Fleets.
We’re Carma, a Y Combinator-backed, first-of-its-kind marketplace platform for commercial fleets to get correct car repair, fast and fair. Our mission is to solve the massive $573B problem with commercial auto repair – difficulty for commercial fleets to efficiently shop for automotive service and difficulty for auto repair shops to attract customers.
Carma is a B2B managed marketplace for commercial fleet owners to get same-day automotive repair for any vehicle with instant transparent offers and guaranteed pricing. Every year, fleet owners spend $573B on auto repairs globally.
Fleet owners request any service through our mobile app, which we send to our network of highly-vetted partner service centers. Our partner service centers give users real-time offers on their requested services.
Our fleet customers save upwards of 50% when they use Carma vs. the median price for the same service in their zip code, while our partner service centers increase their revenues and obtain new customers.
Backed by Y Combinator - Winter 2024 Batch.
About the role
Skills: Android, CSS, GraphQL, HTML, iOS, JavaScript, Node.js, React, React Native, TypeScript, PostgreSQL, Amazon Web Services (AWS)
Type of Role: 100% Remote or In-Person (Candidate Preference)
Start Date: ASAP
Compensation:
Cash: $175,000 - $200,000
Equity: 3.00% - 4.00%
Candidate Requirements:
Attended a reputable 4-year university in the United States with a strong CS program
A strong product-oriented mindset and excellent communication skills
Have an eagerness to build solutions to challenging problems in a fast-paced and autonomous environment, as candidates will take on a wide set of responsibilities
Have an interest in the automotive space
Must be physically located in the United States (no international candidates)
Ideal candidate has:
Has strong personal projects that demonstrate that you have built and shipped products, for which there are current active users
Current job or previous job is at a high-growth startup or market-leading tech company, where you have demonstrated fast-track career progression in those roles
Has experience building marketplaces, reverse marketplaces, or auction systems
In this role, you will:
Design and build a highly scalable web and mobile application that can handle 1M+ users
Deliver across the full software development cycle including coding, testing, implementation, and support
You will need to support building a production-level front-end design and will be leading our UX/UI designers and front-end engineers
Work directly with the CEO and business team by recommending enhancements to improve user experience
Help define and communicate technical and design requirements
Identify, troubleshoot, and resolve performance issues at the code and UI layers
Participate with internal departments in requirements gathering, analysis, and specification, providing technical expertise and recommendations
Provide training, help, and support to other team members
Develop internal processes to assist the fast-growing team
Communicate with engineering teams throughout the organization to build world-class products
Benefits and Perks:
Highly compensation package based on your skills and experience
Long-term opportunity with significant potential for salary growth
Friendly, close-knit atmosphere working directly with founding team
Ability to make an outsized impact and get in on the ground floor of an explosive growth startup, and one of the top startups in Y Combinator’s Winter 2024 batch
Skills Required:
Backend Development
Building backends in NestJS or Node.js.
Experience working with both relational and non-relational databases, preferably PostgreSQL.
Strong familiarity with event-driven architecture.
Frontend Development
Advanced proficiency and experience with React.js / Redux / Other State manager, ECMAScript 6.
Experience working with Redux / Redux Toolkit.
Experience with React Hooks.
Strong experience in HTML / JavaScript / CSS in a production environment.
Typescript / Styled-components / Other preprocessor; Jest, NPM.
API and Integration
Experience leveraging APIs for deep integrations with both iOS and Android platforms.
Experience working with remote data via REST and JSON.
Experience working with REST APIs (Axios / React Query).
Experience with integrating third-party libraries and APIs.
DevOps and CI/CD
Experience with AWS.
Familiarity with CI/CD Pipeline, code versioning, and SDLC processes.
Proficient with cloud-based DevOps.
Experience with Git and branching workflows.
Software Engineering Principles
Strong understanding of OOP.
Software design skills and design patterns.
Ability to maintain code to ensure the product is of the highest quality.
Ability to write well-documented, clean code.
Additional Skills
Testing frameworks and methodologies (e.g., unit testing, integration testing).
Experience with performance optimization techniques.
Familiarity with GraphQL.
Knowledge of security best practices for web applications.
Additional skills that ideal candidate has:
Mobile and Web Development
Building iOS/Android mobile apps in React Native.
Building web apps in React.
Publishing iOS/Android apps to the App Store and Google Play Store.
Mobile Development Specific
Strong knowledge of iOS/Android UI design principles, patterns, and best practices.
Solid understanding of iOS/Android development platforms such as Push Notification, iOS/Android SDKs, and Frameworks.
Familiarity with native build tools like XCode, Gradle, and Android Studio.
About Carma - Same-Day Auto Repair for Commercial Fleets.
We’re Carma, a Y Combinator-backed, first-of-its-kind marketplace platform for commercial fleets to get correct car repair, fast and fair. Our mission is to solve the massive $573B problem with commercial auto repair – difficulty for commercial fleets to efficiently shop for automotive service and difficulty for auto repair shops to attract customers.
Carma is a B2B managed marketplace for commercial fleet owners to get same-day automotive repair for any vehicle with instant transparent offers and guaranteed pricing. Every year, fleet owners spend $573B on auto repairs globally.
Fleet owners request any service through our mobile app, which we send to our network of highly-vetted partner service centers. Our partner service centers give users real-time offers on their requested services.
Our fleet customers save upwards of 50% when they use Carma vs. the median price for the same service in their zip code, while our partner service centers increase their revenues and obtain new customers.
Backed by Y Combinator - Winter 2024 Batch.
Technology
If you are a highly technical, fast-paced coder (full-stack, frontend, or backend) and love solving complex challenges, especially building mobile apps, then we want you to apply. We are looking for someone who has experience or specializes in:
• Building iOS/Android mobile apps in React Native, Swift, or Kotlin • Building web apps in React • Building backends in NestJS or Node.js • Building marketplaces, reverse marketplaces, or auction systems
These more technical skills are an additional plus:
• Strong knowledge of iOS/Android UI design principles, patterns, and best practices • Experience leveraging APIs for deep integrations with both iOS and Android platforms • Experience working with remote data via REST and JSON • Solid understanding of mobile development platforms, including iOS Frameworks, Android Libraries, SDKs, and APIs for push notifications • Familiarity with native build tools like XCode, Gradle, and Android Studio • Experience with AWS • Experience with React Hooks • Ability to write clean, well-documented code • An entrepreneurial mentality where you are comfortable working in an exciting, fast-paced, and autonomous environment • Prior startup experience where you have worked on building a mobile app or something else from scratch • A strong product-oriented mindset • Interest in cars and automotive is a plus
Interview Process
Interview process: Behavioral Zoom Screen (20-30 min), Technical Zoom Screen (60min), Live Coding Challenge (120 min), Offer
We move quickly with the interview process, typically extending offers same-day or next day. We try to schedule the Live Coding Challenge as soon as possible if you pass the Zoom Screens.</description><min_compensation>$175K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Founding engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>66742</job_reference><company>InspectMind AI</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/380201f9cadb6a3d51cb0328080b2378d425269f.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/inspectmind-ai</company_website><company_description>Write Construction Inspections Reports using AI, up to 10x faster</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/66742</url><description>About InspectMind AI
InspectMind AI is changing the game for people who build and design buildings by making it super easy to do their paperwork. Our tool uses AI to quickly turn videos and photos from construction sites into detailed, accurate and well formatted reports. What used to take days of typing and organizing now takes just minutes. With our app, workers can spend less time at their desks and more time doing the important stuff on site.
About the role
Skills: JavaScript, React Native, Machine Learning
InspectMind AI is revolutionizing construction inspections by harnessing the power of the recent cutting-edge AI breakthroughs. We are transforming a traditional industry by unlocking the potential of LLM to tackle real-world challenges, improving productivity by 100x, and creating groundbreaking solutions that have never been done before.
We are seeking our second founding engineer to work alongside a team from Google, Airbnb, Adobe, Berkeley, and CMU, bringing decades of experience in building large-scale software and successful companies.
You will have the exciting opportunity to:
Design and write code across our full stack end-to-end, from frontend, backend to LLM pipeline, making a huge and immediate impact on our product and company growth
Provide hands-on customer support and iterate our software to deliver the best user experience possible
Must-have qualifications:
Exceptional coding skills and the ability to ship high-quality code daily
Strong product ownership and the drive to deliver end-to-end features while making sound daily decisions
Must have a passion for building the best user experience and a genuine care for our customers' needs
Exceptionally fast learner, thriving in a fast-paced environment and comfortable working across the full stack
Preferred qualifications:
Proficiency in our tech stack: React Native, Node.js, and AWS
Experience in building LLM applications, computer vision and ML
3+ years of experience shipping high-quality production code
If you’re ready to be a part of a hyper-focused, fast-paced, and talented team, and work on the latest AI technology, we'd love to hear from you!
Technology
React Native, Node.js, AWS, LLM</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Finance Software: Implementation and Customer Success Lead</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>66720</job_reference><company>Campfire</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b964d406b730adef7e1ad9fcd6fdf8775ca296fc.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/campfire-2</company_website><company_description>A modern version of NetSuite</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/66720</url><description>About Campfire
Campfire is the modern accounting platform for startups and mid-size tech companies. Features include a powerful general ledger, invoicing, billing, revenue accounting and reporting, financial statements, AI-powered conversational reporting, and automated accounting workflows such as bank reconciliation. The product is natively integrated with industry leading solutions such as Ramp, Brex, Rho, Stripe, and has over 100+ API endpoints to build custom integrations and workflows. Campfire is a modern replacement for legacy, small business accounting software and mid-market ERPs.
Campfire's customers range from Seed to Series C with a variety of business models including SaaS, usage, FinTech, consulting and transactions — from startups like Suger and Parallel to mid-size companies like Carbon Direct, Sprig and Delphia.
The company is headquartered in San Francisco and backed by Foundation Capital, Y Combinator and Twenty Two Ventures.
About the role
Location: This role will be working out of our headquarters in San Francisco, CA five days per week.
About Campfire:
Campfire is a modern, accounting general ledger designed specifically for mid-size tech companies. Backed by Y Combinator, Foundation Capital, and many finance and accounting leaders in tech, we are on a mission to streamline financial operations for high-growth tech companies. Think of it as a modern version of Netsuite.
Job Description:
We are seeking a driven and customer-centric Implementation and Customer Success Lead to join our growing team. In this role, you will be responsible for guiding our customers through the implementation process, ensuring a smooth transition onto our platform, and providing ongoing support to maximize their success. The role requires working with financial data for our customers, while also being customer facing.
Key Responsibilities:
- Lead the implementation process for new customers, including project scoping, timeline development, and resource allocation
- Work closely with customers to understand their unique requirements and configure our platform to meet their needs
- Develop and deliver comprehensive training programs to ensure clients are proficient in using our software
- Serve as the primary point of contact for assigned accounts, building strong relationships and fostering client loyalty
- Monitor client health, usage, and satisfaction, proactively identifying and resolving potential issues
- Collaborate with internal teams, including sales and engineering, to provide feedback and drive continuous improvement
Requirements:
- Ideal candidate has 2 to 5 years of experience in a related field such as finance, investment banking, software implementations, customer success, or a related field (flexible for the right candidate)
- Strong project management skills, with the ability to manage multiple implementations simultaneously
- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills, with a proven ability to build rapport with customers
- Experience in the accounting, finance, or technology sectors is a plus
- Proficiency in G Suite, Salesforce, and other relevant tools
- Bachelor's degree or equivalent experience
Benefits:
- Competitive salary and equity package
- Full coverage of healthcare costs for you and 80% for your dependents, inclusive of medical, dental, and vision insurance
To apply:
Please submit your resume and a short, personal note on why you’re a great fit for the role and why you are excited about joining the Campfire team.
Technology
We use Django in the backend, and NextJS in the frontend.</description><min_compensation>$85K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$115K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Scientist I - Molecular Biology &amp; Assay Development</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>66606</job_reference><company>Medium Biosciences</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/0f30f00dbe44cde67296a43e445c0bb0dc14f9b5.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/medium-biosciences</company_website><company_description>AI to design any biomolecule for any function</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/66606</url><description>About Medium Biosciences
Medium Bio is developing new assays &amp; AI models to design biomolecules, starting with antibodies. We believe that the most impactful AI developments will be derived from fast, accurate simulations of the biophysical world. In particular, biomolecule design will help create new therapies for various diseases, grow our understanding of nature, and create lasting abundance.
We are a venture-backed rapidly growing early stage startup. Now is the most exciting time to join us as we expand our AI &amp; Bio team!
About the role
Skills: Biology, Cell biology, Protein engineering
About you
We are seeking a passionate, self-motivated scientist excited about protein design and the development of our platform. You will work with the team to design and validate assays for high-throughput multiplexed protein characterization starting with binding. You will be a part of founding team charting new path for how we design proteins.
Experience independently designing experimental strategies, executing experiments, analyzing data
Work successfully executing a high-throughput assay in academic or industry setting, in particular display assays
Comfortable working in fast-pace environment
You have a growth mindset, are curious and a fast learner
You have good written, oral and visual communications skills in English
Ideal/Pluses:
Experience with designing, implementing, and validating new genetic circuits for specific functional reporters
Experience with engineering mammalian cell lines (e.g. growing, transfecting, troubleshoot, etc)
Experience with developing and integrating biochemical models to analyze and tune experimental design
About the role:
We are looking for candidates who are excited about the opportunity to join the founding team and play an expanding role in the company. Your responsibilities will include:
Development and execution of high throughput library construction and molecular cloning
Design, execution, and fine-tune new in-vitro display techniques (yeast, phage)
NGS and nanopore sequence prep, data collection, and analysis
Protein expression and characterization (e.g. bacteria protein expression, stability, ELISA, SPR, etc)
Work with CROs on to execute on some experiments
Reviewing new literature and integrating findings into experimental design and implementation.
Technology
We are perform biological experiments and build AI models to generate protein structure &amp; sequence performing given biological function. Computational tools we use include:
Machine Learning: Pytorch, Pytorch Geometric, JAX
MLOps: AWS, GitHub, Weights &amp; Biases</description><min_compensation>$90K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$140K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Founding Engineer 🛠️ 🚀</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>66513</job_reference><company>Momentic</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b019cbaf6c0eb247cf32394bf286011b28e84660.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/momentic</company_website><company_description>Automate software testing with AI</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/66513</url><description>About Momentic
One of the most tedious parts of software development is testing. The testing industry has long been plagued with archaic and fragmented software, with Selenium turning 20 years old this year.
By leveraging cutting-edge AI, we’re able to automate the most time-consuming tasks so engineers can focus on what matters, shipping features to customers. Engineers at companies like Chegg and Retool use Momentic to author E2E, UI, API, load, and a11y tests 10X faster.
About the role
Skills: Kubernetes, Node.js, React, TypeScript, Machine Learning
As a founding engineer at Momentic, you will:
Own the entire technical stack, from our foundational AI layer to the customer-facing web app.
Speak with customers regularly to hear their feedback and support them.
Be involved in roadmap prioritization and sequencing of our deliverables.
Document everything as you go, and share knowledge with the team.
To succeed in this role, you’ll need:
To be based in San Francisco and able to work regularly from our SoMa office.
Practical experience building products powered by LLMs.
Great written and verbal communication.
To have a high sense of agency and accountability and can prioritize your work without much outside input.
To be able to immerse yourself in unfamiliar topics and understand complex technical concepts to make informed decisions.
Interest in AI and software testing tools tools.
Technology
We're at the cutting edge of applied AI. We utilize advanced techniques so our AI agents can accurately reason about and interact with any software application.
Our stack:
TypeScript Next.js frontend with web sockets
TypeScript Node.js Express backend with web sockets
Auto-scaling Kubernetes infrastructure to handle arbitrary testing loads with 99.9% reliability
A variety of LLM providers, including custom finetuned domain-specific models
LLM tooling such as multi-provider routing, observability, and intelligent caching</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US / Lausanne, VD, CH / FR / Remote (FR; CH; IT; DE; US)</location><title>Full-stack engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>66393</job_reference><company>Stacksync</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/a1ba092cd9748f3108933638ddb6bec186691eb6.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/stacksync</company_website><company_description>Real-time and two-way sync between CRMs and Databases</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/66393</url><description>About Stacksync
Stacksync powers real-time and two-way data synchronization between CRMs and Databases. Engineers and RevOps teams use Stacksync to (1) build backbone CRM integrations, (2) build internal tools on real-time customer data and (3) ship customer metrics from their database/data warehouse to their business teams.
About the role
Skills: Vue.js, Flask, Python, React, Redis, Docker, PostgreSQL
Build high-performance enterprise systems integration like never before.
Stack:
Python backend
VueJs/React Frontend
Postgres
Docker
Build and deliver things you thought impossible, because nothing is impossible!
Technology
With two-way sync, you can not only consume but also write data to your CRM from your database all with SQL queries. This drastically simplifies your backend and reduces implementation delay and costs by 90%.
Interview Process
meet with our team
prove your tech skills with intuitive real world cases (no exam!)
architecture and system design</description><min_compensation>$60K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$150K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Vancouver, BC, CA,San Francisco, CA, US / Remote (US; CA)</location><title>Founding Software Engineer, Full Stack/Product</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>66268</job_reference><company>Gumloop</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/9fb7e0ce6656ba8369bfc7fdddd4235e6657221b.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/gumloop</company_website><company_description>A no-code platform for automating workflows with AI</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/66268</url><description>About Gumloop
Gumloop is a platform for automating repetitive and complex workflows end-to-end with AI.
Builders drag, drop, and connect modular components onto a canvas to build powerful automations. We provide the tools and the infrastructure to operate at 10x the speed of writing, testing, and productionizing code so you can focus on the problem at hand.
About the role
Skills: JavaScript, React
As a founding engineer, we want you to help shape the core product and build across the stack
Play a leading role in improving overall UX by identifying areas of user friction and addressing them with product iterations.
Speak to users to identify their needs. Subsequently scope and implement improvements to the platform.
Act as a product leader, taking full ownership over parts of our product and roadmap.
Work directly with founders to shape and influence the direction of the product and contribute to the engineering strategy.
You’ll be successful in this role if you…
Are a relentlessly resourceful engineer with 2-6 years of experience building real-world applications, with a high bar for quality.
If you’ve personally built something people use, minimum years of experience is much less important to us.
Can rapidly go from 0 to 1 in building apps in React, Typescript and TailwindCSS.
Care deeply about those who use what you build
Enjoy working collaboratively and can communicate effectively
Bonus points
Prior experience as a founder or founding engineer.


PS - The team is in Vancouver now, but is headed to San Francisco later this year. If you're in SF, they'd love for you to pop up to Vancouver a few times over the summer. And if you're in Canada, they're on the lookout for people who are willing to relocate in the fall. The Gumloop team is happy to assist with travel and relocation.
Technology
React, Typescript, Python, Flask, GCP, Reactflow
Interview Process
Introductory zoom call screening
Technical interview.
Paid multi-day trial period where we work together to determine if it’s a fit. We’ll match the trial pay to whatever salary you’re currently making or market rate to compensate for your time.</description><min_compensation>$110K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$175K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Mateo, CA, US / Remote</location><title>Founding Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>65698</job_reference><company>Roe AI</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/c6e62176aed0b225675a38d104b2bd4aa8deb20e.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/roe-ai</company_website><company_description>Data warehouse to query unstructured data like docs, webs, imgs &amp; more</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/65698</url><description>About Roe AI
At Roe AI, we are at the forefront of revolutionizing data management with our next-generation data warehouse technology. Our mission is to empower enterprises by extracting and leveraging intelligence from both structured and unstructured data at an unparalleled scale. By offering advanced solutions in multi-modal data standardization, classification, inferencing, searching, and aggregation, Roe AI is dedicated to enhancing data intelligence across industries. Schedule a consultation with us and explore how Roe AI can elevate your enterprise's data capabilities to new heights.
We are backed by YCombinator, Gradient Ventures, and Snowflake Executives.
About the role
Skills: Django, Kubernetes, React, Distributed Systems, Machine Learning, Data Warehousing
Key Qualifications
Demonstrated willingness to embrace the dynamic environment of a startup, coupled with a commitment to contributing significantly to our growth.
A deep-seated curiosity and passion for technology, with a fast-paced learning capability. Prior experience is valued but not as crucial as the enthusiasm to learn and adapt.
Strong commitment to customer care, maintaining consistent, responsive communication, and an enjoyment in engaging with customers. Listen, understand, and address customer needs.
Exceptional problem-solving and analytical skills, with a knack for tackling complex challenges.
Proven ability to operate independently as well as part of a team, showcasing strong collaborative skills.
Desirable Skills
Insight into machine learning and data mining techniques.
A minimum of 2 years of experience in product engineering, with a portfolio to show for it.
Proficiency in front-end technologies such as React, Redux, and Next.js.
Expertise in back-end development frameworks like Django and FastAPI.
A solid understanding of data structures, algorithms, and distributed systems principles.
Experience with both SQL and NoSQL database technologies.
Familiarity with cloud services platforms, including AWS, GCP, and Azure.
Knowledge of data processing frameworks like Spark or Hadoop.
Excellent communication and interpersonal abilities.
A Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in Computer Science or a related field.
Join us at Roe AI, where your work will redefine the landscape of data intelligence and pave the way for the next wave of technological innovation. Explore this unique opportunity to become a cornerstone of our growth and success.
Technology
We are looking for a Founding Engineer to join our team in a full-time capacity, with the flexibility for partial remote work. In this pivotal role, you will spearhead the development and scaling of our cutting-edge data warehouse. Collaborating closely with our engineering team, you will play a key role in architecting the platform, crafting and implementing sophisticated algorithms and models, and partnering with cross-functional teams to foster innovation and improve performance.</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>NY, US</location><title>Software Engineer (Infra / Big Data)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>65679</job_reference><company>Paces</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/a92cafe33d123a85f38886d7af1f5aa33cbfd033.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/paces</company_website><company_description>Siting and Due Diligence of Green Projects</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/65679</url><description>About Paces
Paces is software for green infrastructure developers to identify the best places to build and manage their projects.
🛠️ If you’re a builder who wants to actively construct a more climate positive future, join us!
🗺️ We are enabling the climate optimum use for all the world’s land.
🌞 We have paying renewable energy customers and are growing revenue each month, our software supports renewable energy, EV charging, carbon sequestration and data center customers with interconnection, permitting and siting of their projects.
📢 We raised $2.8M in a seed round, led by Resolute Ventures and Y Combinator.
About the role
Skills: Python, PostgreSQL
In the next 30 years, the world will transform every part of the built environment to be climate positive green infrastructure. Knowing what, where, and how to build infrastructure like solar farms is one of the great opportunities of our time.

Paces is software for green infrastructure developers to identify the best places to build and manage their projects. Our software supports renewable energy, EV charging, carbon sequestration and data center customers with interconnection, permitting and siting of their projects. We are venture backed from Resolute Ventures &amp; Y Combinator.
🌳 TL;DR
We are looking for a big data expert who is excited about scaling up systems to join us as we grow.
🏆 What You’ll Achieve
Lead the effort on scale up the existing system to the next level
Take over infra management and keep our system resilient to spiky traffic
Build robust ETL solutions to support large scale ML analytics
Collaborate closely with our CTO and team to directly impact product roadmap
📈 Requirements
Track record of scaling up systems to the next level as traffic grows
Familiar with Python, ORMs, databases, and ETL in general
Comfortable managing data and infra at scale using AWS suite of tools
You are a proactive and fast learner and able to pick up new things quickly
✨ About You
You will thrive in our culture if you:
Have a strong bias towards action and prioritize execution
Share our passion to build something that fights climate change
Easily handle the unstructured environment of fast moving startups
Have the hunger to grow together with Paces as we scale up
🚀 Bonus Points
Previous experience at a high-growth, fast-paced startup
Previous experience working with geospatial data and platforms
Previous experience working with ML modeling
Previous experience scaling up data intensive, AI and analytics heavy solutions
💰 Compensation and Benefits
130K - 200K annual compensation
Competitive equity compensation
401(k) matching
Health, Dental and Vision insurance
Hybrid working in the office 2-4 times per week
Technology
Javascript, Python</description><min_compensation>$130K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Sydney, NSW, AU / San Francisco, CA, US / Remote</location><title>Software Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>65575</job_reference><company>Workflow86</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/c71984e3c90e232ebbf75967edf3df1a6a22f4e9.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/workflow86</company_website><company_description>AI that builds fully-configured automated business processes</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/65575</url><description>About Workflow86
We're capturing the 99% of operational knowledge and expertise held by non-technical teams and turning it into massively scalable software.
Workflow86 is an all-in-one platform for documenting, automating and scaling your team’s internal business processes and workflows.
You use drag and drop components to document and build out your process step by step with modules like forms, business logic, document templates and more. It's no-code, so non-technical team members (bizops, HR, admin, legal, risk and compliance) can set up playbooks and processes on their own.
With Workflow86, teams are able to document and codify their workflows in one central place, massively scale their operational capacity without additional hires, and consolidate fragmented processes into one platform.
About the role
Skills: Java, MongoDB, React, Spring Framework, Amazon Web Services (AWS)
About Us
Workflow86 is revolutionizing the way businesses handle workflow automation. Our AI-powered software enables the autonomous design, construction, modification, and operation of complex business workflows with just natural language inputs. This groundbreaking approach simplifies workflow automation, making it more accessible and efficient for businesses of all sizes.
About the Role
We're in search of a dedicated Senior Software Engineer to strengthen our development team. This role is pivotal for our continued innovation and entails:
Taking full responsibility for significant features or product requirements, often dealing with considerable uncertainty, and breaking these down into actionable design and execution plans.
Efficiently completing and delivering tasks and tickets with a high standard of quality, consistently and with minimal guidance or support.
Rapidly gaining a comprehensive understanding of our codebase and demonstrating expertise in specific areas, becoming a go-to resource for those domains.
Providing guidance and support to junior engineers, helping them execute their tasks effectively.
What We're Looking For
A solid foundation of 5+ years of experience with Java Spring Boot, React JS (Redux/MobX), MongoDB, AWS (EC2, ECS, S3, Cloudfront, Lambda), and microservices architecture.
At least 2 years of experience in contributing to client-side architecture and design.
A commitment to adhering to best practices in coding.
A proven ability to thrive and adapt outside of your comfort zone.
Effective teamwork skills, with experience working closely with junior engineers.
Previous experience with Large Language Models (LLMs) or a strong, proactive interest in LLMs and Generative AI.
Typical Candidate Profile
A Bachelor's or Master's Degree in Software Engineering or Computer Science.
Ideally, at least 5 years of commercial experience in software engineering, demonstrating a track record of technical leadership and innovation.
What We Offer
A competitive salary and equity package.
Flexible working arrangements, accommodating both remote and on-site preferences.
An opportunity to join a venture-backed company at an early stage, significantly impacting the AI workflow automation space.
Location
Preference will be given to candidates located in Australia or the US but we will consider exceptional candidates from any location.
Technology
Java Spring Boot, React JS (Redux/MobX), Mongo DB, AWS (EC2, ECS, S3, Cloudfront, lambda), micro-services. As our focus is on allowing non-technical users to automate complex processes without code, we deal with a lot of interesting engineering problems and decisions as we balance how far users can extend our product and ease of use.
Interview Process
*1st interview (30 to 60 mins): introduction to Workflow86, introduce yourself, general overview of your background, deep dive into past experience (focusing on one major project), technical questions. Attendees: you, Aaron (Founder/CEO) and our senior engineering team *2nd interview (30-60 mins): deep-drive technical discussion and questions (solutions design, architecture, technical decision making). Ask further questions about us and our plans. Attendees: you, Aaron (Founder/CEO) and our senior engineering team *3rd interview (30 mins): offer and final questions from you. Attendees: you, Aaron (Founder/CEO)</description><min_compensation>$80K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$120K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA</location><title>Software Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>48277</job_reference><company>Agave</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/e9bc3a224a6ab03aa39009f5213c25815ae6a7d5.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/agave</company_website><company_description>API &amp; Data Infrastructure for Construction</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/48277</url><description>About Agave
We’re modernizing construction, a $12T global industry run by siloed software built 20-40 years ago (on-prem, no APIs, no mobile access, etc.). We connect these systems by building proprietary APIs and wrapping them in a modern UI for automating work.
Construction Software Companies use our API to integrate their apps with these systems. Construction Companies use our UI to automate work, like keeping financial data in sync between field teams on jobsites and accounting teams in an office. We save both time and money, making them more productive and profitable.
Our founding team has worked together for 10 years, first at Graphiq (acq. by Amazon) then at Amazon. We've raised $3M from YC, Accel, and leaders from Plaid, Procore, Autodesk, PlanGrid, Aconex, and more.
These slides explain our company and market: https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1VIRjj0W8wISEqM2IjPsg2-7carWSw-35GlC4ROTXXkU/edit?usp=sharing.
About the role
tl;dr: we're looking for a world-class engineer who loves simplifying complex systems, unifying fragmented data, and building high-scale backend systems. Learn more about us here (link).
Why Join Us
Opportunity: you have the chance to be an early, pivotal member of a fast-growing YC startup modernizing one of the world's largest industries (construction).
Team: you'll work with a world-class founding team that's experienced, intense, and ambitious. We've worked together for 10 years, first at a startup that Amazon acquired, then at Amazon, and now at Agave. You'll learn a ton while having outsized ownership.
Timing: you're joining at a key inflection point. We're proven (we've grown revenue 4x year over year, have 65+ customers) but also early. This means you have lower risk but also huge upside.
Requirements
Back-end/full-stack engineer, ideally with 1-4 years experience (we're open to exceptional college grads with strong intern/co-op experience).
Familiarity with cloud infrastructure (e.g. AWS).
Self-motivated, high ownership, low ego; desire to work on a fast-paced, intense, fun team. Excited to be our next hire; passion for building a world-class engineering culture.
Pumped to work in-person with us in SF 5 days/week.
No need to have: prior experience with our tech stack or at B2B SaaS/API company
Interesting Technical Challenges
Unification: we’re unifying dozens-to-hundreds of fragmented systems under a single standard that we define. Our unification covers data objects, data models, authentication, account-linking UX, and features like filters and pagination. When designing any new feature, we have to do it in a scalable way. For example, when adding filters, we have to research each system we support (and plan to support) and create a generic, system-agnostic solution.
On-prem: we’re connecting with many types of on-prem systems (SQL-based, DLL-based, API-based), many built 20-40 years ago. We provide tremendous value to customers allowing them to interface with these systems in a secure, fast, reliable way, as if they’re modern, cloud-based products. We need to support real-time communication and webhooks when they don’t exist (e.g., using web-sockets).
Scale &amp; speed: we’re handling millions of API requests per day, and growing daily. For our products that we power with our own API (e.g. Analytics), we need to store and retrieve large amounts of data in an efficient way, building elegant caching layers to reduce latency. We ship code daily and iterate quickly based on actual feedback from paying customers (they share tons!).
Operational excellence: we’re creating a reliable API layer on top of many old systems that don’t have APIs. It’s like building a skyscraper on quicksand, enforced by SLAs. We need to innovate in expanding the depth and breadth of our integrations while simultaneously increasing our development velocity. We need to be very creative in how to continually test our code and integrations, creating scalable testing frameworks that can catch edge cases and bugs across 1k+ endpoints.
Mix of back-end and front-end: we’re building front-end apps that dog-food our own APIs (e.g. Sync, Analytics). This helps us build world-class APIs because we suffer any pain present in our API. We’re building both the lego blocks and the higher-level lego models: we see what kinds of APIs our SaaS customers want, then also look at the kinds of API niceties we want for our own applications (like a caching layer, advanced filtering) and implement a combination of the two.
Variety: without knowing, you might assume adding a new integration is low-ambiguity and routine. But each integration we launch is special, completely different and posing unique challenges. This requires researching that system and its nuances in great depth before building on top of it. It’s part engineering, part archeology.
Tech Stack
Backend: PHP Laravel...why?
We have extensive experience using PHP to scale Alexa's NLP to 100M users.
From YC: https://youtu.be/rP7bpYsfa6Q?t=992
Good HN post: https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=35896954
Frontend: TypeScript, React
Infra: Redis, Postgres, AWS - CDK, EC2
Benefits
Healthcare: we cover 90% of your healthcare costs with several plan options.
401k: we match 100% of your contributions, up to 4% of annual salary.
Relocation: sizable relocation bonus for folks currently located outside of the Bay Area.
Gym: on-site gym with Peloton, squat rack, Tempo, Yoga setup, and more.
Visa: we sponsor Visas (H1B, TN, etc.) for candidates who are a good fit!
Interview Process
At each stage, we decide within 24hrs and update you shortly after.
Intro (15min.) [Virtual]: informal chat for you to learn more about the role. We'll ask for details on past projects. We want to know that you can code, and speak about your work clearly. You’re welcome to ask lots of questions about whether working at Agave makes sense for you.
Experience (30min.) [Virtual] : we'll dive into the details of your most technically complex or challenging projects. Our goal is to ensure you've worked on sufficiently challenging projects to ensure you'll be successful if you join us full-time. We'll also reserve 5-10min to answer any questions you have about Agave.
Coding (1hr): [Virtual] : you'll meet with our CTO. He’ll ask you 1-2 coding questions in your language of preference. We’ll test how you write, test, and debug solutions, and identify tradeoffs.
On-site (1hr x 5 people): [In-Person]: you'll interview with each co-founder and our lead dev. This will be a deeper dive into your technical abilities and overall fit. Each interview is 1hr, 45min for our questions and 15min for yours.</description><min_compensation>$110K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$175K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA</location><title>Technical Product Owner</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>65427</job_reference><company>Agave</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/e9bc3a224a6ab03aa39009f5213c25815ae6a7d5.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/agave</company_website><company_description>API &amp; Data Infrastructure for Construction</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/65427</url><description>About Agave
We’re modernizing construction, a $12T global industry run by siloed software built 20-40 years ago (on-prem, no APIs, no mobile access, etc.). We connect these systems by building proprietary APIs and wrapping them in a modern UI for automating work.
Construction Software Companies use our API to integrate their apps with these systems. Construction Companies use our UI to automate work, like keeping financial data in sync between field teams on jobsites and accounting teams in an office. We save both time and money, making them more productive and profitable.
Our founding team has worked together for 10 years, first at Graphiq (acq. by Amazon) then at Amazon. We've raised $3M from YC, Accel, and leaders from Plaid, Procore, Autodesk, PlanGrid, Aconex, and more.
These slides explain our company and market: https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1VIRjj0W8wISEqM2IjPsg2-7carWSw-35GlC4ROTXXkU/edit?usp=sharing.
About the role
tl;dr: we need a hands-on, technical builder to help us scale our product to hundreds of customers:
You will need to embody opposite traits. On one hand, diving deep into the technical nuances of source systems, building data models, and translating complex business logic to our engineers. On the other, working 1:1 with customers to define their requirements, onboard them, run demo meetings, negotiate deliverables, and more.
You will interface daily between our engineers, customers, and partners (the systems we integrate with). Since we're early stage, we expect you to be a strong generalist.
No need to have familiarity with construction.
Why Join Us
Opportunity: you have the chance to be an early, pivotal member of a fast-growing YC startup modernizing one of the world's largest and most critical industries (construction). You'll work with our world-class engineers to deliver and expand our core product.
Team: you'll work with a formidable founding team that's experienced, intense, and ambitious. We've worked together for 10 years, first at a startup that Amazon acquired, then at Amazon, and now at Agave. You'll learn a ton while having outsized ownership.
Timing: you're joining at a key inflection point. We're proven (we've grown revenue 3x year over year, have 85+ customers) but also early. This means you have lower risk but also huge upside.
Responsibilities
Investigate new source systems to integrate with (data models, business logic, APIs, etc.) and become our go-to subject matter expert on each. It’s part product, part data analysis, and part archeology.
Research and define the structure for new data models we launch (schemas, interrelations with other models, how to standardize each across dozens of systems, etc.).
Write detailed documentation (e.g. runbooks, FAQs) explaining source systems, data models, and API features for internal reference and for our customers to use self-service.
Troubleshoot ad hoc issues with integrations and data models, helping our software engineers debug and resolve errors, and unblock our customers from launches and expansions.
Build and own customer and partner relationships. Work end to end with both software startups and construction companies, from sales/demos to scoping requirements, from onboarding to roll-out.
Translate customer needs to detailed product requirements our software engineers can code against.
Assist sales team in customer demos, showing product functionality, refining customer requirements, and driving toward winning their business.
No need to have: prior experience with Construction or at B2B SaaS/dev tools companies
Requirements
Hands-on: you'll be a full-time builder, not a manager. You must love operating in the messy weeds of nuanced systems, understanding their complexity and simplifying it for our customers. You will focus on product execution and delivery, less on strategy and market research.
Technical: no need to code, but you must have at least 1 year experience working closely with APIs, databases, SQL, Postman, and similar tools. The more, the better.
1+ year experience in software: at least 1 year of full-time experience working for a software company in a data analyst, product, or other technical role. We’re open to exceptional new grads with substantive internships. We want someone hungry and has lots of room to grow, who's ready to roll-up their sleeves and operate in the trenches.
High ownership + conscientiousness: able to manage many threads at once without sacrificing quality.
Meticulous attention to detail: structured thinker who nerds-out on nuances, accounts for edge cases, and tests your work thoroughly before calling it done.
Clear + concise communication: oral and written, must love writing crisp docs for internal + external reference.
Uncanny ability to deliver results: get the job done consistently, doing any task needed to deliver on time.
Comfortable wth customers: able to work with a wide range of customers, spanning software engineers at startups to CFOs at specialty contractors. Can onboard new customers, run demo meetings, negotiate timelines, and communicate clearly over Slack, Zoom, and email.
In-person: pumped to work in-person in SF 5 days per week.
Nice to have:
Experience interfacing with customers (e.g. running user interviews, demoing SaaS products).
Experience building technical products (e.g. APIs, developer tools) alongside software engineers and shipping products on tight timelines.
Knowledge of basic accounting, since many of our use-cases relate to automating financial workflows.
Benefits
Healthcare: we cover 90% of your healthcare costs with several plan options.
401k: we match 100% of your contributions, up to 4% of annual salary.
Relocation: sizable relocation bonus for folks currently located outside of the Bay Area.
Gym: on-site gym with Peloton, squat rack, Tempo, Yoga setup, and more.
Visa: we sponsor Visas (H1B, TN, etc.) for candidates who are a good fit!
Interview Process
At each stage, we decide and update you within 24hrs:
Intro (15min.) [Virtual]: informal chat for you to learn more about the role. We'll ask for details on your past projects and what you're looking for next. We want to know that you meet our basic requirements and can speak about your work clearly. You’re welcome to ask lots of questions about whether working at Agave makes sense for you.
Writing Exercise (30min.) [Virtual]: we provide a short prompt that you reply to in a Google Doc. Our goal is to quickly decide whether you can write clearly, with minimum time investment required from you.
Experience (30min.) [Virtual]: we'll dive into the details of your recent work experience, asking questions to learn about what you've done. Our goal is to ensure you've worked on sufficiently complex projects to confirm you'll be successful if you join us full-time. We'll also reserve 10min to answer any questions you have about Agave.
Case Study (60min.) [Virtual]: we'll provide a product-related case study that you'll prepare asynchronously. You'll submit your response and we'll review it with you on a 60min call.
On-site (60min. x 5 people) [In-Person in SF, we pay for travel]: you'll interview with each co-founder and our lead dev. This will be a deeper dive into your experience, technical fluency, and overall fit. Each interview is 1hr, 45min for our questions and 15min for yours.</description><min_compensation>$110K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$175K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>New York, NY, US</location><title>Product/Frontend Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>65252</job_reference><company>Guac</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/3ffff2e450f7c22939b75b50d62a49acbce05716.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/guac</company_website><company_description>AI-powered demand forecasting for grocery</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/65252</url><description>About Guac
Guac uses machine learning to do demand forecasting for grocers. We predict exactly how much of each product grocers will sell, on each day, at each of their stores.
Our mission is to put an end to the millions of tons of food that goes to waste every single day due to bad inventory planning.
About the role
About Guac
Guac uses machine learning to do demand forecasting for grocers. We predict exactly how much of each product grocers will sell, on each day, at each of their stores.
We’re currently working with large supermarket chains around the world, and our mission is to put an end to the millions of tons of food that goes to waste every single day due to bad inventory planning.
We’re excited to make a huge impact in what is still a highly untapped space, and we’re looking for a product engineer to join us on the journey!
About the role
We are looking for a frontend developer with experience in design to join our team.
This person will be instrumental in designing, prototyping, and developing our web and potentially mobile products. These are the products our customers’ store managers and employees use to interact with our forecasts every day.
Your primary responsibility is having ownership over the development and maintenance of our web/mobile apps using TypeScript, React, and Next.js. Specifically, you’ll be responsible for:
Designing thoughtful UI that communicates our forecasts and recommendations to be easily actionable by store-level employees.
Talk directly to customers to learn about what they need, and then translate that into UX decisions and product features. You’d also be data-driven — implementing analytics and tests to shape your decisions.
Developing and deploying new features that meet the rigorous standards of our enterprise customers.
A small amount of backend related work to support your work on frontend. This might, for example, involve adapting our existing pipelines to transform data for the frontend.
About you
Must have:
You have at least 2 years of post-grad experience in frontend web development. This at least includes TypeScript and ReactJS, Next.js. Bonus for any of: React Native, Tailwind, native mobile (Swift or Kotlin), security/auth protocols.
You have experience in UI/UX design. This doesn’t need to be formal work experience, but some example Figma (or equivalent) work would be desirable, since part of this job will require mocking up product designs from scratch.
Nice to have:
Some full stack awareness and some Python experience. Our backend is built in Python, and there will be times when it will be fastest for you to modify or spin up small endpoints to serve your frontend work.
Experience developing enterprise-grade software, whether that be interfacing with enterprise customers, designing around large enterprise requirements, or coding with security and stability in mind.
Experience with product management tasks, like dealing with customers directly (both for product interviews and feedback reporting), or managing product releases cycles.
Why work with us
Intellectually challenging problems: the everyday problems you’ll be working on require a lot of thinking and creativity. If you derive a lot of fulfillment from solving hard problems, you’ll get that with us. You also won’t be pigeon-holed into one problem, product, or technology.
Have a real-world impact: the grocery industry is enormous (in US, it accounts for ~4% of GDP), and bad demand forecasting is the most expensive problem in the industry — and millions of tons of food are thrown out each year. The better our products are for store employees, the higher the ordering compliance is with our hyper-accurate forecasts, which ultimately means less food waste.
Be surrounded by an awesome team: we’re 100% in person and deeply value having a team that cares about solving interesting problems and has fun working.
Meet interesting customers: while most of the job will be dev-based, we like to spend time with our customers to understand their problems face-to-face. You’ll be able to come along for the ride and see the on-the-ground operations of the grocery industry.
Technology
Ops: GCP (GCS, Cloud Run, Compute Engine mainly), FastAPI, Dask ML: PyTorch, XGB, OpenAI embeddings, SHAP, + more Codebase: Python</description><min_compensation>$130K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA</location><title>Open-Source Product Growth Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>64459</job_reference><company>Eventual</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/f429c16ee024d738c1b758e7c2d0ca5d811f204b.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/eventual</company_website><company_description>Data Warehouse for ML/AI</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/64459</url><description>About Eventual
Eventual is a data platform that helps data scientists and engineers build data applications across ETL, analytics and ML/AI.
Our product is open-source and used at enterprise scale
Our distributed data engine Daft is open-sourced and runs on 800k CPU cores daily. This is more compute than Frontier, the world's largest supercomputer!
Today's data tooling (Spark, Presto, Snowflake) was built for a world of tabular data analytics, but does not generalize to the needs of modern ML/AI such as multimodal data, heterogenous compute and user-defined Python algorithms.
Eventual and Daft bridge that gap, making ML/AI workloads easy to run alongside traditional tabular workloads.
We're growing - come grow with us!
We are well funded by investors such as YCombinator, Caffeinated Capital, Array.vc and top angels in the valley from Databricks, Meta and Lyft.
Our team has deep expertise in high performance computing, big data technologies, cloud infrastructure and machine learning. Our team members have previously worked in top technology companies such as AnyScale, Tesla and Lyft.
We are looking for exceptional individuals with a passion for technology and a strong sense of intellectual curiosity.
If that sounds like you, please reach out even if you don't see a specific role listed that matches your skillsets - we'd love to chat!
About the role
Skills: CSS, Data Analytics
Key Responsibilities
As a Growth Engineer, you will be an early member of the Eventual team with primary responsibilities around making the Daft open-source product successful:
Daft user experience: building out features in Daft for observability, useability and performance
Technical partnerships: guide Daft development by partnering with users and other companies
Technical marketing/DevRel: building out a reproducible process for growing Daft usage and community through technical use-case demos and benchmarks
Our goal is to build the world’s best open-source distributed query engine, and your work will play a key role in realizing that vision.
We are a young startup - so be prepared to wear many hats such as tinkering with infrastructure, talking to customers and participating heavily in the core design process of our product!
What we look for
Our ideal candidate has the following characteristics:
Proficient at technical writing with a passion for building compelling technical demos and tutorials
Obsessive over documentation and user experience
Familiarity with cloud data technologies such as AWS S3, Apache Iceberg and data warehousing
Nice to haves include:
Proficiency with frontend development and design
Experience with data science and data engineering
Most importantly, we are looking for someone who works well in small, focused teams with fast iterations and lots of autonomy. If you are passionate, intellectually curious and excited to build the next generation of distributed data technologies, we want you on the team!
Benefits and Remote Work
We are believers in both having the flexibility of remote work but also the importance of in-person work, especially at the earliest stages of a startup. We have a flexible hybrid approach to in-person work with at least 3 days of in-person work typically from Monday - Wednesday at our office in San Francisco.
We believe in providing employees with best-in-class compensation and benefits including meal allowances, comprehensive health coverage including medical, dental, vision and more.
Technology
Our stack is a mix of Python and Rust. We integrate closely with distributed systems such as Ray and storage engines such as Apache Iceberg and AWS S3.
Examples of domains that we work in include:
Databases: Daft employs modern query planning and optimizations for efficient execution of distributed workloads
Enterprise Big Data: Daft integrates with data lake technologies such as Apache Iceberg and Hive, with record-setting I/O throughputs to these storage formats
Low-Level System Programming: The execution core of Daft is written in Rust for memory-efficient data processing
Interview Process
Introductory Call [15m]
A short phone screen over video call with one of our co-founders for us to get acquainted, understand your aspirations and evaluate if there is a good fit in terms of the type of role you are looking for.
Technical Phone Screen [45m]
A technical phone screen question over video call to understand your technical abilities.
Technical Interview Panel [3.5hr]
Technical interviews with the rest of the Eventual team with questions to further understand your technical strengths, weaknesses and experiences.
Meet the Team
As many chats as necessary to get to know us - come have a coffee with our co-founders and existing team members to understand who we are and our goals, motivations and ambitions.
We look forward to meeting you!</description><min_compensation>$120K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$140K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Founding Engineer (Frontend)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>64136</job_reference><company>Finvest</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/61b78a6a5ac4fd9c4582af51db8cfe1bf6e05bc1.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/finvest</company_website><company_description>Easy way to buy US Treasury Bills</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/64136</url><description>About Finvest

About the role
Skills: Flutter, Android, iOS
We are building the next generation investment platform. Our mission is to enable everyone to grow their money in a stress-free way and we want to become the single place where people manage their money. Our initial game plan is become the #1 company for the entire $130 Trillion fixed income market (eg - Treasury Bills, Certificates of Deposits, Corporate Bonds, Municipal Bonds, High Yield-Cash Account, International Bonds).
Our values
There is a phrase in the sport of cricket called "Zero Not Out" - it indicates when a bater is about to face the first ball. That's how we approach our work - no matter what, we always have a Day One mentality.
We believe hunger is more important than expertise or fancy resumes.
We let the best ideas win, not the loudest voices. That's how A+ teams win.
We strive to provide a world-class service to our customers.
What are we looking for
First and foremost, we are looking for people who are hungry to succeed. Our team is tenacious and we want to work with people who share that mindset.
We are looking for 10x engineers who want to own products, can ship fast, and are not scared to question the status quo.
We don’t intend to have a large team. The sky is the limit for you at Finvest.
What you will do
Design, develop, and maintain Finvest mobile applications, written in Flutter and Dart
Work closely with the founding team to design user journeys that meets the needs of our customers
Help build and scale our team
What you are good at
Experience in building high quality mobile applications
Strong understanding of Flutter or similar mobile developement languages
Familiar with Typescript and Postgres
Designing and shipping user-facing features
Comfortable with version control systems, such as Git</description><min_compensation>$140K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$180K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Oakland, CA</location><title>Robotics Software Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>63967</job_reference><company>Charge Robotics</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/0118080552ba9d1fbdfe132c3eead249237876d9.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/charge-robotics</company_website><company_description>Robots that build solar farms</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63967</url><description>About Charge Robotics
Charge Robotics is a YC-backed startup building robots that build large-scale solar farms. Demand for new solar projects is booming (1/5th of all the solar that exists in the US was installed last year!), but today’s construction companies can’t keep up due to limited labor resources.
We thought this was insane, so we started working on robots to directly address this bottleneck and speed up the world’s transition to renewables.
We’re a small, fast moving company which means constant opportunity for learning and growth. You’ll have a large impact on the direction of our company and our product, which will be reflected in significant equity compensation. And you get to play with 🤖 giant robots 🤖.
If you are excited to work on interesting technical problems with direct climate impact, you’re going to fit right in.
About the role
Skills: Git, Python, Machine Learning
About Charge:
Charge Robotics is a Series A startup building robots that build solar farms.
Demand for new solar projects is booming (1/5th of all the solar that exists in the US was installed last year!), but today’s construction companies can’t keep up due to limited labor resources.
We thought this was insane, so we started working on robots to directly address this bottleneck and speed up the world’s transition to renewables.
Charge is a fast-moving company which means constant opportunities for learning and growth. You’ll have a large impact on the direction of our company and our product, which will be reflected in significant equity compensation. And you get to work with 🤖 giant robots 🤖.
If you are excited to work on interesting technical problems with direct climate impact, you’re going to fit right in at Charge Robotics.
Read more about Charge in recent press:
Fast Company - Solar Building Robots to Solve One of Climate's Biggest Problems
Solar Industry Mag - Charge Completes First Robotics Deployment with Nation's Largest Solar EPC (SOLV Energy)
YouTube - full video of our Gen1 robots building a solar farm
Charge’s funding:
We’re MIT-founded and backed by some of Silicon Valley’s top investors, including Lux, YC (W21), Uphonest, Collab, E14, Outset, and more.
What you’ll be working on:
Architecting, developing, and maintaining high-quality code and documentation for our fleet of fully-automated factories
Controlling industrial automation hardware including 6-axis robot arms, motor controllers, and hydraulic systems.
Maximizing factory throughput by optimizing robot procedures, profiling performance, and adding support for new hardware.
As a Robotics Software Engineer at Charge Robotics, your work will directly deploy gigawatts of clean power generation.
If you’re interested in leveraging your software development skills to have massive climate impact, we want to talk to you.
You:
Are an experienced Python developer
Know how to write software as a member of a team, including writing clean code, documenting it, testing it, and using version control and CI.
Have an advanced understanding of algorithms and data structures
Have excellent written communication skills
Can’t stand tedious work and will find a way to automate it
Are based in or can relocate to the SF bay area
Are excited to see your work deployed onto actual solar farms!
It’d also be nice if you:
Have at least a 4-year degree in CS or similar
Have basic web-dev skills (HTML, CSS, JS)
Know how to instrument and develop highly performant code (networking, high-bandwidth sensor drivers, GPU programming)
Gain satisfaction from personally playing a part in mitigating climate change</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>ML Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>63740</job_reference><company>Instawork</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/1712f8a08b08bb04e192934a1098d1b5144c875b.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/instawork</company_website><company_description>A flexible work app that connects businesses with hourly workers.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63740</url><description>About Instawork
Instawork is the on-demand staffing app for hospitality gigs. We quickly and reliably match businesses with nearby qualified workers. We’re excited to enable our Professionals, a new generation of the emerging, diverse workforce, to be a part of the growing gig economy.
We’ve been fortunate to be funded by some of the greatest investors in Silicon Valley: Benchmark (Bill Gurley), Y Combinator, SV Angel, Crunchfund, Steve Chen (co-founder of YouTube), Mike Vernal (VP of Product at Facebook), among many more.
About the role
Skills: Python, Machine Learning
We're seeking an exceptional Machine Learning Engineer to be a founding member of our cutting-edge team. As a pioneer in this dynamic field, you'll play a pivotal role in shaping the future of work for over 5 million shift workers.
As a founding ML Engineer, you'll be responsible for developing and deploying state-of-the-art machine learning algorithms that power our marketplace. You will collaborate closely with Product, Engineering and Design to personalize our marketplace. Your work will have a direct impact on the lives of millions of workers, helping them find the perfect shift that matches their skills, preferences, and availability.
What You'll Do
*Be part of a team to implement machine learning algorithms to solve complex problems in real-time scheduling and workforce optimization *Gather, clean, and prepare large datasets for machine learning models Implement models using AI frameworks/platforms including LangChain, OpenAI, Bard and more *Build and maintain machine learning pipelines that are robust, scalable, and efficient *Collaborate with cross-functional teams to integrate machine learning solutions into production systems *Monitor and evaluate the performance of machine learning models and make continuous improvements
Technology
Django, React, React Native, AWS, Neo4J
https://engineering.instawork.com/</description><min_compensation>$140K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>QA Automation Engineer - SDET2</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>67368</job_reference><company>Instawork</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/1712f8a08b08bb04e192934a1098d1b5144c875b.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/instawork</company_website><company_description>A flexible work app that connects businesses with hourly workers.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/67368</url><description>About Instawork
Instawork is the on-demand staffing app for hospitality gigs. We quickly and reliably match businesses with nearby qualified workers. We’re excited to enable our Professionals, a new generation of the emerging, diverse workforce, to be a part of the growing gig economy.
We’ve been fortunate to be funded by some of the greatest investors in Silicon Valley: Benchmark (Bill Gurley), Y Combinator, SV Angel, Crunchfund, Steve Chen (co-founder of YouTube), Mike Vernal (VP of Product at Facebook), among many more.
About the role
At Instawork, we’re driven by our vision to create economic opportunity for local businesses and skilled hourly professionals  in communities around the world. With a growing number of hub cities across the world in the U.S., Canada, India, and beyond, we’re looking for top talent to help rapidly scale our high-tech and high-touch labor marketplace. Our accomplished and dedicated team is passionate about our mission and committed to crafting revolutionary products, all with the backing of our world-class investors, including Benchmark, Spark Capital, Craft Ventures, Greylock Capital, Y Combinator, and more!
This role is open for our Bangalore office and requires hybrid work (2 days in-office per week). 
We welcome recent graduates to apply!
Our QA team is growing and needs someone who is laser-focused on raising the software quality bar in a fast-paced environment. This position will give great exposure to the entire lifecycle of cross-platform development and provide a strong foundation for future roles in development / QA. This person will be responsible for building test automation, communicating quality updates across the engineering/product organizations, and solidifying best practices in testing activities across the organization. 
What You'll Do:
Research, Design, and Implement automation framework for tests. Mobile testing (IOS &amp; Android) is the priority and we are willing to train people who have non-Mobile experience
Automate functional, regression, and smoke tests using internal and open source tools 
Create tooling around the entire testing workflow, all the way from test case management, test data creation, automatic bug captures, test progress measurement etc. 
Define test specifications for functional, integration and performance testing
Manage and configure build servers used for running automation 
Work in collaboration with development team in continuous build &amp; deployment process
Report test coverage and participate in troubleshooting 
Manual testing and coverage for new features that have not yet been automated; Perform Black Box and White Box testing 
Create and maintain test plans as our product grows in functionality
Who You Are:
2-3+ years experience with UI Automation testing tools. Bonus for Mobile (iOS/Android) experience using Appium and Selenium
BS or MS in Computer Science or related field
Programming experience in Python + Javascript or similar language
Thorough knowledge of automation testing tools and release processes 
Knowledge of Relational Database such as MySQL is preferred
Self-motivated, especially in learning new software tools and best practices in software quality assurance
Startup mentality: self-starter, proactive, flexible
Good communication and interpersonal skills
You straddle a fine line between QA, software and DevOps engineering
A variety of factors are considered when determining someone’s compensation including a candidate’s professional background, experience, and location. Final offer amounts may vary from the amounts listed above.
Why Explore a career at Instawork
Everyone at Instawork works across the stack. You'll have the opportunity to work backend systems work at scale, build frontend user experiences, and work with Product &amp; Business to make the product meaningful.
We work hard and we work fast. We err on the side of being bold and embrace + celebrate failure, because we'd rather make bets on great features at the expense of shipping some bad ones.
  Perks
Free  snacks • Health Insurance • Personal Insurance • Flexible Hours • Maternity/Paternity Leave • Broadband Reimbursement • Home Office Setup Allowance
  Our Values
Bias for Action -- We are a growing team and an evolving product. We want a team of do’ers to drive the company forward, even if it means making decisions with incomplete information or being wrong.
Act Like an Owner -- Treat this company as though it is your own. Execute on the fundamentals, and act creatively to drive growth. Your ability to drive impact in any part of our company is only limited by your courage and conviction, not your job title.
Always Be Learning -- We are changing an entire industry. We strive to learn from each other and get better each day, week, and month, so that our team’s learnings can compound and we can all improve, together.
Empathy, Trust, Candor -- Empathy for our business partners and professionals means we put ourselves in their shoes. Empathy for our colleagues means we are always upfront and honest with each other, which comes from trust.
About Instawork
Founded in 2016, Instawork_ is the leading flexible work app for local, hourly professionals. Its digital marketplace connects thousands of businesses and more than five million workers, filling a critical role in local economies. Instawork has been featured on CBS News, the Wall Street Journal, The Washington Post, Associated Press, and more. In 2022, Instawork was ranked among the country’s top 10% of fastest-growing companies by Inc. 5000 and was included in the Forbes Next Billion Dollar Startup list. Instawork was also named the 2022 ACE Award recipient for “Best Innovation” and one of the “Best Business Apps” by Business Insider. Instawork helps businesses in the food &amp; beverage, hospitality, and warehouse/logistics industries fill temporary and permanent job opportunities in more than 25 markets across the U.S. and Canada. _
_For more information visit _www.instawork.com
We value diversity on our team and firmly believe Instawork is stronger when we hire people who make their own unique contributions to our culture. We welcome all applicants and encourage candidates from underrepresented backgrounds to apply. 
_To learn more about our company values, please visit: _https://info.instawork.com/about
Technology
Django, React, React Native, AWS, Neo4J
https://engineering.instawork.com/</description><min_compensation>$140K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Fremont, CA, US / Remote</location><title>Chief Financial Officer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>60996</job_reference><company>Holy Grail</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/925403a7e59a5a2741fd31488376fa35f2b90f4e.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/holy-grail-inc</company_website><company_description>We capture CO2 from the atmosphere and store it above ground</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60996</url><description>About Holy Grail
Holy Grail removes carbon dioxide from the atmosphere to contribute to the long-term sustainability of humans and other species on Earth
About the role
Holy Grail developed a direct air carbon capture technology that removes CO2 from the atmosphere and permanently stores it above the ground. We are looking for proactive candidates ready to take ownership and passionate about creating a scalable solution to removing excess CO2 from the atmosphere.
  Requirements
• 2-5 years of accounting experience or an equivalent combination of education, training, and experience
• Advanced financial modeling skills
• Advanced spreadsheet skills
• Strong analytical and problem-solving skills
• Excellent communication skills
• Thorough knowledge of general ledger accounting and account reconciliation
• Highly detail-oriented
• Degree in Accounting, Finance, or a related field
  Responsibilities
• Lead all financial matters within the company
• Audit financial documents and procedures
• Manage relationship with accounting firm
• Provide accurate quantitative information on our financial position, liquidity, and cash flows of our business
• Ensure compliance with all tax regulations
• Prepare invoices and pay suppliers
  Nice to have
• Experience with accounting software
• Experience applying for federal and non-federal grants
• Experience leading a finance team
  What we offer
You will join a team that is passionate about having an impact on climate change. We care about the optimal way to solve problems and nurture a culture of creativity and collaboration. We care about quick iterations, minimizing assumptions, and we use emojis to label our chemicals. We work on interesting technical problems and provide support and resources to tackle them.
  Impact: Your contribution will directly impact the company's milestones, and you will fully own your projects
No politics: We give you the resources to test all your wildest ideas in hours or days, not months
Ownership: Not only you will own your projects you will also own part of the company
Autonomy: We welcome your independent perspective and embrace thought diversity and creative freedom
Flexibility: We encourage you to set and manage your time to achieve our shared goals, and we offer a less rigid environment and company structure compared to academia and larger companies
Fun: We cultivate an informal environment that is focused on the end goal but celebrate all our wins along the way
  Benefits
• Stock options
• Paid time off
• Paid sick leave
• Health &amp; dental insurance
• 401K
Technology
We capture CO2 from the atmosphere and store it above ground</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$150K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Durham, NC, US</location><title>Computer Vision and Optimization Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>63298</job_reference><company>BotBuilt</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/6c0f70c9a27028dd4b634603cfcc5021fc68ccb3.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/botbuilt</company_website><company_description>We use robots to build houses.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63298</url><description>About BotBuilt
BotBuilt is creating flexible robotic systems to solve the housing crisis. Our cutting-edge software and cost-efficient hardware allow us to improve the world by providing beautiful construction, safer job sites, and sustainable building techniques. The $600 billion residential construction industry is facing a massive labor shortage. Our robotic systems leverage the latest in rapid prototyping, artificial intelligence, and computer vision. By taking on some of the hardest technical challenges on earth, BotBuilt is ready to help solve one of society’s biggest problems.
About the role
Skills: Machine learning, Computer Vision
What does BotBuilt do?
We build robots that build homes.
We collaborate with traditional home builders to enhance their construction process through speed, safety, and precision. Having already delivered framing components for multiple houses, our innovative building method is driven by a versatile team made of experts in robotics, computer vision, optimization, mechanical design, pcb layout, and algorithm design.
What you'll do at BotBuilt
Design, implement, and optimize CV models.
Setup MLOps pipeline for continuous improvement of CV models.
Meet with contractors and understand their needs.
Develop optimizations that apply to important aspects of the construction industry.
Your qualifications
We seek a dedicated and innovative software engineer with 3-5 years of experience to expand our capabilities.
Proficiency in Python is crucial.
Demonstrated skill in Computer Vision, and/or Optimization.
Knowledge of C++ is advantageous.
Experience deploying Computer Vision models is preferred.
Experience with Operations Research is a plus.
Your role will encompass both pure Computer Vision projects, and cross-functional projects that involve integration with hardware teams. You'll own an important part of the technology stack that enables the robots to build the homes of tomorrow.
Company Perks
Competitive compensation and equity options.
Comprehensive health, vision, and dental insurance for you and dependents.
Inclusive 401(k) match.
Generous PTO flexibility.
Daily catered lunches and an array of snacks.
Access to our company gym.
The BotBuilt Team
Our team is a distinguished collective of experts, including alumni engineers from NASA, veterans of the U.S. Special Operations Forces, and doctorates in Robotics and Civil Engineering. Bound by a shared mission, we harness advanced technology to address the critical challenge of housing shortages. Our unique blend of experience and passion positions us at the forefront of innovation in this field, poised to make significant impact.
Where to Apply
Please apply on our Rippling board: https://ats.rippling.com/botbuilt/jobs/87be6bdc-a2ba-4272-8040-e160ecb379da
Technology
We're designing custom hardware and software for building houses with robotic arms. ROS, Python, and/or CAD experience preferred but not required.</description><min_compensation>$90K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$130K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Durham, NC, US</location><title>Software Infrastructure Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>63231</job_reference><company>BotBuilt</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/6c0f70c9a27028dd4b634603cfcc5021fc68ccb3.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/botbuilt</company_website><company_description>We use robots to build houses.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63231</url><description>About BotBuilt
BotBuilt is creating flexible robotic systems to solve the housing crisis. Our cutting-edge software and cost-efficient hardware allow us to improve the world by providing beautiful construction, safer job sites, and sustainable building techniques. The $600 billion residential construction industry is facing a massive labor shortage. Our robotic systems leverage the latest in rapid prototyping, artificial intelligence, and computer vision. By taking on some of the hardest technical challenges on earth, BotBuilt is ready to help solve one of society’s biggest problems.
About the role
Skills: Python, Docker
BotBuilt
We build robots that build homes.
We collaborate with traditional home builders to enhance their construction process through speed, safety, and precision. Having already delivered framing components for multiple houses, our innovative building method is driven by a versatile team proficient in robotics, computer vision, optimization, mechanical design, pcb layout, and algorithm design.
What you'll do at BotBuilt
Design, manage, and optimize our infrastructure for the autonomous framing system.
Design, and deploy data logging and retrieval for heterogeneous robot data.
Facilitate high-level robot developer support and troubleshooting.
Implement and uphold infrastructure quality and security standards.
Your qualifications
We seek a dedicated and innovative infrastructure engineer with 3-5 years of experience to lead in crucial areas.
Proficiency in Python is crucial.
Familiarity with CI tools and best practices.
Knowledge of C++ is advantageous.
Background in system administration or network management is a plus.
Experience with IoT deployment is preferred, particularly experience with Balena.
Your role will encompass both pure infrastructure management and cross-functional projects. Assignments will range from optimizing IoT deployments to providing essential tools for the software and robotics teams.
Company Perks
Competitive compensation and equity options.
Comprehensive health, vision, and dental insurance for you and dependents.
Inclusive 401(k) match.
Generous PTO flexibility.
Daily catered lunches and an array of snacks.
Access to our company gym.
The BotBuilt Team
Our team is a distinguished collective of experts, including alumni engineers from NASA, veterans of the U.S. Special Operations Forces, and doctorates in Robotics and Civil Engineering. Bound by a shared mission, we harness advanced technology to address the critical challenge of housing shortages. Our unique blend of experience and passion positions us at the forefront of innovation in this field, poised to make significant impact.
Please apply for this job on our job board here: https://ats.rippling.com/botbuilt/jobs/682ecaab-80d2-4f06-824d-2e4678cbb312
Technology
We're designing custom hardware and software for building houses with robotic arms. ROS, Python, and/or CAD experience preferred but not required.</description><min_compensation>$90K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$130K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Durham, NC, US</location><title>Firmware Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>63297</job_reference><company>BotBuilt</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/6c0f70c9a27028dd4b634603cfcc5021fc68ccb3.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/botbuilt</company_website><company_description>We use robots to build houses.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63297</url><description>About BotBuilt
BotBuilt is creating flexible robotic systems to solve the housing crisis. Our cutting-edge software and cost-efficient hardware allow us to improve the world by providing beautiful construction, safer job sites, and sustainable building techniques. The $600 billion residential construction industry is facing a massive labor shortage. Our robotic systems leverage the latest in rapid prototyping, artificial intelligence, and computer vision. By taking on some of the hardest technical challenges on earth, BotBuilt is ready to help solve one of society’s biggest problems.
About the role
Skills: C++, Device Drivers, Distributed Systems, Docker
What does BotBuilt do?
We build robots that build homes.
We collaborate with traditional home builders to enhance their construction process through speed, safety, and precision. Having already delivered framing components for multiple houses, our innovative building method is driven by a versatile team with deep experience in robotics, computer vision, optimization, mechanical design, pcb layout, and algorithm design.
What you'll do at BotBuilt
Design, manage, and optimize firmware for novel mechanisms.
Design, and manage the deployment and remote debugging process for firmware.
Work closely with electrical, and hardware teams to design systems.
Your qualifications
We seek a dedicated and innovative firmware engineer with 1-3 years of experience to lead in crucial areas.
Proficiency with C/C++.
Demonstrated skill at sensor integration and embedded control.
A keen eye for hardware in the loop testing.
Experience with STM and PlatformIO are strongly preferred.
Previous experience with Python is advantageous.
Experience with IoT deployment is preferred, particularly experience with Balena.
Your role will encompass both pure firmware and cross-functional projects. Assignments will range from sensor integration, real time communication to control algorithms for motors.
Company Perks
Competitive compensation and equity options.
Comprehensive health, vision, and dental insurance for you and dependents.
Inclusive 401(k) match
Generous PTO flexibility.
Daily catered lunches and an array of snacks.
Access to our company gym.
The BotBuilt Team
Our team is a distinguished collective of experts, including alumni engineers from NASA, veterans of the U.S. Special Operations Forces, and doctorates in Robotics and Civil Engineering. Bound by a shared mission, we harness advanced technology to address the critical challenge of housing shortages. Our unique blend of experience and passion positions us at the forefront of innovation in this field, poised to make significant impact.
Where to Apply
Please apply here on our rippling job board: https://ats.rippling.com/botbuilt/jobs/450208da-3455-4e58-ad38-802c6f7178ae
Technology
We're designing custom hardware and software for building houses with robotic arms. ROS, Python, and/or CAD experience preferred but not required.</description><min_compensation>$90K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$130K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Durham, NC, US</location><title>Mechatronics Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>63514</job_reference><company>BotBuilt</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/6c0f70c9a27028dd4b634603cfcc5021fc68ccb3.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/botbuilt</company_website><company_description>We use robots to build houses.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63514</url><description>About BotBuilt
BotBuilt is creating flexible robotic systems to solve the housing crisis. Our cutting-edge software and cost-efficient hardware allow us to improve the world by providing beautiful construction, safer job sites, and sustainable building techniques. The $600 billion residential construction industry is facing a massive labor shortage. Our robotic systems leverage the latest in rapid prototyping, artificial intelligence, and computer vision. By taking on some of the hardest technical challenges on earth, BotBuilt is ready to help solve one of society’s biggest problems.
About the role
Skills: C++, Device Drivers, Distributed Systems, Docker
What does BotBuilt do?
We build robots that build homes.
We collaborate with traditional home builders to enhance their construction process through speed, safety, and precision. Having already delivered framing components for multiple houses, our innovative building method is driven by a versatile team with deep experience in robotics, computer vision, optimization, mechanical design, pcb layout, and algorithm design.
What you'll do at BotBuilt
Design, manage, and optimize firmware for novel mechanisms.
Design, and manage the deployment and remote debugging process for firmware.
Work closely with electrical, and hardware teams to design systems.
Your qualifications
We seek a dedicated and innovative mechatronics engineer with 1-3 years of experience to lead in crucial areas.
Proficiency with C/C++.
Demonstrated skill at sensor integration and embedded control.
A keen eye for hardware-in-the-loop testing.
Experience with STM and PlatformIO are strongly preferred.
Previous experience with Python is advantageous.
Experience with IoT deployment is preferred, particularly experience with Balena.
Your role will encompass both pure firmware and cross-functional projects. Assignments will range from sensor integration and real-time communication to control algorithms for motors.
Company Perks
Competitive compensation and equity options.
Comprehensive health, vision, and dental insurance for you and your dependents.
Inclusive 401(k) match
Generous PTO flexibility.
Daily catered lunches and an array of snacks.
Access to our company gym.
The BotBuilt Team
Our team is a distinguished collective of experts, including alumni engineers from NASA, veterans of the U.S. Special Operations Forces, and doctorates in Robotics and Civil Engineering. Bound by a shared mission, we harness advanced technology to address the critical challenge of housing shortages. Our unique blend of experience and passion positions us at the forefront of innovation in this field, poised to make significant impact.
Where to Apply
Please apply here on our rippling job board: https://ats.rippling.com/botbuilt/jobs/450208da-3455-4e58-ad38-802c6f7178ae
Technology
We're designing custom hardware and software for building houses with robotic arms. ROS, Python, and/or CAD experience preferred but not required.</description><min_compensation>$90K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$130K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>New York, NY, US / Remote (US)</location><title>Full-Stack Founding Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>63390</job_reference><company>ProSights</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/86bf134602f5d866bd328711b018beed3c5b0c6d.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/prosights</company_website><company_description>AI-Native Operating System for the Modern Investment Firm</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63390</url><description>About ProSights
ProSights is radically transforming manual investor software through LLMs. Our hyper-verticalized models scan internal and external data to automate sourcing, diligence, and portfolio monitoring.
About the role
Skills: HTML, Node.js, TypeScript, React
Job Description
As a Founding Full-Stack Engineer at ProSights (and one of the first employees), you will play a pivotal role in developing our core ProSights product from the ground up. You’ll be building a platform that will completely reimagine the workflows of financial services companies from the ground up and be a driving force in the fintech AI revolution.
This role calls for a hands-on developer with a robust understanding of both front-end and back-end technologies, and a passion for building scalable systems.
You will work closely with the founding team in a fast-paced, agile environment, contributing to all phases of the software development lifecycle—from conception to deployment.
Here is what we are looking for:
Strong Sense of Drive: This role requires someone who can take a concept and run with it with a high level of autonomy. You'll need to make critical technical decisions and be comfortable with high levels of responsibility.
Understanding of Startup Life: We are a scrappy team and work hard. We want someone who understands that startups are hard work, but you will be solving a real problem and have the once-in-a-lifetime chance to be part of a YC company that will reinvent how investment firms do business.
Mindset: You should have a strong orientation towards understanding and solving investor problems. We want to reinvent how investment firms operate and to do so, we will need to spend much time with these investors and understand their workflows.
Learning &amp; Adaptability: In startup-land, priorities and workflows can shift quickly. We value engineers who can pivot and adapt to new challenges while continuing to deliver results and are flexible around changing workflows.
Commitment to Quality: You should strive for excellence in your work, understanding that everything from the user interface to back-end stability contributes to the user experience.
Qualifications
Bachelor’s or master’s degree in computer science, Engineering, or a related field
Experience as a full-stack developer or similar role; experience in fintech or investment management software is a plus
Experience with LLMs, including OpenAI's ChatGPT, GPT-4, and DALL-E, and familiar with incorporating RAG (Retrieval-Augmented Generation) into applications.
Proficient in integrating and customizing LLM APIs for enhanced functionality in user-facing products.
Proficiency in NextJS, React, Python, Databases
Ability to work in a dynamic startup environment and manage multiple projects with tight deadlines
What We Offer
A chance to lead the development of a startup that is at the forefront of revolutionizing the investment industry with AI technology
Working directly with the founders of a YC-backed fintech company
Significant equity in the company as a founding member of the team
A collaborative, inclusive, and dynamic work environment in the heart of NYC
Comprehensive health benefits and a flexible vacation policy
About ProSights
ProSights is an AI-native platform that is reimagining how investment firms do deals. We leverage large language models to integrate internal and external data sources into interactive dashboards that enable investment firms to become better investors. Our platform automates critical functions such as sourcing, diligence, and portfolio monitoring, transforming manual and disorganized workflows into a seamless, data-driven process.
Technology
Full Stack Engineer
Interview Process
Round 1: 30-minute conversation with a ProSights co-founder
Round 2: Take-home project of build a quick vertical chatbot within a week (recommended time of 5-20 hours)
Paid Work Trial: 1-2 week work trial with the co-founding team</description><min_compensation>$120K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$160K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>AI / ML Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>63264</job_reference><company>Sieve</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b247c36fd7cd016d5bb505d32429cd07b9acfcbb.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/sieve</company_website><company_description>The cloud for video &amp; audio AI</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63264</url><description>About Sieve
Sieve is a new kind of specialized cloud built specifically around video / audio understanding and generation use cases. We have a set of production-ready APIs available out of the box, and tooling that makes it easy to combine various models together in your apps — and share them with your team as an intuitive AI playground.
About the role
Sieve’s product comes with a lot of pre-built, production-ready apps available out of the box. You’ll explore ways to combine new models to solve popular use cases, and make them work at high quality bars and quick speeds. It’s a combination of implementing models, optimizing them, and having intuition for the right ways to combine them.
Some good qualities to have include:
An interest in keeping up to date with the models coming out everyday
Experience optimizing models to run faster
No need for a PhD but experience having built cool projects with ML models
Love being in CUDA hell. Just kidding, but experience in dealing with NVIDIA drivers and CUDA.
Check out this page to learn more about the company and what it's like to work with us!
https://sievedata.com/about/jobs
Technology
As an early engineer, you’ll get to:
work on low level containerization, networking, and distributed systems problems impacting thousands of GPU workloads at any given moment
write and deploy code that touches users every single day
work with the latest generative models
make decisions on product experience and design
interact directly with customers in calls, shared Slack channels, etc.
We primarily code in Go, Python, and Rust. Additionally, we heavily utilize Redis, Prometheus, Loki, Grafana, MongoDB, Pulumi, and Clickhouse. Our frontend is build with Next.js.</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Infrastructure / Systems Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>63263</job_reference><company>Sieve</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b247c36fd7cd016d5bb505d32429cd07b9acfcbb.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/sieve</company_website><company_description>The cloud for video &amp; audio AI</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63263</url><description>About Sieve
Sieve is a new kind of specialized cloud built specifically around video / audio understanding and generation use cases. We have a set of production-ready APIs available out of the box, and tooling that makes it easy to combine various models together in your apps — and share them with your team as an intuitive AI playground.
About the role
Sieve’s backend involves complex infrastructure working to deliver a simple, seamless experience for the customer. You will spend your time improving the both the reliability and speed of our system, directly impacting the quality of life for our customers.
We primarily code in Go, Python, and Rust, on top of Kubernetes. Additionally, we heavily utilize Redis, Prometheus, Loki, Grafana, MongoDB, Pulumi, and Clickhouse. Familiarity with these is not required, but certainly encouraged. Some indicators of a good fit for this role include:
Interest in challenging infrastructure problems
Can intuitively prioritize feature development based on product impact
Great communication skills
Prior experience building production or open-source infra projects
Check out this page to learn more about the company and what it's like to work with us!
https://sievedata.com/about/jobs
Technology
As an early engineer, you’ll get to:
work on low level containerization, networking, and distributed systems problems impacting thousands of GPU workloads at any given moment
write and deploy code that touches users every single day
work with the latest generative models
make decisions on product experience and design
interact directly with customers in calls, shared Slack channels, etc.
We primarily code in Go, Python, and Rust. Additionally, we heavily utilize Redis, Prometheus, Loki, Grafana, MongoDB, Pulumi, and Clickhouse. Our frontend is build with Next.js.</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Product Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>63261</job_reference><company>Sieve</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b247c36fd7cd016d5bb505d32429cd07b9acfcbb.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/sieve</company_website><company_description>The cloud for video &amp; audio AI</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63261</url><description>About Sieve
Sieve is a new kind of specialized cloud built specifically around video / audio understanding and generation use cases. We have a set of production-ready APIs available out of the box, and tooling that makes it easy to combine various models together in your apps — and share them with your team as an intuitive AI playground.
About the role
Sieve’s product involves a frontend website + dashboard, a Python client, a CLI, and an API (https://docs.sievedata.com). You’ll spend most of your time building improving these things and probably have a great knack for what a delightful developer experience feels like.
Our current stack for these things involve Next.js, Python, Go, and Kubernetes though you don’t need to be familiar with all of it to start.
Great attention to detail and obsessing over the little things
Prior experience shipping full stack products
Great communication skills
Interest in machine learning
Check out this page to learn more about the company and what it's like to work with us!
https://sievedata.com/about/jobs
Technology
As an early engineer, you’ll get to:
work on low level containerization, networking, and distributed systems problems impacting thousands of GPU workloads at any given moment
write and deploy code that touches users every single day
work with the latest generative models
make decisions on product experience and design
interact directly with customers in calls, shared Slack channels, etc.
We primarily code in Go, Python, and Rust. Additionally, we heavily utilize Redis, Prometheus, Loki, Grafana, MongoDB, Pulumi, and Clickhouse. Our frontend is build with Next.js.</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Austin, TX, US</location><title>Founding Software Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>63053</job_reference><company>Tank Payments</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/4db7a5077a335ed33cdb02645791bdc760dba1ca.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/tank-payments</company_website><company_description>Tank is the neobank that gets truckers paid faster.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/63053</url><description>About Tank Payments
Tank Payments is building a modern financial infrastructure for the trucking industry. We offer payables automation software for logistics businesses that make hundreds of payments to trucking businesses every day. Trucking companies that receive payments through our software run their financial back office with Tank, using a banking and cash management application tailored specifically for the unique needs of the trucking vertical.
We raised a $3.3M Seed round led by Y Combinator, Greylock, and others. We've been growing at an incredibly fast rate and are looking for world-class engineers to join us early as we scale up. Our founding team has worked together for 5+ years at a tech startup and later at Amazon and brings a diverse range of backgrounds and expertise.
Read more about us below:
https://www.tankpayments.com
https://www.ycombinator.com/companies/tank-payments
About the role
tl;dr - Full-stack software engineer role at a seed-stage startup modernizing payments in the logistics industry.
Why Join Us
Opportunity: Join at the earliest stage of fast-growing YC startup modernizing payments in one the largest industries in the US. You’ll take on a critical role in scaling the business and accelerate your career
Timing: Business model with strong traction and revenue growth, but still early. Huge upside potential.
Team: Building a world-class, in-person team that is experienced, ambitious, and tight-knit. We will continue to maintain a high bar for every member who joins us as we scale.
Requirements
Full-stack/front-end software engineer ideally with 1-4 years of experience
Experience building and contributing to highly scalable and reliable systems
Entrepreneurial drive and comfort working in an early-stage startup environment
Excited about being founding member of a startup and building a world-class engineering culture
Not required:
Previous experience with our tech stack or in the trucking industry
Tech Stack
Backend: Python
Frontend: Next.js, React, TypeScript, Tailwind
Infrastructure: AWS (CDK, Lambda, ECS/EC2, DynamoDB, Gateway, etc)
Mobile App: Flutter
Technology
Backend: Python, Go
Frontend: Next.js, React, TypeScript, Tailwind
Infrastructure: AWS (CDK, Lambda, ECS/EC2, DynamoDB, Gateway, etc)
Mobile App: Flutter
Interview Process
At each stage, we will give you an update within 24-48 hours. Here's what you can expect:
Phone Screen (40-60min): [Virtual] A conversation for you to learn more about the role and evaluate whether Tank Payments is a good fit. We will give you an overview of the company and ask about your previous experience. We are looking for candidates who are driven and can speak about their work clearly and with passion.
Technical Screen (40-60min): [Virtual] A coding screen to assess basic technical abilities. We will ask about your previous projects and go through 1-2 simple coding exercises. We are looking to evaluate how you write, test, optimize, and debug solutions.
On-Site Interview (60min x 3 people): [In-Person] A 1 hour interview with each member of the founding team. We will dive deeper into your technical abilities and evaluate your general fit for the role. The last 15 minutes are reserved for answering your questions. This is a chance for you to get to know us better, understand what it's like to work with us, and explore how you could contribute to our mission.
We look forward to getting to know you!</description><min_compensation>$110K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$150K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US / Bengaluru, KA, IN</location><title>Founding Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>62769</job_reference><company>Giga ML</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/5dbd878c7f71c963b446c01d1e48bb5e43e87485.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/giga-ml</company_website><company_description>AI customer service agent for B2C Companies</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/62769</url><description>About Giga ML
Giga ML is an applied AI lab focused on building end-to-end customer care agents, co-founded by Varun Vummadi and Esha Manideep. Varun left the Stanford PhD program in AI (2023) and Esha was ranked third at IIT KGP in 2023 to work on Giga ML. We raised $3.7 million in seed funding, led by Nexus, and are part of Y Combinator's S23 Batch. Garry Tan, CEO of YC, personally invested in us.
About the role
Skills: Django, Python, React
Job Description: Full Stack Engineer at Giga ML
Exceptional Achievements: We are looking for candidates who are in the top 0.1% of their field, with outstanding achievements such as GitHub projects with 3k-5k stars, Olympiad medals, or other exceptional accomplishments in the software field.
Note: This role requires a willingness to relocate to our San Francisco or Bengaluru office. Compensation will be adjusted accordingly.
About Giga ML:
Giga ML is an applied AI lab focused on building end-to-end customer care agents, co-founded by Varun Vummadi and Esha Manideep. Varun left the Stanford PhD program in AI (2023) and Esha was ranked third at IIT KGP in 2023 to work on Giga ML. We raised $3.7 million in seed funding, led by Nexus, and are part of Y Combinator's S23 Batch. Garry Tan, CEO of YC, personally invested in us.
Key Qualifications:
- Experience: Minimum of 1+ years in full-stack development.
- Back-end Skills: Strong background in Python and Django. Familiarity with FastAPI is a plus.
- Front-end Skills: Proficiency in React and Material UI.
- Scalability: Hands-on experience with Kubernetes to ensure web applications scale efficiently.
- Cloud Platforms: Knowledge of AWS, GCP, and Azure.
Core Responsibilities:
- Building MVPs: Rapidly build, test, and iterate on multiple MVPs to validate product ideas and achieve product-market fit.
- Technical Leadership: Provide technical direction and make critical decisions on technology choices and architecture.
- Cross-functional Collaboration: Work closely with co-founders and other team members to translate business vision into actionable project plans.
- Agile Development: Lead a fast-paced, iterative development process, adapting quickly to feedback and emerging business needs.
- Continuous Learning and Improvement: Stay updated with emerging technologies, and continuously improve our systems to ensure Giga ML stays at the forefront of technological advancement.
What You'll Gain:
- Impact: Have a significant impact by contributing to cutting-edge ML projects that are reshaping industries.
- Growth: Evolve in a fast-paced, forward-thinking environment alongside other innovative minds.
- Recognition: Gain recognition as a core member of a high-profile project backed by Y Combinator.
- Innovation: Lead in a culture of continuous innovation, working with advanced tools and technologies.
- Autonomy: Enjoy a high degree of autonomy and ownership over the technical direction of Giga ML.
Join us in propelling the capabilities of LLMs to new heights and making them more accessible and secure for specialized domains. Learn more about Giga ML at gigaml.com.
If you are an exceptional candidate with a proven track record of outstanding achievements in the software field, we would love to hear from you. Apply now and join our mission to revolutionize customer care with AI-powered agents.
Technology
Backend: Django Front end: React Cloud: GCP We fine-tune Open-source LLMs with our own scripts</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Chicago, IL, US / Remote</location><title>Carrier Sales Manager</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>62394</job_reference><company>Zerobroker</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/50ea6dff87858daec561d9cdd85d12bfca2e3ec2.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/zerobroker</company_website><company_description>Broker-free shipping platform for businesses.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/62394</url><description>About Zerobroker
Everything you buy was shipped. And you overpay for it because freight brokers are always involved in every freight shipping and charge enormously high commissions. At Zerobroker, we transform the $800 billion trucking industry and make freight shipping broker-free.
About the role
Everything you buy today was shipped. Freight brokers charge 20-30% commission on every shipment. Zerobroker is transforming the $800 billion trucking industry and making freight shipping broker-free.
Zerobroker is an all-in-one operating system for businesses to manage their end-to-end logistics. With one click, businesses ship, finance and pay. It is as simple as buying items on Amazon today.
Our team is ever expanding, and we are looking to develop the next leaders in the logistics space. We offer the opportunity to learn and grow within this industry. The carrier sales representative is responsible for curating and developing strategic business partnerships with outside service providers and owner-operators. This position requires a unique personality and skill set. The possibilities for growth are endless and completely determined by your own efforts and work ethic.
Come join us!
Role Description
This is a full-time remote role for a Carrier Sales Manager. The Carrier Sales Manager will be responsible for managing carrier accounts, developing and maintaining customer relationships, and leading a team of sales representatives. Additional responsibilities include negotiating rates, collaborating with other departments, and achieving sales targets.
Qualifications
Communication and Sales skills
Account Management and Sales Management experience
Freight knowledge and experience in the transportation industry
Excellent negotiation and relationship management skills
Proven track record of achieving sales targets
Ability to lead and motivate a sales team towards common goals
Bachelor's degree in Business Administration, Sales, Marketing, or related field
Experience with transportation management software is a plus
Strong analytical and problem-solving skills
Requirements
College or University degree.
Previous experience in Brokerage/ dispatch/ sales is an asset.
Effective communication skills and ability to work in a fast-paced environment.
Must have good understanding of North American geography.
Strong command over MS Office with an ability to learn new software easily.
Benefits
Competitive Salary and Equity
Career Growth
Technology
The problem we are solving is extremely hard! No one ever solves it before. Zerobroker is the first company in the world that challenges the status quo of the old freight transportation industry and makes it broker-free.
We do it by providing real-time upfront pricing, automating payments, insurances, capacity vetting, matching, and everything else that companies need to move their loads securely and without paying brokerage commissions.
We also empower small and mid-sized trucking companies to act as full-scale logistics companies without hiring a single employee.
When we succeed 7.6 billion people in the world will buy products cheaper!</description><min_compensation>$60K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$120K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA</location><title>Research Scientist or Research Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>48397</job_reference><company>Exa</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/52045f1870e5f9705f78339ab4b3f96126403b66.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/exa</company_website><company_description>Web search rebuilt for LLMs</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/48397</url><description>About Exa

About the role
Search is our interface to information. A search engine with new capabilities -- creativity, memory, analogy -- will change what we know and how we think.
We're looking for research scientists and research engineers to join our team. We have a lot of compute per capita and have a good shot at defining a future technology. If that sounds up your alley, here's what we're looking for:
You have graduate level ML experience (or are an exceptionally strong undergrad)
You have an eye for fundamental, novel architectures that can scale
You're comfortable implementing your own ideas and creating large-scale datasets
(Research engineer applicants only) You have a good understanding of performance optimization and distributed computing
Still apply even if you think you don't fit all the criteria—exceptionally good researchers often don't follow conventional paths.</description><min_compensation>$120K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$250K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA</location><title>Generalist Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>61829</job_reference><company>Exa</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/52045f1870e5f9705f78339ab4b3f96126403b66.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/exa</company_website><company_description>Web search rebuilt for LLMs</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/61829</url><description>About Exa

About the role
Search is our interface to information. A search engine with new capabilities -- creativity, memory, analogy -- will change what we know and how we think.
We're looking for a generalist engineer to join our team. Here's what we're looking for:
You're comfortable thinking up your own creative solutions and evaluating the speed/compute tradeoffs from the user's perspective
You're comfortable wearing many hats (sales, marketing, backend, frontend, etc)
You have a good understanding of software fundamentals like data structures, performance optimization, etc.
You care about improving the way people find information
You'd be excited if you were given a project like "recreate google-level search over a billion pages in 1 month"
Example Projects:
Recreate google-level search over a billion pages in 1 month
Revamp our document parser to work well with any website
Make our web crawler 3x faster
Come up with clever ways to combine ChatGPT with Metaphor search</description><min_compensation>$120K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$250K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA</location><title>Design Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>61830</job_reference><company>Exa</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/52045f1870e5f9705f78339ab4b3f96126403b66.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/exa</company_website><company_description>Web search rebuilt for LLMs</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/61830</url><description>About Exa

About the role
Search is our interface to information. A search engine with new capabilities -- creativity, memory, analogy -- will change what we know and how we think.
We're looking for a design engineer to join our team. Here's what we're looking for:
You're comfortable thinking up your unique, creative designs and rapidly prototyping them
You're able to convert designs to working react apps quickly
You're comfortable wearing many hats (sales, marketing, frontend, etc)
You care about improving the way people find information
Example Projects:
Completely update Metaphor's design materials from first principles
Revamp our frontend
Create internal tooling for monitoring all aspects of Metaphor's internal systems</description><min_compensation>$120K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$250K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Business Operations (Generalist)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>61817</job_reference><company>Pier</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/eb10300785960d3b48dfff648ae5ee0f8ba40cfc.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/pier</company_website><company_description>Stripe for Credit - End-to-end credit infra via API</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/61817</url><description>About Pier
Pier is building "Stripe for Credit" — our API is the fastest and simplest way for companies to compliantly launch &amp; manage loan, line of credit and other credit programs. Using Pier, companies can quickly understand the federal &amp; state-by-state compliance requirements and trust Pier to handle the end-to-end complexities of the credit infrastructure. Popular use cases include credit builder, BNPL and merchant advance for consumer and business borrowers.
About the role
About Us
At Pier, our mission is to improve credit access for Americans by enabling the next generation of credit providers. We're building "Stripe for Credit" -- Our API is the fastest and simplest way for companies to launch &amp; manage loan, line of credit and other credit programs, in compliance with applicable state and federal laws.
We recently raised an oversubscribed round and have been adding 6-figure ARRs every single month. 🚀🚀🚀
As the 1st Business Operations Generalist at Pier, you will play a critical role in establishing the operational foundation of our company, ensuring efficient and customer-centric operations while maintaining compliance. You will work directly with our co-founders and drive strategic projects and initiatives for the company.
Your Primary Responsibilities Will Be:
Assist in day-to-day credit and fintech operations related to our B2B SaaS API product, ensuring seamless integration and functionality for our customers.
Develop and optimize operational processes tailored to our product, ensuring efficiency, accuracy, and adherence to regulatory requirements in the credit and fintech space.
Collaborate closely with cross-functional teams to gather and analyze data, providing insights to support decision-making and process improvements.
Assist in managing relationships with business customers and vendors, ensuring effective collaboration and service delivery.
Support customer interactions and inquiries, providing excellent service and escalating issues as needed.
Conduct data analysis and reporting to monitor key operational metrics, identify trends and provide insights to support decision making and product enhancements
Work closely with the compliance and engineering teams to prioritize and implement customer-driven improvements and new features.
Participate in strategic planning initiatives, working closely with the founder to set goals, develop operational strategies, and execute plans within the credit and fintech space
Ensure compliance with credit and lending regulations, including but not limited to consumer lending, business lending, fair lending practices, credit reporting, privacy laws and other industry-specific requirements.
Oversee projects related to system integrations, API enhancements, and new product integrations with customers and end-users
Foster a collaborative and cohesive work environment, effectively communicating and collaborating with cross-functional teams, including sales, marketing, and customer success.
Demonstrate a start-up mindset, being adaptable, resourceful, and proactive in problem-solving within the credit and fintech space.
Qualifications and Experience:
Bachelor's degree in Business, Finance, Computer Science, or a related field.
2-3 years of relevant work experiences, preferably in a early-stage fintech startup, business operations or management consulting role
Strong analytical skills, with the ability to gather, analyze, and interpret data effectively.
Proficiency in using tools such as Excel, data visualization software, SQL or CRM systems for data analysis and reporting
Excellent organizational and time management skills, with a keen attention to detail.
Strong interpersonal and collaboration skills, with the ability to effectively communicate and work with internal teams and external business customers.
Experience working with business customers, providing support, managing relationships, and gathering feedback for product improvements.
A proactive mindset, with the ability to take ownership of tasks and seek opportunities for process improvement.
Adaptability, flexibility and willingness to learn and take on new challenges in a fast-paced startup environment.
Strong understanding of credit and fintech operations, particularly related to APIs and Saas products is a plus
Our Cultures and Values:
Customer Obsession: Obsessed with our customers’ and their end-users’ pain points. Everyone is customer service and customer support. We believe that amazing products stem from deep-rooted understanding of customer pains and building solutions to address them.
High velocity: thrive in high-velocity environments where you learn fast, operate light-speed and execute with a very high bar &amp; with bias towards actions. Be hungry, curious and continue to push the limits. It’s less about where you’re at, more about where you can be &amp; how fast you can get there!
Empathy factor: Empathizing with those around you, whether it’d be customers, partners, teammates or others. Have genuine interests in the lives of others and how what we do can affect everyone around us.
Entrepreneurial mindset: founder-mentality, crave ownership and high accountability. Embrace chaos and be comfortable with uncertainty and ambiguity.
Transparency: no BS, no politics. We’re extremely flat, tight-knit. Always embrace clarity and transparency.</description><min_compensation>$90K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$120K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Champaign, IL</location><title>ECE / Robotics Engineer (Full-Time) – Yummy Future</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>60742</job_reference><company>Yummy Future</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b16e65239377a055987a5fda8f301c3a3cd7876f.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/yummy-future</company_website><company_description>We build robotic coffee shops.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60742</url><description>About Yummy Future
We build robotic coffeeshops
About the role
Skills: C, C++, Python, Linux
Overview
Yummy Future is a food &amp; beverage robotics startup(Yummy-future.com). We design, build and operate robotic coffee shops. We are looking for highly energetic and innovative engineers to build top-notch, effective robotics solutions that are going to bring a huge impact on our daily life. This is a perfect company to acquire hands-on robotics experience and be part of a fast-evolving robotics industry.
Location
United States – Illinois – Champaign
Role type
Full-Time
Responsibilities
Design, develop, and maintain software and robotics systems using Python and C++
Collaborate with cross-functional teams to ensure that software and robotics systems meet requirements
Troubleshoot and debug software and robotics systems to ensure their smooth operation
Develop and execute software and robotics tests to ensure their functionality and reliability
Optimize software and robotics systems for performance, scalability, and maintainability
Stay up-to-date with emerging trends and technologies in the software and robotics fields
Qualifications
Bachelor's or master's degree in Computer Science, Mechanical Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Robotics engineering, or a related field
Proficiency in Python and C++
Experience in software and robotics development
Experience in Linux and embedded systems like Arduino, Raspberry Pi, ESP32, STM32, etc.
Experience in solving planning problems with operating systems:
Simple data structures: queues, heaps, stacks, lists
Synchronization: primitives, memory semantics, mutual exclusion, semaphores, scheduling, and race conditions
Exceptions and signals: exceptions due to instructions, memory accesses, and floating-point operations; signal semantics and delivery
Networking programming: socket abstractions, basics of low-level network protocols, relationship to kernel I/O abstractions
Ability to work in a fast-paced, project-oriented, team environment
Strong analytical and problem-solving skills
Excellent communication and teamwork skills
Relocation
Relocation to Champaign, Illinois is needed
Visa Sponsorship
We sponsor CPT, OPT, and H1B
Application Process
To apply for this position, please fill out our application form here: https://airtable.com/shrnmK9muszNdRD07
Technology
Robotics, Machine Learning,IoT</description><min_compensation>$1</min_compensation><max_compensation>$1</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Hourly</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Champaign, IL</location><title>ECE / Robotics Engineer (Full-Time) – Yummy Future</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>60931</job_reference><company>Yummy Future</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b16e65239377a055987a5fda8f301c3a3cd7876f.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/yummy-future</company_website><company_description>We build robotic coffee shops.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60931</url><description>About Yummy Future
We build robotic coffeeshops
About the role
Skills: C, C++, Python, Linux
Overview
Yummy Future is a food &amp; beverage robotics startup(Yummy-future.com). We design, build and operate robotic coffee shops. We are looking for highly energetic and innovative engineers to build top-notch, effective robotics solutions that are going to bring a huge impact on our daily life. This is a perfect company to acquire hands-on robotics experience and be part of a fast-evolving robotics industry.
Location
United States – Illinois – Champaign
Role type
Full-Time
Responsibilities
Design, develop, and maintain software and robotics systems using Python and C++
Collaborate with cross-functional teams to ensure that software and robotics systems meet requirements
Troubleshoot and debug software and robotics systems to ensure their smooth operation
Develop and execute software and robotics tests to ensure their functionality and reliability
Optimize software and robotics systems for performance, scalability, and maintainability
Stay up-to-date with emerging trends and technologies in the software and robotics fields
Qualifications
Bachelor's or master's degree in Computer Science, Mechanical Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Robotics engineering, or a related field
Proficiency in Python and C++
Experience in software and robotics development
Experience in Linux and embedded systems like Arduino, Raspberry Pi, ESP32, STM32, etc.
Experience in solving planning problems with operating systems:
Simple data structures: queues, heaps, stacks, lists
Synchronization: primitives, memory semantics, mutual exclusion, semaphores, scheduling, and race conditions
Exceptions and signals: exceptions due to instructions, memory accesses, and floating-point operations; signal semantics and delivery
Networking programming: socket abstractions, basics of low-level network protocols, relationship to kernel I/O abstractions
Ability to work in a fast-paced, project-oriented, team environment
Strong analytical and problem-solving skills
Excellent communication and teamwork skills
Relocation
Relocation to Champaign, Illinois is needed
Visa Sponsorship
We sponsor CPT, OPT, and H1B
Application Process
To apply for this position, please fill out our application form here: https://airtable.com/shrnmK9muszNdRD07
Technology
Robotics, Machine Learning,IoT</description><min_compensation>$1</min_compensation><max_compensation>$1</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Hourly</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Champaign, IL</location><title>Mechanical / Robotics Engineer (Full-Time) – Yummy Future</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>60743</job_reference><company>Yummy Future</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b16e65239377a055987a5fda8f301c3a3cd7876f.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/yummy-future</company_website><company_description>We build robotic coffee shops.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60743</url><description>About Yummy Future
We build robotic coffeeshops
About the role
Overview
Yummy Future is a food &amp; beverage robotics startup(Yummy-future.com). We design, build and operate robotic coffee shops. We are looking for highly energetic and innovative engineers to build top-notch, effective robotics solutions that are going to bring a huge impact on our daily life. This is a perfect company to acquire hands-on robotics experience and be part of a fast-evolving robotics industry.
Location
United States – Illinois – Champaign
Role
Mechanical / Robotics Engineer
Role type
Full-Time
Responsibilities
Design parts for 3D printing, optimizing orientation, and slicing parameters
Define requirements for tools, equipment, materials, parts, and processes used in the engineering design, manufacture, and/or maintenance of Yummy Future robotic products
Collaborate with project teams to coordinate database development and determine project scope and limitations
Troubleshoot mechanical problems and develop innovative solutions
Qualifications
Bachelor's or master's degree in Mechanical Engineering, Automotive Engineering, Robotics Engineering, or a related field
Experience in 3D design modeling using software such as Fusion 360, SolidWorks, or CAD
Knowledge of real-world robotic systems and the ability to solve planning problems
Ability to work in a fast-paced, project-oriented, team environment
Proficiency in CAM using CNC Router
Familiarity with PCB Design
Understanding of 3D graphics and geometry
Demonstrated ability and knowledge of sheet metal work
Nice to Have
Proficiency in Python, C++, C# programming in a production environment
Strong computer skills and excellent organizational abilities
Experience soldering small components on PCB
Visa Sponsorship
We sponsor CPT, OPT, and H1B
Application Process
To apply for this position, please fill out our application portal at https://airtable.com/shrnmK9muszNdRD07
Technology
Robotics, Machine Learning,IoT</description><min_compensation>$1</min_compensation><max_compensation>$1</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Hourly</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Champaign, IL</location><title>Mechanical / Robotics Engineer (Full-Time) – Yummy Future</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>60930</job_reference><company>Yummy Future</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b16e65239377a055987a5fda8f301c3a3cd7876f.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/yummy-future</company_website><company_description>We build robotic coffee shops.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60930</url><description>About Yummy Future
We build robotic coffeeshops
About the role
Overview
Yummy Future is a food &amp; beverage robotics startup(Yummy-future.com). We design, build and operate robotic coffee shops. We are looking for highly energetic and innovative engineers to build top-notch, effective robotics solutions that are going to bring a huge impact on our daily life. This is a perfect company to acquire hands-on robotics experience and be part of a fast-evolving robotics industry.
Location
United States – Illinois – Champaign
Role
Mechanical / Robotics Engineer
Role type
Full-Time
Responsibilities
Design parts for 3D printing, optimizing orientation, and slicing parameters
Define requirements for tools, equipment, materials, parts, and processes used in the engineering design, manufacture, and/or maintenance of Yummy Future robotic products
Collaborate with project teams to coordinate database development and determine project scope and limitations
Troubleshoot mechanical problems and develop innovative solutions
Qualifications
Bachelor's or master's degree in Mechanical Engineering, Automotive Engineering, Robotics Engineering, or a related field
Experience in 3D design modeling using software such as Fusion 360, SolidWorks, or CAD
Knowledge of real-world robotic systems and the ability to solve planning problems
Ability to work in a fast-paced, project-oriented, team environment
Proficiency in CAM using CNC Router
Familiarity with PCB Design
Understanding of 3D graphics and geometry
Demonstrated ability and knowledge of sheet metal work
Nice to Have
Proficiency in Python, C++, C# programming in a production environment
Strong computer skills and excellent organizational abilities
Experience soldering small components on PCB
Visa Sponsorship
We sponsor CPT, OPT, and H1B
Application Process
To apply for this position, please fill out our application portal at https://airtable.com/shrnmK9muszNdRD07
Technology
Robotics, Machine Learning,IoT</description><min_compensation>$1</min_compensation><max_compensation>$1</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Hourly</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Chiyoda City, Tokyo, JP / San Francisco, CA, US / Remote</location><title>AI Researcher (Anime)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>60810</job_reference><company>Spellbrush</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/fb441dcc9519c0cc22e2464b6b1c3b1ca462403b.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/spellbrush</company_website><company_description>Magic Anime Pictures</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60810</url><description>About Spellbrush
Here at Spellbrush, we're passionate about making a good anime game. We also happen to be the world's leading generative AI studio — we're the team behind niji・journey. We are currently investigating how AI can be used to help human artists perform masterpieces in the most complex medium of our times: videogames. Our games are characterized by a no-compromise approach to well-balanced gameplay married to a truthful love of visual arts. If you love turn-based tactics games, please consider applying!
About the role
Skills: Machine learning, Python, Torch/PyTorch
The Anime Researcher Role:
We're looking for an experienced AI Researcher to join our team and help us push the boundaries of AI and anime. You'll design and develop large-scale diffusion models with a primary focus on images, and secondary focus on other modalities like 3d, text, video and audio.
You may be a good fit if:
You love anime and the anime aesthetic.
This one of the only labs in the world where you can combine your expertise on anime and deep learning to work on state-of-the-art anime models.
You understand diffusion, or can get up to speed quickly.
We're looking for experienced researchers who aren't afraid of jumping headfirst into experimenting and designing massive models.
You're proficient in Pytorch (and maybe JAX too)
We have a very large Pytorch codebase, and an equally large JAX codebase for large-scale TPU training.
You enjoy a tight loop between research and production.
We pride ourselves on getting models from the lab into production quickly. Our research team works closely with our internal studio to both develop game-ready models, and deploy regular quality updates to niji・journey.
You're comfortable working on small, fast-paced teams
We currently have a team of four on AI. You'll be working closely alongside some of the best AI researchers in the world, on the literal best image model in the world.
We also believe in the unmatched speed of in-person teams, and prefer on-site collaboration in either our primary research office in Tokyo (downtown Akihabara), or San Francisco. Visa sponsorships are available.
IMPORTANT:
Given the anime focus of this position, it is required to answer the question "Who is your favorite waifu or husbando" when submitting your application through Bookface. Applications that fail to include a response to this question in the application message will NOT be reviewed.
Technology
At Spellbrush, we're pushing the boundaries of generative networks through our state-of-the-art diffusion text-to-image research. There's no shorted of interesting tech challenges here:
Research: We make heavy use of Pytorch and JAX, and train large-scale models using both TPUs and GPUs. Our researchers spend each day developing and testing novel state-of-the-art diffusion models.
Engineering: We make use of a lot of Elixir for real-time backend systems, Python for machine learning, and lots of simulation and game logic code written in C# via Unity. We also have tons of internal tools and apps written in Typescript, React, and RN.
Infrastructure: We've done everything from building our own in-house GPU supercomputer, to scaling up massive inference clusters in our own datacenters, typically orchestrating via some unholy combination of SLURM, kubernetes, and NATS.</description><min_compensation>$75K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US / Remote</location><title>LLMs and general AI Researcher/Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>60361</job_reference><company>Rosebud AI</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/0669f9afff20bf775d9b001b89480415cdb33109.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/rosebud-ai</company_website><company_description>Make games at the speed of thought.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60361</url><description>About Rosebud AI
About Us
Rosebud.ai is building the AI Roblox. We use generative AI workflows to accelerate game development and creative. The next few years of AI are going to define the coming few decades of the world. Some wait a lifetime for a moment like this. For those who have an inner fire to make something great, join us. Let’s build.
About Us
For more on vision and team. Check out this 3 min video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JuxMHfzUff0&amp;ab_channel=Lishali . We're the team that built Tokkingheads (2 million IOS downloads, all organic) that allows any portrait/photo/face to be animated in seconds with no skill, and Synth (https://www.synth.run), a simple mobile app that allows users to create images based on Stable Diffusion.
We’re a team of PhD researchers, creatives and engineers backed by Y Combinator with our seed led by Vinod Khosla at Khosla Ventures with participation from Balaji Srinivasan **(Former CTO Coinbase and A16Z GP), Ilya Sutskever (cofounder/chief scientist Open AI),  Kevin Lin (cofounder COO Twitch), Holly Liu Co-founder Kaba,  Kun Gao (cofounder, CEO Crunchyroll), Linda Xie Founder Scalar Capital, Jon Snoddy SVP @ Walt Disney Imagineering, Jeff Dean SVP Google Research, Adam D'Angelo CEO Quora, and Lily Liu. cofounder http://earn.com.
About the role
Skills: Python
Application Process
Fill out this form so we can get in contact with you: https://airtable.com/shrZj3eXVXaUnV1KB
About Us
Rosebud.ai building generative AI workflows to accelerate game development and creative. We want to empower indie devs to build games at the speed of thought.
We're the team that built Tokkingheads (2 million IOS downloads, all organic) that allows any portrait/photo/face to be animated in seconds with no skill.  And Synth (https://www.synth.run), a simple mobile app that allows users to create images based on Stable Diffusion. We’re a team of PhD researchers, creatives and engineers backed by Y Combinator with our seed led by Vinod Khosla at Khosla Ventures with participation from Andrej Karpathy, Balaji Srinivasan **(Former CTO Coinbase and A16Z GP), Ilya Sutskever (cofounder/chief scientist Open AI),  Kevin Lin (cofounder COO Twitch), Holly Liu Co-founder Kaba, Jon Snoddy SVP @ Walt Disney Imagineering, Jeff Dean SVP Google Research and Adam D'Angelo CEO Quora.
Why Join us?
🚀 Join a Rocket Ship!
🚀 Ship products that delight millions of users while having direct product impact on a small team (2 million downloads in over 180+ countries).
🚀 Do cutting edge ML and full stack work
🚀 Remote outside of SF Bay Area, or 4 day in person policy for Bay Area.
🚀 Work with a passionate, low ego, world class team!
Our team is still quite small (&lt;10), so you’ll have massive impact on the trajectory of the business from Day One.
Your Role
Ongoing research in generative assets creation methods in text domain
Combining the full power of large language models with more traditional NLP algorithms
Investigating new methods for creating games
Implementing state-of-the-art generative methods from scratch, as well as modifying them, including LLMs for code generation and editing
Prototyping ml models and pipelines to meet business requirements
Follow generative DL methods trends
You fit well if you have great experience in modern natural language processing dl based methods, if you can take some idea or business task, find good open source or implement simple methods to create prototype, package all of this for demo and always have ideas on how to iteratively improve (better quality, faster for inference, other workflows, …)
Requirements
Experience in generative DL in text domain
Great experience in DL and traditional text processing methods
Experience in LLMs
Great pytorch knowledge
Dev tools - git, docker, clouds
Experience in related domains (images processing, 3d graphics, video processing, gamedev) is a plus
Technology
LLMs for code gen. Generative AI for 2D and 3D asset generation Browser based games.</description><min_compensation>$50K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$180K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Mountain View, CA, US / San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>Full Stack Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>59932</job_reference><company>JustPaid.io</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/d4d3f38c1d243925fc15067d6f5cc3998e355140.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/justpaid-io</company_website><company_description>AI accounts receivable agent</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/59932</url><description>About JustPaid.io

About the role
Skills: Django, Python, React, PostgreSQL
JustPaid.io - your AI financial controller is looking for a full-stack developer. https://www.justpaid.io/careers
Founders will work with you 2-3 times a week in person.
Interview Process
Please apply here: https://www.justpaid.io/career You would be scheduled to do a zoom call with the founders to see if there is a good fit. It would be great if you could complete a quick test - to hack something you are passionate about. It could be anything. Or be prepared to share your GitHub account. We will make a decision quickly without taking too much of your time and looking to hire people in a hybrid environment. The team is in Sunnyvale/Los Altos.</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$100K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Remote / Salt Lake City, UT, US / Remote</location><title>Software Engineer, Strategy</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>59533</job_reference><company>Angle Health</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/d49817ec52cedb0a83c434d820655f46cd43b8ad.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/angle-health</company_website><company_description>Health Insurance for Startups</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/59533</url><description>About Angle Health
At Angle Health, we're tackling the healthcare crisis at the point where our health system starts and stops: health insurance. By building a modern, technology-driven health plan, we are creating a customer-centric experience that gets our members the care they need when they need it. We're on a journey to making people healthier and we're starting with startups. If you want to be part of the future of healthcare, we'd love for you to join us.
About the role
Changing Healthcare For Good
At Angle Health, we believe the healthcare system should be accessible, transparent, and easy to navigate. As a digital-first, data-driven health plan, we are replacing legacy systems with modern infrastructure to deliver our members the care they need when they need it. If you want to build the future of healthcare, we'd love for you to join us.
The Role
As a Deployed Software Engineer on the Strategy team at Angle Health, you will be part of an elite team of problem solvers tackling some of the hardest operational challenges across the business. You will be working closely with Technical Product Managers and other engineers in small teams embedded within functions across the company—from sales to operations to finance and more.
In partnership with operational stakeholders, your job will be to quickly understand business workflows, and design and implement technical, data-driven solutions to achieve the intended business outcomes. That may include architecting backend micro-services, building and maintaining robust data pipelines, standing up health metrics and automated alerts, and developing scalable technical solutions to support Angle Health's day-to-day operations.
Every day will be a new learning experience in this role and may span discussing architecture with fellow engineers, wrangling large-scale data, coding a custom web app or micro-service, or speaking with customers and executives.
This role is ideal for entrepreneurial engineers, applied data scientists, and creative, intellectually curious thinkers that want to solve high-value problems in healthcare.
This position may be based in San Francisco, New York City, Salt Lake City, or Remote.
What We Value
A strong engineering background in computer science, software engineering, data science, mathematics, or similar technical field is required for this role
Proficiency in programming languages (e.g. Python, SQL, Java, TypeScript/JavaScript, or similar) and data engineering frameworks
A highly analytical mindset and an eagerness to build technical solutions to complex business problems
High attention to detail and intellectual curiosity—you're not satisfied with surface-level answers. You want to dive into the data, the "how," and the "why" because "the way it's always been done" is not always the way it should be done
Low ego—the outcome matters more than who gets the credit
Demonstrated ability to collaborate effectively in teams of technical and non-technical individuals
Highly organized with an ability to multitask, problem solve, and balance competing priorities in a rapidly changing environment
Because We Value You:
·      Competitive compensation and stock options
·      100% company paid comprehensive health, vision &amp; dental insurance for you and your dependents
·      Supplemental Life, AD&amp;D and Short Term Disability coverage options
·      Discretionary time off
·      Opportunity for rapid career progression
·      Relocation assistance (if relocation is required)
·      3 months of paid parental leave and flexible return to work policy (after 10 months of employment)
·      Work-from-home stipend for remote employees
·      Company provided lunch for in-office employees
·      401(k) account
·      Other benefits coming soon!
Backed by a team of world class investors, we are a healthcare startup on a mission to make our health system more effective, accessible, and affordable to everyone. From running large hospitals and health plans to serving on federal healthcare advisory boards to solving the world's hardest problems at Palantir, our team has done it all. As part of this core group at Angle Health, you will have the right balance of support and autonomy to grow both personally and professionally and the opportunity to own large parts of the business and scale with the company.
Angle Health is proud to be an Equal Employment Opportunity and Affirmative Action employer. We do not discriminate based upon race, religion, color, national origin, gender (including pregnancy, childbirth, or related medical conditions), sexual orientation, gender identity, gender expression, age, status as a protected veteran, status as an individual with a disability, or other applicable legally protected characteristics. Angle Health is committed to working with and providing reasonable accommodations to applicants with physical and mental disabilities.
Technology
Being a full stack carrier means sitting at the nexus of care, money and data. Our major tech challenges will involve building out first class backend infrastructure that integrates with the various pieces of the healthcare stack (claims clearinghouses, HR/Payroll platforms, providers, wellness companies) and running sophisticated ML models to identify leading indicators of cost and high risk members. We are also developing a first-in-class member &amp; provider experience unlike any option that exists today. Our tech stack comprises mainly of Python, Postgres, AWS, React, React Native, and Swift.</description><min_compensation>$1</min_compensation><max_compensation>$1</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Hourly</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US / New York, NY, US</location><title>Founding Product Manager</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>56985</job_reference><company>Explo</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/780b4e13b382139633e716a4aa5a74afed2cbe10.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/explo</company_website><company_description>Customer-facing analytics, lightning fast</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/56985</url><description>About Explo
Our mission is to empower everyone to responsibly solve problems with data.
After working at companies such as Palantir and McKinsey and working with customers struggling with data problems, we discovered companies need to expose data and analytics to their own customers.
Not only do companies themselves want to analyze and utilize the data they collect, but more and more, their customers want access to that same data. Current embedded analytics tools require immense setup costs and aren't designed specifically for customer-facing analytics. Explo is the easiest way to set up your customer-facing dashboards and share reports and data with your customers.
About the role
Explo is currently hiring for our Founding Product Manager to join our team! This is an opportunity to be the first PM at a Series-A startup and be a pivotal member of the team. You will be responsible for implementing processes and systems that will turn our product organization into a well-oiled machine. This is an opportunity to have a great deal of ownership on a product that is highly impactful for our customers with a huge amount of growth!
What you will do: Establish and manage Explo’s product development process Establish processes across the team for product roadmapping, OKRs, and goal-setting Manage and delivery products that require collaborating across the entire business - from sales to strategy to product Identify market opportunities to expand value to existing customers and launch new product lines within Explo’s suite of offerings What we're looking for: 3+ years experience as a Product Manager in a software company Comfortability with data concepts like SQL, data manipulation, and dashboarding Founder mentality - take ownership of the products that you manage and find ways to help the business thrive Bonus Points for: SaaS experience or data product experience in an early stage start up.
Benefits + Perks
Unlimited PTO Monthly lunch stipend One Medical membership 401k Comprehensive health, vision and dental insurance Competitive salary range from $150k to $200k dependent on years of experience and skill level
About Us Explo makes it easy for companies to build customer-facing dashboards, replacing the need for a in-house analytics team. We’re a passionate, growth minded, group of people who truly enjoy working together! We’re always on the hunt for individuals who are excited about joining a high-growth startup with a collaborative culture, so if this role doesn’t round like the right fit feel to reach out!
Technology
We are building a web app with modern technologies: React/typescript frontend and Django/python backend. We also deeply integrate with data warehouses like BigQuery, RedShift, and Snowflake.
Explo has been a great way to learn about modern data infrastructure and help build on top of the newest tech.</description><min_compensation>$150K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>New York, NY / Remote</location><title>Finance Operations</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>55807</job_reference><company>Kalshi</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/42535d3c0d7bdb4069a3dc31f088f327ee7e59da.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/kalshi</company_website><company_description>1st federally regulated exchange where people can trade on events</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/55807</url><description>About Kalshi
Kalshi is a an exchange where people can trade on the outcome of events. Our vision is to allow people to capitalize on what they know and what they believe in by making predictions on the outcome of things they’re interested in.
About the role
What we're up to:
Kalshi has launched the first regulated financial exchange that allows people to trade on the anticipated outcome of events. We’re now looking for the right people to help us continue to grow and scale.
Our vision is to allow people to capitalize on their opinions and hedge risks that relate to their everyday lives, from "Will New York City close indoor dining?” to "Will 2021 be the hottest year on record?" 
We're on a long journey in uncharted territories and are looking for passionate and outlier members excited to embark on this voyage towards building the future of the financial system.
Role Roadmap:
In the Finance Operations role, you will be a one of the first members of Kalshi's Finance team. An exchange is a highly complex machine with complex cash flows. The Finance team is responsible for managing the finances from the perspective of the company's operations as well as that of the exchange's financial transactions. We're scaling, which means your role will evolve and grow with the company; your initial attack threads include:
Managing the routine cash-flow operations between the exchange and the clearinghouse Monitoring and validating clearing and settlement performed by the clearinghouse for our markets Educating exchange participants on the different tax requirements that apply to their trading activities Working with the executive team to develop financial strategy including budgeting and revenue projections Managing compliance with regulatory requirements Managing regulatory reporting and quarterly financial submissions to the CFTC Running financial accounting and overseeing tax preparation
The rest of what the role looks like is up to you - a big part of our approach is that you get to chart your path as we grow and evolve. There's a lot of green field to conquer, we trust that you'll make a lot of it your own :)
Our Culture:
We are a group of people who work hard and get things done, and we're looking for more people like that! Meritocracy is at our core, and we value people who take ownership and figure (usually hard) things out - we don't care much about anything other than the product of your work. We think of Kalshi as a family bound together by our mission: we believe that this is the best (and most fun!) way to work. Kalshians are, by far, Kalshi's largest asset and we're obsessed with growing and investing in our people.
Technology
Go backend, React frontend, Python for our surveillance systems.</description><min_compensation>$80K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$150K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA</location><title>Founding Platform / Full-Stack / Front-end Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>55727</job_reference><company>Poly</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/2c933e4442d83b03a9d59a60dc94be3f95e9d475.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/poly</company_website><company_description>Intelligent Personal Cloud Storage</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/55727</url><description>About Poly
Poly is the most advanced personal cloud storage platform for your files and media. Our platform is designed to be so good, that it'll replace Finder/File Explorer on your desktop. Find anything with multi-modal, natural language search. Browse with lightning fast caching and loading. Convert file types, open in your favorite apps, and tag/rank your content for instant access.
Built on a foundation of incredible research and engineering, Poly is revolutionizing a technology that people use every day by reimagining the stack top to bottom using advanced proprietary AI.
About the role
Skills: TypeScript, Rust, SQLite, Data Modeling
About Us
Poly is building a better file storage platform for everyone. We're backed by YC, Bloomberg Beta, Felicis, Figma Ventures, AI Grant, and more, and we're looking to grow our founding team of superstar builders and dreamers.
Our file storage platform will "replace Finder and File Explorer" as the de-facto user experience for managing your personal files (we will host them as well). We know, it's an insanely ambitious goal, but we think it's not only possible but necessary to finally do away with these legacy file systems.
Concretely, here's three reasons why people need Poly:
Find anything using natural language and multi-modal queries ("images in the style of X from last week"), so that you never lose track of your stuff again.
Auto-upload/sync content from your GenAI apps via auth or browser plugin, complete with metadata.
Create projects and workspaces where you can pin files, save folders that dynamically update, and mention notes/links for reference. Spend less time managing files and more time getting stuff done.
About You
We are looking for a founding platform developer to join us in building Poly's desktop and web applications. You will need to wear many hats, but the only hat you'll never remove is your attention to detail and dedication towards excellence. You must have significant experience (or significant enthusiasm) in building cross platform full-stack experiences. Specifically, we would pay attention to your expertise in the following:
Core software design and architectural considerations in developing a full-stack application for file management, including reactivity (e.g. React, Vue), persistence, latency, data caching, interaction, and API
Extensive knowledge of client-server communication strategies including HTTP, websockets, binary formats such as protobufs/cbor, etc.
Cross-platform considerations using Electron/Tauri or some other packaging framework that suits our needs
WASM and other optimizations over raw JS that allow us to perform hyper-fast data management
Debugging and test practices that let us catch both unit, integration, and interaction bugs.
Modern web standards across domains, such as WebGPU, WebGL, WebAudio, WebRTC, File Storage/File Access.
Send a friend request on LinkedIn with a short blurb (in the connection request) to me, and I will be 1000+% more likely to see and respond to your interest. My bio is here: http://linkedin.com/in/abhaykagarwal/
Technology
We have built an entirely home-grown AI platform and self-trained models for search and ranking. That includes our own inference stack, training pipeline, and so forth. We don't rely on any 3rd-party APIs or services because we want to control our own destiny and build the absolute best tools possible.
Interview Process
Our entire interview process is extensively documented here. The interview process is going to look roughly like the following:
An introductory call with a founding team member.
You will talk to another team member, who will want to know more about your background, prior projects, and hard/interesting problems that you have worked on. We'll likely be basically grilling you on specifics, and this interview might come off as "insistent", or "demanding". This is only because we are essentially trying to dig in deep enough to where we're satisfied that you are deeply aware of the technical trade-offs of a given system.
We'll have you do a take-home project or exercise (most of you will come here because of that). You'll have essentially unlimited time to work on this, but the longer that you work on it, the higher the standard becomes. On the other hand, working more on this also shows higher passion and conviction. Overall, we are extremely comfortable with both the "ninja that did this in less than an hour" types, but also the more methodical types. So even if you're in a hurry, give it a shot!
We will do a team-wide set of interviews where you will be speaking with everyone on the team. As long as we are small, we will operate on a consensus basis for hires, so we all want to be highly excited to hire you. Please see the "Team Interview" section for more information on how to prepare for this.
If we are all very high conviction in your capabilities after all those conversations, the last thing we will do is pay you to fly out to meet us, and work with us for a while (at least a day, less than a week at most). You have agency in this, in terms of when you can come, how long you can stay, and what you want to work on while you're here. We ue you have fun!
Finally, we'll make you an offer and/or discuss logistics. In most cases, we'll have already discusses some of the specifics already, so this won't be full of bad surprises.</description><min_compensation>$150K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$250K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA</location><title>Solutions &amp; Sales Operations</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>54842</job_reference><company>Zensors</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/01f2ed9f6b2573e18e28f42a8c260ee15a0a777a.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/zensors-inc</company_website><company_description>Google Analytics for the physical world</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/54842</url><description>About Zensors

About the role
Zensors is a fast-growing tech startup searching for mission-driven Swiss-Army knives who welcome the challenge of meeting the needs of a growing business. We’re specifically looking for a Sales / Biz Ops Lead who will roll up their sleeves and lead operations as part of GTM efforts. As a key member of our team, you will help, building strong relationships with customers and collaborating with cross-functional leaders internally to deliver consistently excellent customer experiences.
What You’ll Do
Autonomously spearheading growth of new product initiatives and collaborating with product and sales to launch
Working directly with customers to understand their needs and to inform onboarding, implementation, and retention strategies
Building connections with strategic channel partners
Analyzing budget and financials to help determine internal growth strategy
Determining and continuously improving on internal metrics to track progress; building out dashboards and reporting for the team to drive better decision-making
Managing day-to-day operations and building out functional organizations and processes as we rapidly grow
Promote the value of the product and upsell services and products with brand image and promoting value through customer experience
Promote an energetic fan base for products and locate brand ambassadors to share the product's benefit and value
What We’re Looking For
3-5 years of experience in Sales Operations, Sales Strategy, Finance, Management Consulting, or Project Management
Experience with datasets, synthesizing insights, and recommending actions from data
Exceptional ability to communicate and foster positive business relationships
Experience working with executive-level clients or stakeholders
Technical skills required, as they relate for the use of the product to service to be solid
Deep understanding of customers concerns and thoughts regarding the use of products, and the ability to troubleshoot as needed
About Zensors
Zensors provides streams of interconnected, actionable data that can be extracted from a single video feed along with an AI engine that can interpret, optimize, forecast or alert on changes in customer demand, internal staffing and other key service metrics in real time. With vision based deep learning, what was once an expensive, error prone, and time consuming process, has become, cost-effective, and accurate method of collecting and analyzing large amounts of data. Zensors is at the forefront of this modern movement with a unique AI system that provides data collection and analysis 24 hours a day, seven days a week, even in the toughest conditions.</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Redwood City, CA / Remote</location><title>Internship: 3D Character Artist (Realistic)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>54561</job_reference><company>DreamWorld</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/e32caa6326e2187568d8936a5e7a613643f07428.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/dreamworld</company_website><company_description>DreamWorld is a next-gen Minecraft</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/54561</url><description>About DreamWorld
DreamWorld is an infinite game world, with unparalleled multiplayer capacity. Think Minecraft, created by generative AI, with all players together in one world.
Here's a video of our current gameplay: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VIwL3vzt4XE&amp;list=PL0x8zBFe0sRjHB3ddXPLh6g6gTEMNeuDg&amp;ab_channel=PlayDreamWorld
Look at the software that has fundamentally changed how people live: Search (Google), Social Networks (Facebook), Ecommerce (Amazon). Now think of what will come in the next 25. One of these monumental shifts will be the pervasiveness of the Digital World, and it is our goal to create it.
We believe this Digital World will rise out of the medium that's had the seeds of it for a while, Gaming. So, we are building a massive Sandbox MMO, with the game focused on User Creation and Socializing. You can think of our initial goal as creating a successor to Minecraft and World of Warcraft.
About the role
Skills: Zbrush, Autodesk Maya, Blender, 3DS Max, Unreal Engine
We're looking for great intern teammates that are willing to dive in, work hard, and learn. This is a 6+ month program.
You must proficient in modeling and texturing for realistic characters. Unreal Engine experience is a huge plus. Unreal Engine Metahuman experience is a huge help. Rigging is a nice to have.
You will work on modular humanoid characters, and ideally creatures / non-humanoids as well.
When submitting your application, kindly include your portfolio link.
You should take this job if you:
Passionate about making and playing games.
Want to be a founding member of a company where you steer artistic vision, product design, and future growth.
Want to have a visible, critical impact on weekly releases.
Enjoy minimal process and deciding what you work on every week.
Strongly proficient in industry standard software such as Maya, ZBrush, Substance Painter/Designer, and Photoshop.
Work with the technical partners to define and refine the look and feel of the characters for the project.
Collaborate with Engineering and other artists to develop the character creation and integration pipeline.
Ensure character assets are of the highest artistic quality.
Experienced with Unreal Engine
Portfolio demonstrates relevant skills including realistic characters.
Be able to rig your character to the Unreal Engine skeleton.
Technology
We're building DreamWorld in C++ on Unreal Engine, creating gameplay features that we ship every week to eager players.</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Medellín, Antioquia, CO / Remote</location><title>Data Acquisition Specialist (Colombia location)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>60716</job_reference><company>Veryfi, Inc.</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/b363a44bfe1278786c4092bd157ce82f208e1a21.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/veryfi-inc</company_website><company_description>APIs to Liberate Trapped Data in Unstructured Documents</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/60716</url><description>About Veryfi, Inc.
Veryfi empowers organizations to transform their unstructured data in the form of receipts, invoices, purchase orders, checks, W2s and other business documents into structured data at scale. Their suite of data transformation APIs can be leveraged for many use cases in financial services to deliver valuable business intelligence in seconds. Trusted by enterprises and technology companies alike, Veryfi’s AI-based platform is being leveraged by companies worldwide.
Veryfi is backed by NewView Capital (NVC), Act One Ventures, TI PLatform, Y Combinator and Zillionize
Veryfi Raises $12 Million To Use AI To Tackle The Unstructured Data Entry Market https://www.forbes.com/sites/rebeccaszkutak/2021/04/26/veryfi-raises-12-million-to-use-ai-to-tackle-the-unstructured-data-entry-market/?sh=886fe19183f8
The Untapped Potential of Unstructured Data https://nvc.vc/perspectives/veryfi-the-untapped-potential-of-unstructured-data/
Capterra Reviews https://www.capterra.com/p/141684/Veryfi-Receipts-and-Expenses/reviews/
COME AND SAY G'DAY!
About the role
Skills: Python
Location: Hybrid/Remote Work
We are seeking a full-time Data Acquisition specialist, who has the ability to correctly identify patterns as becoming a specialized, but essential skill when dealing with large amounts of data. Diverse fields from cyber threat to genomics rely on accurately identifying, acquiring, and, at times, correcting a very specific pattern among a sea of potential targets.
What You’ll be Doing
You are a regular expression expert comfortable dealing with texts from all over the world. You don’t necessarily have to be fluent in many languages, just be able to process/manipulate many different languages, formats and symbols with ease. The ideal candidate should be able to create/modify the patterns into classes/categories/rules with experience in automating and parallelizing tasks. You have a working knowledge of python is necessary.
Qualifications:
CS degree is not essential, but a degree/experience is necessary in sufficiently technical or related fields, e.g bioinformatics data preprocessing, quantitative linguistics, fields where data extraction from a large number of logs/dataset is involved.
Bonus:
Excellent command of python if the candidate aspires to take on the role of task automation. Mongodb Linux command line environment Exposure to cloud environments (AWS, GCP) Understanding of distance functions and how they relate to error correction Regex experience with right to left languages, e.g. Hebrew and Arabic
Notice(s)
Salary Range Disclaimer
The base salary range represents the low and high end of the Veryfi salary range for this position. Actual salaries will vary depending on factors including but not limited to location, experience, and performance. The range listed is just one component of Veryfi's total compensation package for employees. Other rewards may include an open Paid Time Off policy, and many region-specific benefits.
Equal Opportunities and Accommodations Statement
Veryfi is deeply committed to building a workplace and global community where inclusion is not only valued, but prioritized. We’re proud to be an equal opportunity employer, seeking to create a welcoming and diverse environment. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, gender identity or expression, family status, marital status, sexual orientation, national origin, genetics, neuro-diversity, disability, age, or veteran status, or any other non-merit based or legally protected grounds.
We value diverse experiences, including those who have had prior contact with the criminal legal system. We are committed to providing individuals with criminal records, including formerly incarcerated individuals, a fair chance at employment.
Where legally permitted, Veryfi requires all individuals attending or working out of Veryfi offices or visiting Veryfi clients to be fully vaccinated against COVID-19. For positions that can only be performed at an Veryfi office, candidates must be fully vaccinated against COVID-19 and present acceptable proof of vaccination by the date of hire as a condition of employment. For positions that require some in-office work or in-person client meetings, exceptions to these in-office or in-person job requirements may be made at the discretion of the business through June 2022, at which point full vaccination will be required. Veryfi will consider requests for reasonable accommodation as required under applicable law. To qualify as being fully vaccinated against COVID-19 there should have been a two week period after receiving the second dose (or any government recommended booster shot) in a 2-dose COVID-19 vaccine series, or a two week period after receiving a single-dose (or any government recommended booster shot) in a single dose COVID-19 vaccine
Technology
(a) Native Mobile apps: Swift, Objective-C &amp; Kotlin
(b) Backend: Python 3, TensorFlow, APIs on Django, Hub/Web on Flask
(c) IaaS: AWS with auto deploys to 4 geographies (read the deployment posts by Andrew here https://medium.com/the-road-to-silicon-valley)
(d) Database: Amazon Aurora</description><min_compensation>$24K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$36K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>New York, NY, US / Remote</location><title>UX Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>47241</job_reference><company>Skio</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/c87a6ed342316be397663cebac7a3099c11d1320.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/skio</company_website><company_description>Subscriptions for Shopify</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/47241</url><description>About Skio
Skio (skio.com, $10M+ ARR w/ 90% margins in 3 years, profitable, $8.4M raised) helps brands on Shopify sell subscriptions without ripping their hair out.
Brands using Skio include Liquid I.V., Bulletproof, Milk Bar, Barstool Sports, Unilever, 100 Thieves, Vega, KOS, KITSCH, True Botanicals, mindbodygreen, Transparent Labs, GHOST, Wild One, OpenStore, The Nue Co., Immi, DRMTLGY, Boba Tea Protein, KraveBeauty, Glamnetic, Doe Lashes, Magic Mind, Remedy Organics, &amp; Siete Foods.
Our team (skio.com/team) brings experience from Shopify, Recharge, Klaviyo, Attentive, Google, Amazon, Facebook, Pinterest, Hulu, Twitch, Nacelle, Smile.io, Groupon, Databricks, &amp; Y Combinator.
Investors (skio.com/investors) include Y Combinator, Adjacent, Jason Wong, Shaan Puri, Julian Shapiro, Geoff Woo, &amp; Sahil Bloom, as well as founders and executives of companies like Italic, Magic Mind, Immi, Bev, Smile.io, Okendo, Wonderment, Archive, Parker, HVMN, &amp; MuteSix.
About the role
https://skio.com/careers
Technology
Tech stack: Next.js (React), Hasura (GraphQL/Postgres), Serverless (AWS)</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>New York, NY, US / Remote</location><title>Launch Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>50514</job_reference><company>Skio</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/c87a6ed342316be397663cebac7a3099c11d1320.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/skio</company_website><company_description>Subscriptions for Shopify</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/50514</url><description>About Skio
Skio (skio.com, $10M+ ARR w/ 90% margins in 3 years, profitable, $8.4M raised) helps brands on Shopify sell subscriptions without ripping their hair out.
Brands using Skio include Liquid I.V., Bulletproof, Milk Bar, Barstool Sports, Unilever, 100 Thieves, Vega, KOS, KITSCH, True Botanicals, mindbodygreen, Transparent Labs, GHOST, Wild One, OpenStore, The Nue Co., Immi, DRMTLGY, Boba Tea Protein, KraveBeauty, Glamnetic, Doe Lashes, Magic Mind, Remedy Organics, &amp; Siete Foods.
Our team (skio.com/team) brings experience from Shopify, Recharge, Klaviyo, Attentive, Google, Amazon, Facebook, Pinterest, Hulu, Twitch, Nacelle, Smile.io, Groupon, Databricks, &amp; Y Combinator.
Investors (skio.com/investors) include Y Combinator, Adjacent, Jason Wong, Shaan Puri, Julian Shapiro, Geoff Woo, &amp; Sahil Bloom, as well as founders and executives of companies like Italic, Magic Mind, Immi, Bev, Smile.io, Okendo, Wonderment, Archive, Parker, HVMN, &amp; MuteSix.
About the role
https://skio.com/careers
Technology
Tech stack: Next.js (React), Hasura (GraphQL/Postgres), Serverless (AWS)</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>New York, NY, US / Remote</location><title>Anything</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>47535</job_reference><company>Skio</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/c87a6ed342316be397663cebac7a3099c11d1320.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/skio</company_website><company_description>Subscriptions for Shopify</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/47535</url><description>About Skio
Skio (skio.com, $10M+ ARR w/ 90% margins in 3 years, profitable, $8.4M raised) helps brands on Shopify sell subscriptions without ripping their hair out.
Brands using Skio include Liquid I.V., Bulletproof, Milk Bar, Barstool Sports, Unilever, 100 Thieves, Vega, KOS, KITSCH, True Botanicals, mindbodygreen, Transparent Labs, GHOST, Wild One, OpenStore, The Nue Co., Immi, DRMTLGY, Boba Tea Protein, KraveBeauty, Glamnetic, Doe Lashes, Magic Mind, Remedy Organics, &amp; Siete Foods.
Our team (skio.com/team) brings experience from Shopify, Recharge, Klaviyo, Attentive, Google, Amazon, Facebook, Pinterest, Hulu, Twitch, Nacelle, Smile.io, Groupon, Databricks, &amp; Y Combinator.
Investors (skio.com/investors) include Y Combinator, Adjacent, Jason Wong, Shaan Puri, Julian Shapiro, Geoff Woo, &amp; Sahil Bloom, as well as founders and executives of companies like Italic, Magic Mind, Immi, Bev, Smile.io, Okendo, Wonderment, Archive, Parker, HVMN, &amp; MuteSix.
About the role
https://skio.com/careers
Technology
Tech stack: Next.js (React), Hasura (GraphQL/Postgres), Serverless (AWS)</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>New York, NY, US / Remote</location><title>Product Designer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>48785</job_reference><company>Skio</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/c87a6ed342316be397663cebac7a3099c11d1320.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/skio</company_website><company_description>Subscriptions for Shopify</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/48785</url><description>About Skio
Skio (skio.com, $10M+ ARR w/ 90% margins in 3 years, profitable, $8.4M raised) helps brands on Shopify sell subscriptions without ripping their hair out.
Brands using Skio include Liquid I.V., Bulletproof, Milk Bar, Barstool Sports, Unilever, 100 Thieves, Vega, KOS, KITSCH, True Botanicals, mindbodygreen, Transparent Labs, GHOST, Wild One, OpenStore, The Nue Co., Immi, DRMTLGY, Boba Tea Protein, KraveBeauty, Glamnetic, Doe Lashes, Magic Mind, Remedy Organics, &amp; Siete Foods.
Our team (skio.com/team) brings experience from Shopify, Recharge, Klaviyo, Attentive, Google, Amazon, Facebook, Pinterest, Hulu, Twitch, Nacelle, Smile.io, Groupon, Databricks, &amp; Y Combinator.
Investors (skio.com/investors) include Y Combinator, Adjacent, Jason Wong, Shaan Puri, Julian Shapiro, Geoff Woo, &amp; Sahil Bloom, as well as founders and executives of companies like Italic, Magic Mind, Immi, Bev, Smile.io, Okendo, Wonderment, Archive, Parker, HVMN, &amp; MuteSix.
About the role
https://skio.com/careers
Technology
Tech stack: Next.js (React), Hasura (GraphQL/Postgres), Serverless (AWS)</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Oakland, CA / Remote</location><title>Full stack Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>49903</job_reference><company>Informed K12</company><company_logo>https://avatar.tobi.sh/1158918516?size=520</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/informed-k12</company_website><company_description>Workflow software to help districts keep up with the pace of change needed to run their day to day operations</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/49903</url><description>About Informed K12
We are building a workflow and reporting platform that has to be powerful enough for support hundreds of unique approval processes in a school district but easy enough for anyone, from the Chief Business Officer to a school site office manager, to use.
Our users work at all levels of the district in district office departments ranging from finance, payroll, HR, custodial services, transportation, food services and more. They also work at individual school sites as principals, teachers, substitutes, counselors, and even parents. To meet the needs of this wide variety of users, there are thousands of unique forms and processes on our system that span from new hire packets to student injury reports to bus services requests to permission slips. Our backend models need to be flexible enough to support a wide variety of use cases but structured enough to allow for scale and data retrieval across the entire system.
Other technical challenges may relate to:
Data security and privacy, as our forms may collect sensitive information
Customized bulk data exports in a variety of formats (csv, pdf, zip)
Seasonality and spikes of system usage - 1/3 of our total traffic for the year occurs in the rush up to the start of the school year, in August and September
Finally, because our districts rely on us for their critical processes we must ensure our system is reliable and stable. The team understands that working code is not enough and a primary component of an engineer's job is to improve the maintainability of the long-term structure of the system.
About the role
What do we do for school districts?
Currently, we’re helping our districts adapt to the pandemic and properly provide for their communities.. Our admins are figuring out how to deliver PPEs to their schools, how to feed families when classes are not in session, how to give internet access to students without it at home, how to support special needs with remote learning and more. To do all this, they not only need to communicate rapid changes to their staff, they also need to ensure everyone has the tools they need to do their day to day work along with these new responsibilities. Our platform and team enables the processes that help districts keep ahead of these evolving needs and support their people.
Types of work you might be doing:
Building a consistent and reusable front end architecture to support our long term vision
Digging into back end performance issues
Exploring the space and find solutions to problems that we may not know we even have
Contributing to our engineering culture that encourages everyone to bring their whole selves to work
A little bit of everything both in engineering and across the company
How is this job unique?
The mindset that runs through everything that we do is our focus on having an equitable, diverse and inclusive culture. How we sell our platform, how we support our districts, and how we write our code. Every team and process works in a way that takes those values and goals into consideration. We conduct onsite research to understand the day to day of everyone who touches the platform from the front office secretary at the school site to the assistant superintendent of business in the district office. We also work to be intentional in how we collaborate as an engineering team to make sure that our newest engineers are supported and have the space to speak up and that our most senior people continue to have to space to learn and hone their craft.
Quick state of the business
The company is doing well! In 2020 we got to 135% of our yearly sales target by October, and since then we're continuing to sell very well. We’re a growing company, looking to continue doing so sustainably and responsibly, and are in it for the long haul.
How we build it
Our Stack: Rails 6.0, Postgresql, Typescript (React/jQuery/Vanilla), Sass CSS, Sidekiq, Circle CI, Heroku, Github
As a platform we focus on the needs of school districts in aggregate. We don’t build custom features for single schools, rather we learn what are things that can help every district. Additionally we don’t try to “disrupt” how school districts work, we meet them where they are. By partnering with our district staff and administrators on critical processes they manage day to day, we work with them over multiple years and are eventually able to bring about organizational and cultural change together.
Making sure that we are building things that districts need means that we do a lot of product research before we start on something. We build things deliberately and intentionally as our districts need a consistent and predictable platform. We make sure we spend the time to deeply understand the needs of our users across all levels of the district. Our platform does a lot of complicated things so we try to limit complexity to where it is needed.
Similarly we try to use technology that is mature and focus on effectiveness over current trends. Our platform is built on a Rails monolith with 100% unit test coverage as well as integration testing for the “happy path” (all tests run in ~7 minutes on CI). With a small team we try to automate what we can while writing clean readable code with great commit messages. It’s not a perfect codebase! But it does some important things very well.
Job posting link: https://informed-k12.breezy.hr/p/b9ddfab2d429
Technology
Our users work at all levels of the district in district office departments ranging from finance, payroll, HR, custodial services, transportation, food services and more. They also work at individual school sites as principals, teachers, substitutes, counselors, and even parents. To meet the needs of this wide variety of users, there are thousands of unique forms and processes on our system that span from new hire packets to student injury reports to bus services requests to permission slips. Our backend models need to be flexible enough to support a wide variety of use cases but structured enough to allow for scale and data retrieval across the entire system.
Other technical challenges may relate to:
Data security and privacy, as our forms may collect sensitive information
Customized bulk data exports in a variety of formats (csv, pdf, zip)
Seasonality and spikes of system usage - 1/3 of our total traffic for the year occurs in the rush up to the start of the school year, in August and September
Finally, because our districts rely on us for their critical processes we must ensure our system is reliable and stable. The team understands that working code is not enough and a primary component of an engineer's job is to improve the maintainability of the long-term structure of the system.
We work in small, nimble teams of 2-3 engineers. We have a bi-weekly standup meeting and use Clubhouse to manage our projects and tasks. Projects that each team takes on range from real-time search and export tools, database and server optimization, or building our front end system. We do planning on a quarterly basis and some projects take a few months, while some 6 months to a year. When you join you will probably end up getting to work with everyone on the team at some point.
We take code quality seriously and are constantly improving our codebase. Every project we work on has dedicated time to address tech debt and we prioritize code quality initiatives on our product road map. Oh, and we never ship code without writing a full suite of tests (don’t worry, we’ll help in case this is newer to you)!</description><min_compensation>$115</min_compensation><max_compensation>$149</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Hourly</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Remote</location><title>Design Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>49042</job_reference><company>Anima</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/d24874dbb8f1a038430d7e22f6fa5816224e777c.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/anima</company_website><company_description>The next generation care enablement platform</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/49042</url><description>About Anima
Anima builds Care Enablement for care teams. You'll be building a product that saves lives and multiple Clinical Engineers (ex-MDs and fullstack SWEs) quit lucrative medicine jobs to join Anima for that very reason! Our ambition is to be the OS for all of healthcare and life sciences, through a proprietary active learning, crowdsourcing training architecture - we call it Anima 2.0. We already have one of the biggest, highest quality labelled datasets in the world.
We're profitable, growing at 300-400% MoM, and went from $0 ARR to $1m ARR in 6 months from launch (Apr '22). That's pretty unprecedented in SaaS, nevermind healthcare! We have a pretty unique hacker culture at Anima: almost everyone is technical and can code. A 'knights of the round table' structure and thinking from first principles is core to our culture, and is how we've made such rapid progress. It's reflected in how we operate:
There's no separate product &amp; engineering teams - instead, we have Clinical Engineers who are both their own customers (MDs) and are strong fullstack engs, collaborating with pure software engineers. Due to the quality of our team, there's a heavy focus on coaching and teaching, with minimal to no line management.
We're relentlessly resourceful - in 14 months, we've built an extremely loved enterprise app (NPS = 87) that users have said 'seems too good to be true'. Anima can take an information complete medical history as good or better than a typical human doctor, and automates patient comms and clinical notes.
Anima is a safe haven for free thinkers and we've been careful to build a culture where everyone feels comfortable being their complete self, without ever needing to self-censor. Our hiring acceptance rate is around 0.5-0.8%, which is lower than YC. You're joining hyper elite special forces, and your crewmates will never let you down or waste your time.
We hire candidates from all over the world. We have remote hubs in EU West and NA, and plans to seed some in person teams in those areas too in the next 12 months (in addition to our fully remote teams).
We have a good time :) we've had team lunches in Duck&amp;Waffle, Breakfast Club, dumplings in Chinatown, had private screenings in our own cinema, booked out the Sky Pool etc. We'll be doing at least 2x international team meets, with the next one in a beautiful chateau in Southern France.
About the role
Skills: Figma
To apply:
Click here to start your application
IMPORTANT: you must complete our Ashby application form linked above in order to be considered for this role; sending a message through WaaS is not sufficient. If we don't receive an application form, we will not consider your application!
Click the link to start your application by completing a few quick questions. We'll review your application as soon as possible and if your answers catch our eye, next steps would be a short screening and a 30 min intro chat with one of the founders. Please make sure to mention WaaS when you apply!
Join Anima and save lives 🌟
Do you wish your work had greater tangible impact? Join Anima (YC W21), and you can have your cake and eat it too: we pay upper quartile for salary + equity, and you'll help to solve super interesting technical problems that will save lives.
We’ve gone from $0 ARR to $1m ARR in 6mo from our April 22 launch! Recently we’ve been growing around 300-400% MoM! Our NPS is 87, we’ve never churned a clinic and we’re growing very efficiently - we’re profitable with infinite runway. We’ve gotten here through being design-led and UX obsessed. We see every line of code as building proprietary UX that leads to user love and pricing power. We care so much that all our engineers chose to become proficient in Figma :)
Hi - I'm Shun, a medical doctor and CEO of Anima. Thanks for checking out our job ad! We’re tackling a problem that has affected everyone in some way.
Globally, millions die every year because their medical problems aren’t treated quickly enough. Hundreds of millions suffer pain, worry and discomfort needlessly because of long waiting times.
We’ve built ambitious software to automate the entire healthcare workflow - from history taking consultations, to report abstraction, to recommending &amp; saving a coded action plan for the patient, ready for a human doctor to greenlight.
By doing this, we get patients optimal care within 24 hours and 10x the clinical workflow in the process.
Backed by a top 1% VC 🚀
We were one of the hottest companies of YC’s W21 batch: we raised over $2.5m before Demo Day within 4 days, led by Hummingbird (consistently top 1% of global returns), giving us a runway of 4+ years. We are pretty unique among health techs: we have both medical and engineering domain expertise. I wrote the first backend in Node, 80% of which is still used, with no major vulnerabilities found from recent pen testing. As a doctor and former HM Treasury health policy advisor managing £4bn budgets in UK health spending, I have full stack domain knowledge and personal experience of the problem we’re solving.
Our mission is to deliver precision medicine to everyone in the world, within 24 hours. We know exactly how to get there and we’re moving ferociously with focus.
Join a design-led company where incredible UX is at the core of every line of code, and everything we do
Great design is built our DNA: Rachel, co-founder and COO, heads the design of all our products. Our thesis is that code serves UX - ideally proprietary UX that users are willing to pay a lot for. We care a lot - we always build clear UX directed graphs (sometimes called user flows) and Figma mockups before beginning architecting or writing a single line of code. We close the loop by using our UX DiGraphs as E2E testing models. We care so much that all our engineers chose to become proficient in Figma :)
We’re looking for visionary designer leaders and architects who can think from first principles and have high growth potential - great decision makers who deserve to have complete autonomy and are forces of nature when empowered with it. At the same time, we are deeply collaborative, and through mutual and self-challenge, we converge towards the optimum, and decisively execute. We are united by child-like intellectual curiosity and experiment and wander freely when the right path isn’t clear. We believe all future managers should be formidable ICs &amp; domain experts. Decisions are never made in isolation by the founders. All information is transparently available to the whole team on our Notion - every meeting, decision, success, failure. Anima is a safe refuge for everyone to share their honest thoughts, feelings and be their complete unfiltered self. We offer unlimited holidays and flexibility over work schedule and location.
The quickest way to get your creations into the hands of users
When everyone is UX obsessed, it’s much easier to stay on the same page &amp; execute rapidly. This means we have a super short latency from ideation to real usage - here are two recent examples:
Rachel, co-founder and currently leading design, talked to power users and discovered a critical need for multiple organisations to able to join the same real time multiplayer dashboard. She mocked up a new dashboard in Figma with our engineers, getting async feedback from power users throughout (our users are generally very fanatical and helpful!), and we got it shipped within 5 days!
Alex (Clinical Engineer), realised that there was a need for care teams to communicate internally and with outside collaborators, and helped Rachel create UX flows and mockups for a game changing feature where virtual care teams could discuss cases and see a single source of truth for the patient history. We managed to get it shipped in 4 weeks!
Does this sound like you?
Hungry and wants their shot to change the world - a force of nature when empowered with the tools, resources and development to do it.
Bored and frustrated at big companies; feel held back by red tape, bureaucracy and poor decisions.
Keen to understand the big picture &amp; entire context of the company and vertical; has a sense of urgency for growth towards a senior executive role.
Have hacked together a cool project in the past, that did something useful, and want to relive that feeling of accomplishment (everyday!).
High sigma product intuition and empathy - an uncanny ability to intuit the deepest anxieties and opportunities for user joy even with minimal user research.
Obsessed with optimising UX: quickly able to understand the needs of our users and translate deep anxieties and latent opportunities for excitement and joy into optimal UX flows.
Exceptional attention to detail &amp; an eye for aesthetics that ensure a careful &amp; thorough approach to Figma mockups.
An excellent communicator: concisely and clearly communicate designs to the team both verbally and through the materials you produce (sketches, wireframes, prototypes etc.)
Able to understand and distil complex concepts &amp; processes and make them accessible for our users in the form of simple, elegant user flows and interactions.
Able to work in an iterative design process, guided by user feedback &amp; company goals; motivated and energised by group critique.
Seeks to maximise not only self productivity, but combined team productivity, communicating the right things at the right time through the right channels (verbal/Slack/Notion).
Intellectually curious and loves learning - able to tackle entirely novel challenges that lack prior precedent through applying strong design fundamentals and first principles thinking, creatively using the best tools for the job to maximise user delight.
Familiarity with Figma and/or hungry to learn.
We don’t enforce any particular experience level, but you’ll need to demonstrate most of the above through past projects and/or our assessment process.
Our current stack &amp; what to expect from the role
Here is some information on our technical stack in case you are interested (this may not make much sense to you - that's okay!): we are tech agonistic, and collectively choose the best tools for the job. We’re constantly looking to maximise our productivity and minimise what we call “discounted dev time cost” for shipping features. We have 2 separate fully functional web apps in prod: one for clinical users and one for patients. We have good functional &amp; unit test coverage and we recently implemented an advanced CI/CD pipeline which supports golden screenshots and automated frontend tests. We primarily use Figma for our mock-ups &amp; wireframes.
We’re looking to add talented product designers who are hungry and understand the urgency and importance of what we’re doing for society.
First month - some examples of what to expect:
Work with our engineers and sales team to identify, create and implement the user flows that make using Anima a delight for both doctors and patients.
Design and implement creative solutions that improve the clarity and comprehension of our 2 apps, and our website.
Join customer calls to develop a deep understanding of their fundamental motivations and needs/pain points.
Next 6 months - some examples of what to expect:
Lead on the design and implementation for our flagship features, including building out our video consultation offering &amp; seamlessly incorporating integrations with NHS APIs into our UX.
Collaborate with engineers to apply insights from user cohort &amp; A/B testing to inform decisions about feature selection &amp; design.
Hire/scale the team, while implementing the right processes at the right times to maximise discounted team productivity and maximise user delight.
6+ months - some examples of what to expect:
Potential to transition to a more managerial/executive role.
Define and formalise our design standards, and grow and scale our design tools and processes so we keep rapidly shipping features that result in a high retention delta.
This is a permanent role: things get even more exciting down the line!
To apply:
Click here to start your application
Click the link to start your application by completing a few quick questions. We'll review your application as soon as possible and if your answers catch our eye, next steps would be a short screening &amp; 30 min chat with one of the founders. Please make sure to mention WaaS when you apply!
We can't wait to hear from you!
Technology
We see product dev as building incredible, proprietary UX that leads to pricing power, balanced against 'discounted dev cost'. We favour multidimensional and tech agnostic people, who are relentlessly resourceful, rather than dogmatic.
Our whole stack is in TS/JS, with a Lambda microservices BE in Node, DynamoDB, and a large number of GraphQL and REST APIs connected to many AWS services like S3, SQS, SNS, SES, Chime SDK, Opensearch.
We build novel and hard features on a weekly basis, like MDT Hub (Slack for care teams), care orchestration (programmable no-code workflow editor). We work a lot with graphs, and shipping our ML powered features into prod involves solving difficult and novel graph problems - like how do we best cluster similar patient cases? Can we create 'dynamic DAGs' which can recursively self-improve based on clinician intervention feedback?</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Remote</location><title>Fullstack Engineer (Senior / Leadership)</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>45746</job_reference><company>Anima</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/d24874dbb8f1a038430d7e22f6fa5816224e777c.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/anima</company_website><company_description>The next generation care enablement platform</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/45746</url><description>About Anima
Anima builds Care Enablement for care teams. You'll be building a product that saves lives and multiple Clinical Engineers (ex-MDs and fullstack SWEs) quit lucrative medicine jobs to join Anima for that very reason! Our ambition is to be the OS for all of healthcare and life sciences, through a proprietary active learning, crowdsourcing training architecture - we call it Anima 2.0. We already have one of the biggest, highest quality labelled datasets in the world.
We're profitable, growing at 300-400% MoM, and went from $0 ARR to $1m ARR in 6 months from launch (Apr '22). That's pretty unprecedented in SaaS, nevermind healthcare! We have a pretty unique hacker culture at Anima: almost everyone is technical and can code. A 'knights of the round table' structure and thinking from first principles is core to our culture, and is how we've made such rapid progress. It's reflected in how we operate:
There's no separate product &amp; engineering teams - instead, we have Clinical Engineers who are both their own customers (MDs) and are strong fullstack engs, collaborating with pure software engineers. Due to the quality of our team, there's a heavy focus on coaching and teaching, with minimal to no line management.
We're relentlessly resourceful - in 14 months, we've built an extremely loved enterprise app (NPS = 87) that users have said 'seems too good to be true'. Anima can take an information complete medical history as good or better than a typical human doctor, and automates patient comms and clinical notes.
Anima is a safe haven for free thinkers and we've been careful to build a culture where everyone feels comfortable being their complete self, without ever needing to self-censor. Our hiring acceptance rate is around 0.5-0.8%, which is lower than YC. You're joining hyper elite special forces, and your crewmates will never let you down or waste your time.
We hire candidates from all over the world. We have remote hubs in EU West and NA, and plans to seed some in person teams in those areas too in the next 12 months (in addition to our fully remote teams).
We have a good time :) we've had team lunches in Duck&amp;Waffle, Breakfast Club, dumplings in Chinatown, had private screenings in our own cinema, booked out the Sky Pool etc. We'll be doing at least 2x international team meets, with the next one in a beautiful chateau in Southern France.
About the role
Skills: JavaScript, Node.js, TypeScript, Angular
To apply:
Click here to start your application.
IMPORTANT: you must complete our Ashby application form linked above in order to be considered for this role; sending a message through WaaS is not sufficient. If we don't receive an application form, we will not consider your application!
Click the link to start your application by completing a few quick questions. We'll review your application as soon as possible and if your answers catch our eye, next steps would be a technical screen &amp; 15 min intro chat with the CEO. Please make sure to mention WaaS when you apply!
Join Anima and save lives 🌟
Do you wish your work had greater tangible impact? Join Anima, and you can have your cake and eat it too: we pay upper quartile for salary + equity, and you'll solve super interesting technical problems that will save lives.
Hi - I'm Shun, an MD and CEO of Anima. Thanks for checking out our job ad! We’re tackling a problem that has affected everyone in some way.
Millions die every year because their medical problems aren’t treated quickly enough. Hundreds of millions suffer pain, worry and discomfort needlessly because of long waiting times. I founded Anima because I was tired of breaking bad news to patients who later died, because they didn’t get a great care plan quickly. So many of those deaths were avoidable.
We’ve built an ambitious ‘Care Enablement Platform’ to automate the entire healthcare workflow, starting with primary care - combining online consultation with productivity tools and a single source of patient data truth. Anima has next generation features like autogenerating coded clinical notes and patient comms, and a real time multiplayer dashboard with a Slack-like chat experience that supports 1000s of discussion channels per clinic.
By enabling care, we get patients optimal care within 24 hours and 10x the clinical workflow in the process.
Since our launch and first pilot in March 2022, we're now used in dozens of clinics across the country, serving 100,000s of patients. We’ve been growing more than 80% MoM in terms of users and revenue. We’re default alive, and currently have over a decade of runway - though we expect to be strongly cashflow positive by the end of 2023.
Users love our product. The biggest testament to this is that most of our growth comes from virality and referrals with $0 spent on marketing, despite being B2B/enterprise. We have never churned a clinic.
Backed by a top 1% VC. We’ve raised a large Series A just 7 months after launch, in the first bear market of a decade. 🚀
We were one of the hottest companies of YC’s W21 batch and raised our first round in 4 days, led by Hummingbird (consistently top 1% of global returns). We are pretty unique among health techs: we have both medical and engineering domain expertise. I wrote the Anima 1.0 backend in Node, 80% of which is still used. I also built Annie 1.0, a tuned LLM coupled with a policy engine, that can output structured medical summaries, potential differential diagnoses and management plans. As a doctor and former HM Treasury health policy advisor managing £4bn budgets in UK health spending, I’m a technical, product-focused CEO with full stack domain knowledge and personal experience of the problem we’re solving.
Our mission is to deliver precision medicine to everyone in the world, within 24 hours. We know exactly how to get there and we’re moving ferociously with focus, and we have everything we need to win.
#** Anima has a unique hacker culture: everyone is technical with almost complete autonomy akin to ‘Knights of the Round Table’. In 14 months, we built the most advanced Care Enablement platform that exists.**
Over 80% of the product team are ex-technical founders, former CTOs. We also have many technical domain experts (’fullstack Clinical Engineers’, ex-MDs) who are their own users.
Everyone in product is technical at Anima and can write production code. This makes for a truly flat hierarchy. There’s no separate founder, product or customer team - there is very little communication loss because we all deeply understand the problem, engineering, grading for potential features, and trade-offs. Deep domain knowledge &amp; a tight feedback loop between product dev and user pain is how launched in the highly complex health space, growing from 0 to over 100,000 MAUs in months.
We only hire exceptional talent who can think from first principles and have high growth potential - great decision makers who deserve to have complete autonomy and are forces of nature when empowered with it. At the same time, we are deeply collaborative, and through mutual and self-challenge, we converge towards the optimum, and decisively execute. We are united by child-like intellectual curiosity and experiment and wander freely when the right path isn’t clear. We believe all future managers should be formidable ICs &amp; domain experts.
Decisions are never made in isolation by the founders. All information is transparently available to the whole team on our Notion - every meeting, decision, success, failure. Anima is a safe refuge for everyone to share their honest thoughts, feelings and be their complete unfiltered self.
We’re super flexible over work schedule and location. Currently our main hubs are in West Europe (London) and West Coast US.
The quickest way to get your code into the hands of users. In 14 months, we built the most advanced Care Enablement platform that exists.
When everyone is technical and make great decisions, it’s much easier to stay on the same page &amp; execute rapidly. This means we have a super short latency from ideation to real usage - here are two recent examples:
When everyone is technical and make great decisions, it’s much easier to stay on the same page &amp; execute rapidly. This means we have a super short latency from ideation to real usage.
Here are 3 concrete examples with specs and timelines (I’d be delighted to demo any of these to you):
Jay, built an verticalized analytics platform for Anima with Elasticsearch, supporting advanced features like a no-code query builder (similar to Amplitude) in 6 weeks. He also recently built semantic search and released Annie 1.5, a semantic search enabled, global context aware LLM that can converse and answer any question about any patient in the clinic.
Alex, a clinical engineer, built ‘Slack for medical teams’, supporting 1000s of channels per organisation and a real time single source of truth for patient data, in 4 weeks, picking up a large set of new technologies on the way (ground up built from low-level services like Appsync, GraphQL, not Twilio).
Dennis built a lightning fast cloud document library for clinics in a few days, with &lt;100ms traversals through preloading. Recently, when faced with an ancient legacy API that took 30s to return an array of hits, he hacked together an async indexing service with caching that reduced latency to &lt;2s without harmful race conditions. He built and deployed to prod this in under 24 hours.
If high growth delta and joining an elite scrappy crew is your priority, you’re gonna love it here.
Does this sound like you?
Hungry and wants their shot to change the world - a force of nature when empowered with the tools, resources and development to do it. Sees joining Anima as potentially their shot to do this, and takes duty to crew and mission extremely seriously.
Obsessively concerned with UX, and optimises for this when building features rather than arbitrary technical goals.
Bored and frustrated at big companies; feel held back by red tape, bureaucracy and poor decisions.
Keen to understand the big picture &amp; entire context of the company and vertical; impatient for growth towards a senior executive role.
Expert competency in TS, and reasonably tech + language agnostic. Comfortable with key frameworks/libraries like Angular, Node and React. Able to work full stack in JS/TS. Values pragmatism and open discussion from first principles rather than dogma.
Seeks to maximise not only self productivity, but combined team productivity, communicating the right things at the right time through the right channels (verbal/Slack/Notion).
Disciplined towards best practice version control, CI/CD and code extensibility. Values ‘interface safety’ through dimensionality reduction at interfaces.
Exceptional at ‘breadth-first search’ through Googling when tackling new challenges, and consistently mindful of local maxima.
Intellectually curious with a growth mindset - able to tackle entirely novel challenges that lack prior precedent through applying strong CS fundamentals and first principles thinking, creatively using the right data structures &amp; algorithms to solve problems 90/10.
Familiarity with AWS (APIG, DynamoDB, Lambda, Cognito, Amplify, CloudFormation) and/or hungry to learn.
We don’t enforce any particular experience level, but you’ll need to demonstrate most of the above through past projects and/or our assessment process.
Our current stack &amp; what to expect from the role
We are tech agonistic, and collectively choose the best tools for the job. We’re constantly looking to maximise our productivity and minimise what we call “discounted dev time cost” for shipping features. We have 2 separate fully functional web apps in prod: one for clinical users and one for patients. Our stack is currently entirely in JS/TS: Angular + Capacitor + Electron, React (internal tools), Amplitude (analytics), a fully serverless backend in AWS (Cognito, Appsync GraphQL, Lambda, DynamoDB). We have good functional &amp; unit test coverage and CI/CD.
Our stack is in a great place already: highly scalable, cost effective, good test coverage, easily maintained, secure and performant with minimal to zero Ops. The product and codebase are stable and loved by our users. We write, test, deploy &amp; ship new features rapidly.
Strategically, we prioritise strong frontend-backend decoupling through GraphQL and strong modularisation of frontend and backend into hierarchical pure modules, with high abstraction internal services and helpers, allowing ephemeral lances (similar to ‘squads’) to work on functional modules without needing to understand or be overly concerned about other parts of the codebase.
We’re looking to add talented engineers who are hungry and understand the urgency and importance of what we’re doing for society.
First month - some examples of what to expect:
Help add further key third party API integrations, including with legacy EMR systems and national APIs like e.g. the electronic prescribing service, allowing Anima to directly issue prescriptions.
Iterate on a proprietary graph traversal algorithm to improve patient care and clinical value, and increasingly move away from explicit curation to implicit curation by NNs.
Ship important features that will directly increase delta lives saved in your first 2 weeks.
Join customer calls to develop a deep understanding of their fundamental motivations and needs/pain points.
Next 6 months - some examples of what to expect:
Help architect and deploy a scalable &amp; cost effective ETL data pipeline with version control, outputting clean data ready for tokenisation.
Help deploy our active deep learning training &amp; validation architecture to prod, so that we can correctly eat up our ‘1.0’ systems at the right time
Build cutting edge products like global context aware chat with semantic search, care orchestration and LLM-enabled cloud telephony e2e
Hire/scale the team, while implementing the right processes at the right times to maximise discounted team productivity and minimise discounted dev time cost for shipping.
6+ months - some examples of what to expect:
Potential to transition to a more managerial/executive role. Lead an autonomous lance of elite engineers to fix healthcare and save lives.
Work with the ML/data team to creatively ideate and ship features to improve ETL pipeline throughput and quality through a data-driven approach powered by analytics.
This is a permanent role: things get even more exciting down the line!
To apply:
Click here to start your application
Click the link to start your application by completing a few quick questions. We'll review your application as soon as possible and if your answers catch our eye, next steps would be a technical screen &amp; 15 min intro chat with the CEO. Please make sure to mention WaaS when you apply!
We can't wait to hear from you!
Technology
We see product dev as building incredible, proprietary UX that leads to pricing power, balanced against 'discounted dev cost'. We favour multidimensional and tech agnostic people, who are relentlessly resourceful, rather than dogmatic.
Our whole stack is in TS/JS, with a Lambda microservices BE in Node, DynamoDB, and a large number of GraphQL and REST APIs connected to many AWS services like S3, SQS, SNS, SES, Chime SDK, Opensearch.
We build novel and hard features on a weekly basis, like MDT Hub (Slack for care teams), care orchestration (programmable no-code workflow editor). We work a lot with graphs, and shipping our ML powered features into prod involves solving difficult and novel graph problems - like how do we best cluster similar patient cases? Can we create 'dynamic DAGs' which can recursively self-improve based on clinician intervention feedback?</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA</location><title>Generalist Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>45965</job_reference><company>Dots 💸</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/ef214a749c163e81772f2ba192fdf4eeec23bbb3.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/dots-2</company_website><company_description>Developer friendly drop in payouts infrastructure</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/45965</url><description>About Dots 💸
Dots is a developer-friendly API that lets businesses pay their contractors through just a few lines of code. Whether its gig workers like Uber drivers, sellers on marketplaces like Etsy, or simply your local handyman - Dots’ abstracts away the complexity of payouts completely. We manage the entire process: information collection (KYC), payments through any rail (ACH, Venmo, CashApp, Zelle, international, and many more to come), and even filing tax forms! Dots lets developers get payouts up and running over just a few hours, rather than the many months this would normally take.
We believe the next generation of workers are already here, and are contractors in various shapes and sizes. We’re dedicated to providing a simple-to-use API that makes money movement as flexible as the modern workforce.
About the role
Skills: Python, React
About Dots
Dots is a developer-friendly API that lets businesses pay their contractors through just a few lines of code. Whether its gig workers like Uber drivers, sellers on marketplaces like Etsy, or simply just your local handyman - Dots’ abstracts away the complexity of payouts completely. We manage the entire process: information collection (KYC), payments through any rail (ACH, Venmo, CashApp, Zelle, international, and many more to come), and even filing tax forms! Dots lets developers get payouts up and running over just a few hours, rather than the many months this would normally take.
We believe the next generation of workers are already here, and are contractors in various shapes and sizes. We’re dedicated to providing a simple-to-use API that makes money movement as flexible as the modern workforce.
What you'll do
As a generalist engineer, you're willing to take risks, iterate and make your own path. You will have a say in every decision made at Dots and drive the change you want to see. You're excited by our vision to revolutionize money movement , eager to contribute to it, and energized by our ambiguity. You're ready to write a lot of code, and comfortable throwing a lot of that out as we test and iterate, especially since you'll be an integral part of driving that iteration. You're happy working in an fluid environment, and eager to create the structure it lacks.
What you'll bring
You have a strong technical background (No minimum work experience required but a history of excellent projects is recommended)
You enjoy delivering beautiful and polished front-end experiences in React, but you also know how to write an API (Python)
You are willing to design scrappy systems. We'll have to refactor code as we scale, but we still want to build on good fundamentals
You have a willingness to learn and have fun!
Bonus points if you have
worked in FinTech or Finance
infrastructure experience with AWS, K8s
Tech Stack
Frontend in React
Backend in Python
AWS, ECS
GitHub, Linear, Slack, Notion
What we provide
Private medical insurance, including dental and vision
WeWork or similar co-working stipend
Unlimited vacation policy with a minimum requirement of three weeks off per-year
Regular team off-sites
Home office - Apple equipment and anything else you need to be productive
Technology
Python + React hosted on AWS. We like to keep it simple :).
Postgres + Redis.</description><min_compensation>$130K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$180K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>Durham, North Carolina (Remote Okay) / Remote</location><title>Bioinformatics specialist</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>35229</job_reference><company>Data Driven Bioscience</company><company_logo>https://avatar.tobi.sh/444336898?size=520</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/data-driven-bioscience</company_website><company_description>Cancer Diagnosis 10X faster, 10X cheaper</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/35229</url><description>About Data Driven Bioscience
Data Driven Bioscience is revolutionizing the approach to cancer diagnosis by connecting cancer diagnostic testing with intelligent software. Unlike other industries, we are unaffected by COVID-19 and are continuing to grow.
This is an opportunity to create novel software applications that connect machine learning with cancer tests, and to do work that matters. You will work closely with an interdisciplinary team to connect some of the largest databases in the world through software. We pay a very competitive salary and offer stock ownership of one of the hottest startups anywhere.
We are hiring for a number of different positions including user interface development, back end/cloud-focused dev-ops and data scientists.
There is the potential to work part time and/or remotely.
About the role
Skills: Python, R
Use your skills to cure cancer.
About us:
Data Driven Bioscience is revolutionizing the approach to cancer diagnosis by connecting a novel DNA &amp; RNA sequencing assay with intelligent software.
We are looking for a highly motivated individual to help with both the development of a clinical diagnostic and to support researchers involved in one of the largest genomic projects in the world. This individual will work with a team of exceptionally competent scientists and engineers. We are a small company and are looking for someone who is adaptable and can succeed in many different roles.
We pay a VERY competitive salary and offer stock ownership of one of the hottest startups anywhere. This position can be remote or local.
About you:
This is a position for someone who wants to apply their skills to directly help cancer patients. You will develop new applications that connect cancer tests with large databases and machine learning to improve cancer diagnosis and treatment. You will continue to grow and learn cutting edge skills around machine learning, high performance computing and databases.
Tasks:
• Analysis of large-scale NGS data sets • Provide bioinformatics support to researchers involved in genomic projects • Troubleshoot and maintain bioinformatics pipelines While the list of qualifications below is a guide, don’t worry if you don’t check all the boxes. We are looking for someone who is really good at some of these aspects. Please apply and we’ll follow up promptly.
Preferred Qualifications:
• PhD. degree with 2+ years (or MS degree with 5+ years) of working experience in bioinformatics • Solid computational skills and a deep understanding of NGS data and its analysis • Familiarity with git version-control workflows • Extensive experience in NGS, systems biology and analysis of large-scale genomics datasets • Extensive experience with scientific computing, R or Python preferred • Experience with computational analysis, algorithm development, statistics, and machine learning • Strong UNIX/LINUX expertise required • Experience with NGS datasets and pipelines including pipeline testing, troubleshooting and optimization • Experience with cloud computing: AWS, Google Cloud
Job Type: Full-time.
Part-time and contract positions are also available.</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Redwood City, California / Remote</location><title>3D Artist</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>35049</job_reference><company>DreamCraft Entertainment, Inc.</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/e5350e1545dde29c153c2bb23ad5d1fdb3f3bf68.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/dreamcraft-entertainment-inc</company_website><company_description>Platform that allows anyone to create and monetize video games.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/35049</url><description>About DreamCraft Entertainment, Inc.
We believe games should be created by passionate gamers, regardless of programming knowledge or artistic ability. We are here to make it easier for anyone to create, launch, and earn a living by making games on any platform.
About the role
Skills: Photoshop, Autodesk Maya, 3DS Max
About Us
DreamCraft creates technology that inspires talented individuals to create all kinds of video games without programming. To do that we must break the existing rules of game development based on funded teams and professional engines, and gear up our creators the most intuitive, easy-to-use, instant-deploy tools and unleash their full potential so that they can create the next "Dota", "PUBG", and "Clash of Clans".
Responsibilities
Work on the development of a visual style, design, and overall look for our brand new IP
Create beautiful characters, assets, and environments to be rolled out for production
Contribute with artwork ideas toward communities and forums
Get involved in the look and feel of further projects, including animation, community, and marketing
Generally just nail 2D and 3D for games on various platforms
Requirement
Driven and fierce
2+ years of experience
Capability to independently create concept sketches
Ability to create game ready stylized 3D assets, including high-poly and low-poly
Able to create hand-painted textures and PBR maps
Proven experience with 3D software (e.g. Maya / 3DS Max)
Experience with Adobe Photoshop and Flash or Spine
Pride and responsibility in your work when given the freedom to work independently
Modesty and respect when receiving feedback from your team
Appreciation and understanding of User Interface design
Ability to create rigging and animation a plus
Technology
Here are the technologies we use:
Unity3D
C#, Lua, OpenGL
React, JavaScript, Nodejs, AWS</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA, US</location><title>⌨️ Full-stack Software Development Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>16598</job_reference><company>Acho</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/539c698774160947b830b5edbd9d46daf94911d7.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/acho</company_website><company_description>Modern ERP for Operations Leaders</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/16598</url><description>About Acho
Acho helps business teams turn data into apps. Anyone can connect different databases, build complex data pipelines, and build scalable data applications - all in one place with a point-and-click interface.
About the role
Skills: Kubernetes, Kafka, Spark, Hadoop, Elastic Stack (ELK), CSS, HTML, JavaScript, MySQL, Python, Linux, Docker
🔷 Overview
Hi there 👋, glad that you found us! I hope that this page explains what we do pretty well. Feel free to reach out to us if there is anything unclear.
Acho is building a Collaborative GUI for data engineering tasks. From building a data connector, data pipeline to supporting an application, we make Acho accessible to all members of a team regardless of their roles, technical background.
Today, hundreds of business teams use Acho to transform their processes and unlock more value from their data than ever before. Team Acho is engineering-focused and collaborative. Recently closed a Seed Round by Y Combinator, VCs, and industry leaders, we are setting off to solve some of the hardest problems in the data space today.
As an engineer, you'll work on a variety of interesting products and problems for our customers. You'll generate great product ideas, as well as architect, implement, and release them.
We love engineers owning projects, from start to finish. For example, new features often start off as customer ideas. So it could be your responsibility to talk to the customer and scope out what a solution might look like, in addition to actually building it, testing it, documenting it, and releasing iterating on it with the customer.
💠 Qualification
BS or Master degree in Computer Science
1-3 years of experience in Frontend Development
You are passionate about technology and thrive in a dynamic environment with a focus on creative innovation over absolute perfection
Architecting, building, and maintaining web applications
Proficient in modern web client-side technologies and frameworks (Experience with Vue.js or React.js is preferred)
Excellent communication skills in verbal and written English
🛠️ Necessary Skills
HTML, CSS, and Javascript
Modern JavaScript Framework (Experience with Vue.js is preferred)
Experience with SSR
SEO Optimization
Webpack
API Design
Database (MySQL, MongoDB, etc.)
🌎 Website
https://acho.io/?=bookface
❓ FAQ
What does the interview process look like?
We’ll reach out for an intro call after reviewing your resume. We may follow by scheduling a technical interview. If the tech round went well, we’d give you a small project. After assessing the project, we’d be ready and make an offer.
Can I work remotely?
Yes. We support a hybrid of remote and on-site work environments.
What’s it like working for a startup?
Being a small nimble team is the best way to grow fast both personally and collectively as a team. We tend to debunk some of the stereotypes about working at a startup. We rarely work overtime. Our processes are pretty clear and structured. Our goal is super defined. Our financial risk is actually a lot lower than a lot of established businesses as we have zero debt, fewer commitments/overheads, and actually grow each month.
What can I expect in terms of compensation?
We aim to compensate competitively. Additionally, we ensure a “happy rate” and boost in pay for every milestone we achieve together.
What’s unique about this role?
The Front-end will work closely with our product designer and ship amazing features that delight users. Different from the full-stack SDE position, this role will spend more time on UI/UX, design, and business logic.
What’s special about team Acho?
We’re a group of builders who aren’t afraid of the toughest engineering challenges. The world as we understand it is a big puzzle with tons of problems to be solved. The bigger our goal is, the more and harder the problems become. We’d always want to be the team that solves the most, and hardest problems. 
Technology
         HTML &amp; CSS
         Javascript (Vue.js, bootstrap, axios, redux, google analytics, jquery, datatables, webpack)
         RESTful API Design &amp; Implementation (OpenAPI)
         MySQL Commands &amp; Utilities (Mysqldump...)
         Elasticsearch
         DynamoDB
         Docker &amp; Docker-compose
         Python3 (Requests, PyMySQL, SQLAlchemy, Scrapy, multiprocessing, apscheduler, pandas, numpy...)
         Linux Commands &amp; Utilities (Ubuntu, screen, crontab)
         Kubernetes (GKE)
         Load Balancer (Ingress)
         Compute Engine (GCE)
         Cloud Endpoint
         MySQL (Cloud SQL)
         Redis</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$200K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>0</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA / Los Angeles, CA, US / Remote (US; CA)</location><title>Fullstack Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>15995</job_reference><company>Sapling.ai</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/5aa6fac6d2489885ce08d4c58cabcc5b5a131c29.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/sapling-ai</company_website><company_description>Language models for enterprise applications.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/15995</url><description>About Sapling.ai
Sapling's API and SDK help integrate language models into enterprise applications.
Sapling's assistant sits on top of CRMs and messaging platforms to help customer-facing teammates more efficiently compose responses.
About the role
Skills: JavaScript, Python, Amazon Web Services (AWS)
We are looking for a full-time engineer to work with on our Python/C++ backend as well as build frontend interfaces for our language model products.
You will:
Have critical impact on Sapling growing its set of enterprise customers.
Build integrations and infrastructure for an language model-powered system.
Work closely with the founders.
Have a flexible work schedule.
Learn about early stage startups and machine learning/deep learning from Berkeley/Stanford AI grads.
Technology
Python, C++
AWS, Kubernetes, Terraform
Machine learning/deep learning/natural language processing
React, Flask</description><min_compensation>$100K</min_compensation><max_compensation>$150K</max_compensation><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame>Annual</compensation_time_frame><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>Boston, MA / Remote</location><title>Software Engineer I</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>15570</job_reference><company>Apprentice Health</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/2bac8275fdcfe971bb93e76e851a743444aaf613.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/apprentice-health</company_website><company_description>We deploy sensors and software that increase hospital efficiency.</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/15570</url><description>About Apprentice Health
Apprentice Health helps clinical teams deliver exceptional care to more patients by improving the usage of their most valuable resources - clinical time, space, and equipment. We increase the number of patients that can access care, improve the patient experience, and improve workdays for clinical staff.
About the role
Skills: Python, React, Machine Learning, Internet of Things (IoT), Amazon Web Services (AWS)
Apprentice Health is a fast-paced startup using IoT and cloud technologies to optimize clinical workflows in a way that improves the patient experience and reduces the cost of health care. We use edge gateways and embedded devices to measure physician and patient workflows in real time. This feeds into our cloud architecture and powers a range of predictive models that optimize clinic experience. We’re looking for bright, mission-driven engineers who are excited to dive into a wide array of technologies and come up with novel solutions to challenging technical and operational problems.
Responsibilities: With guidance from senior engineers, implement front-end and back-end components to support our analytics and real-time location UI Provide input on product and system design Follow up on bugs or issues, root-causing them and coming up with appropriate solutions Suggest new or different approaches to a problem or process to help build our application and our team
General Requirements: Be hard-working, intelligent, and willing to learn Don’t be dedicated to a specific technology or language; be willing to work outside your comfort zone to use what works in the situation at hand Be flexible and willing to take on roles or responsibilities that may be outside your area of expertise Know that every project is a team effort, and be willing to help out others when they need it Be humble, and willing to admit when you don’t know something Have at least a bachelor’s degree, or equivalent work experience Be excited about IoT, location-aware systems and real-world applications of software solutions
Technical Requirements: Have a proven track record of projects you’ve worked on from start to finish (personal projects are great for this) Know how to build code that’s unit testable, reusable and simple to understand Feel comfortable on a command line Understand good API design and documentation Have experience with serverless or cloud-based infrastructure
Nice to Haves: Python experience Experience in AWS Experience building front-ends in ReactJS CI/CD or DevOps experience Experience working in a PCI-, HIPAA- or SOC2-compliant environment
Technology
We leverage sensors (IoT), software, and AI (ML, NLP) to accomplish our mission. Reach out to us if you're interested in learning more.</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>1</remote></job><job><location>San Francisco, CA / Remote</location><title>Senior Software Engineer</title><country>United States</country><job_type>Fulltime</job_type><posted_at /><job_reference>15183</job_reference><company>Instacart</company><company_logo>https://bookface-images.s3.amazonaws.com/small_logos/9750fca21baaee75e035f1baaf58df8e2f5dcc67.png</company_logo><company_website>https://www.workatastartup.com/companies/instacart</company_website><company_description>Marketplace for grocery delivery and pickup</company_description><category /><url>https://www.workatastartup.com/jobs/15183</url><description>About Instacart
Instacart is the North American leader in online grocery and one of the fastest-growing companies in e-commerce. Instacart’s same-day delivery and pickup services bring fresh groceries and everyday essentials to busy people and families across the U.S. and Canada in as fast as an hour. Since its founding in 2012, Instacart has become an essential service for millions of families, while also serving as an immediate, flexible earnings opportunity for hundreds of thousands of shoppers across North America. The company partners with more than 350 retailers and delivers from more than 25,000 stores across more than 5,500 cities in North America. Today, Instacart is accessible to more than 85% of households in the U.S. and more than 70% of households in Canada.
About the role
We're looking for experienced engineers to join our fast moving team. We work on a range of interesting and challenging problems, from supporting thousands of concurrent shoppers and processing millions of data points in real time, to determining the best route for deliveries and predicting store inventory levels.
We love full-stack engineers, not only capable of building a solution but owning the problem end to end. There is a tremendous amount of opportunity in front of us, and joining now gives you a chance to grow your career and interests as we succeed.
Responsibilities:
You will be part of a small team, with a large amount of ownership and responsibility for managing things directly. You will ship high-quality solutions with a sense of urgency and speed. You will work closely with product managers, other teams, and both internal and external stakeholders, owning a large part of the process from problem understanding to shipping the solution. You will have the freedom to suggest and drive organization-wide initiatives.
Requirements:
Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, computer engineering, electrical engineering or equivalent work experience Self-motivation and an enjoyment for a startup environment A blend of product, system, and people knowledge that lets you jump into a fast paced environment and contribute from day one Strong knowledge of common Web technology such as Ruby on Rails and/or Python and/or JavaScript frameworks (React, AngularJS, Ember or Backbone.js) An ability to balance a sense of urgency with shipping high quality and pragmatic solutions Extensive experience working with a large codebase and cross-functional teams A strong sense of ownership
Desirable:
Interest or experience in distributed systems Strong ability to analyze data Experience with AI / machine learning / data modeling iOS / Android experience
Technology
From a technology point of view, our platform is complex, rapidly scaling and processing millions of transactions in real-time all of the time. Our technology coupled with operational expertise enables Instacart to deliver fresh groceries in as little as an hour. We use a modern stack including Ruby/Rails, Python, React and many more technologies.</description><min_compensation /><max_compensation /><compensation_currency>USD</compensation_currency><compensation_time_frame /><remote>1</remote></job></jobs></source>